<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jobs xmlns="https://adview.online/XMLSchema"
      xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
      xsi:schemaLocation="https://adview.online/XMLSchema
      https://adview.online/XMLSchemaOutbound.xsd">
<job>
	<id><![CDATA[454789870]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[https://adview.online/dispatch/job/feed/healthcare-consultant-senior-consultant?utm_source=feed-200&utm_medium=postjobfree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[Healthcare - Consultant & Senior Consultant]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[We are currently looking for Consultants and Senior Consultants to join a market leading boutique healthcare services provider, and make a real difference to patient outcomes across social care and health.<br><br>Company<br><br>Operating in the new Health and Social Care landscape, this team supports commissioners of health and social care to identify, develop, and deliver their commissioning objectives and strategies. With a strong track record of strategic planning and design but with a very big focus on delivery and implementation by supporting clients to operate as effective, high performing commissioning organisations, working with leadership teams and staff groups to develop their commissioning skills and capabilities; embed core commissioning and delivery processes; and ensure that resources are used both efficiently and effectively.<br><br>Candidate requirements<br><br>In order to succeed in this challenging role, you will have a proven track record of developing and implementing commissioning strategies and plans. Experience of establishing effective models of joint or integrated commissioning would also be highly desirable, as would consultancy skills and experience.<br><br>The successful candidates will possess strong technical capabilities including project and programme management; business case generation; outcome evaluation; patient, service user, and wider stakeholder engagement; comprehensive understanding of the commissioning cycle, a deep knowledge of care provision.<br><br>Valuable Skills and Experiences:<br><br>Commissioning<br><br>Programme and project managers<br>Strategic perspective and experience (for strategy interventions)<br>OD and change management experience<br>Performance management/modelling skills (dashboards)<br>Ability to work autonomously<br>Commercial and business development experience<br>Can provide illustrations where the candidate demonstrated the ability to effectively engage, influence, and ensure commitment of stakeholders at various levels with credibility<br>Able to build and maintain relationships<br>Ability to work collaboratively with others leading interfacing projects<br>Organisational Development<br><br>Strategic perspective and experience (for strategy interventions)<br>Organisational design and organisational development experience<br>Designing and delivering OD interventions<br>Change management experience<br>Cultural analysis and change<br>Leadership development<br>Strategy development – including vision, mission, values and objectives<br>Staff and leadership engagement<br>Programme and project management<br>Performance management system experience (individual)<br>Ability to work autonomously<br>Commercial and business development experience<br>Engagement, collaboration and relationship building skills<br>Can provide illustrations where the candidate demonstrated the ability to effectively engage, influence, and ensure commitment of stakeholders at various levels with credibility<br>Ability to work collaboratively with others leading interfacing projects<br>]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[London]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[City of London]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[London]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[London]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[EC3A]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[60595.96]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[60595.96]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[annum]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[Management and Consultancy]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[Mindbench]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[2019-08-16]]></expiration-date>
</job>
<job>
	<id><![CDATA[454789871]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[https://adview.online/dispatch/job/feed/german-and-spanish-speaking-top-graduates-with-maths-engineering-science-degrees?utm_source=feed-200&utm_medium=postjobfree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[German and Spanish speaking top graduates with Maths, Engineering, Science degrees]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[Our clients are fast growing specialist boutique consulting firms. They have immediate requirement for top-notch graduates<br>in a numerate subject who are also bi-lingual Spanish or German. <br><br>You will undertake modelling work in the TMT, Financial Services or Manufacturing sectors to better understand the industry and improve the clients performance. <br><br>You will have a First Class degrees in Maths, Physics or Engineering from a tier-1 university such as Oxford, Cambridge, LSE or Imperial. You will have good Excel modelling skills to an advanced level. You will be an English speaker and be fluent (ideally native) in German or Spanish. <br><br>We have opportunities in London and outside London. Please send your CV to richard@mindbench.co.uk <br><br>]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[London]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[City of London]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[London]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[Central London / West London]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[EC3A]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[27229.31]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[27229.31]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[annum]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[Management and Consultancy]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[Mindbench]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[2019-08-16]]></expiration-date>
</job>
<job>
	<id><![CDATA[454789879]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[https://adview.online/dispatch/job/feed/fast-track-opportunity-for-top-perfroming-graduates-and-consultants?utm_source=feed-200&utm_medium=postjobfree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[Fast track opportunity for top perfroming graduates and consultants]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[Our client is an exceptional strategy boutique which provides strategy and change management advice for health authorities, local government and and higher education bodies.<br><br>Based in London, they are experiencing rapid growth and offer an outstanding environment for progression and personal development. <br>The work is really impactful and offers the chance to make a significant difference to how public services are delivered.The projects are London based so there is very little travel required - this is a truly unique opportunity for highly motivated graduates and consultants. <br><br>We are looking for top graduates with a 2:1 or above from Oxford, Cambridge or a leading redbrick university. You will also be comfortable with maths and Excel, and be very interested in working in public services with a specialist consultign firm. You will have grit and determination to get things done and want to work in a fast growing small business. Ideally you will have some consulting experience or experience from a think tank, the civil service fast stream, the Bank of England or other government related organisation. <br><br>Please send your CV for review to richard@mindbench.co.uk]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[London]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[City of London]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[London]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[Central London]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[EC3A]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[27046.37]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[27046.37]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[annum]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[Management and Consultancy]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[Mindbench]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[2019-08-16]]></expiration-date>
</job>
<job>
	<id><![CDATA[454789880]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[https://adview.online/dispatch/job/feed/operational-research-top-supply-chain-analysts?utm_source=feed-200&utm_medium=postjobfree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[Operational Research - Top Supply Chain Analysts]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[Our client is a growing supply chain consulting firm working in the UK and internationally. They are expanding rapidly and are looking for top graduates with Operational Research experience.<br><br>You will be a good graduate with:<br>- Strong numerical analysis skills (the ability to apply mathematics to real-life business situations)<br>- must have strong spreadsheet and database skills<br>- logical reasoning skills- operational research<br><br>Ideally you will also have this experience:<br>- Specific logistics and supply chain experience<br>- FMCG experience (retail, wholesale or manufacturing)<br>- Awareness of Lean / Six-Sigma / World Class Manufacturing<br>- Supply chain, logistics or operational research qualifications- language skills – English plus another European language (French, German, Italian, Spanish <br><br>Language skills – English plus another European language (French, German, Italian, Spanish <br>Please send your CV to richard@mindbench.co.uk]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[London]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[City of London]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[London]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[London]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[EC3A]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[33053.84]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[33053.84]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[annum]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[Management and Consultancy]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[Mindbench]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[2019-08-16]]></expiration-date>
</job>
<job>
	<id><![CDATA[454789881]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[https://adview.online/dispatch/job/feed/growth-strategy-and-innovation-consultants-and-managers-excellent-boutiques?utm_source=feed-200&utm_medium=postjobfree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[Growth Strategy and Innovation Consultants and Managers - Excellent Boutiques]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[Mindbench is working with top boutiques specialising in innovation and also with MBB firms globally.<br><br>Senior consultants design and run projects that inject entrepreneurial spirit into corporate clients. As a senior consultant or a Manager you will be the engine room for the business in terms of project management and delivery. This means understanding clients’ needs, and going that extra mile to make sure the team delivers great work.<br><br>What our client looks for: <br><br>o A track record of launching new innovations, either for a consultancy or in-house within a corporate function <br>o Previous experience in a consulting environment, ideally in a strategy, growth or proposition role <br>• Proven ability to lead teams and run end to end project delivery<br>• Ability to take ownership of accounts and in identifying and developing on-sale opportunities <br>• Ability to construct and deliver inspiring and convincing arguments both on paper and on your feet <br>• Excellent facilitation and presentation skills, confidence in delivery <br><br><br>Title: Consultant, 3yrs experience + <br><br>As a consultant you’ll form the backbone of our projects and be proactive, resourceful and collaborative in creating high-quality work. This includes helping to facilitate workshops, working in joint teams with clients and creating clear, well-designed outputs.<br><br>What we look for <br><br>• A minimum of 3 years’ relevant experience:<br>o Previous experience in a consulting environment, ideally in a strategy, growth or proposition role <br>o Ideally some experience of innovation in your previous experience or outside of work<br>• Previous experience in developing and delivering high quality outputs<br>• Previous experience facilitating and running workshops <br><br>Non role specific requirements<br><br>In addition to the above, they look for the following: <br><br>• A blend of creative and analytical skills <br>• An entrepreneurial drive, someone who is genuinely interested in and/or getting involved in new ventures<br>• A constantly optimistic and a can-do attitude<br>• A desire to put the client interest at heart and go the extra mile to build strong and loyal relationships<br>• Excitement and interest in the work and above all pride in the quality of the outcomes and outputs<br>• A fun and interesting person, someone who will help shape their culture and get involved<br><br><br>What they can offer you<br><br>• A genuinely entrepreneurial culture with the chance to shape your career as you wish <br>• A fun, enthusiastic and positive place to work<br>• A broad range of experience across clients and sectors <br>• A strong career pathway and far reaching opportunities <br><br>Please send your CV to richard@mindbench.co.uk]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[London]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[City of London]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[London]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[Central London]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[EC3A]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[50417.52]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[50417.52]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[annum]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[Management and Consultancy]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[Mindbench]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[2019-08-16]]></expiration-date>
</job>
<job>
	<id><![CDATA[454789883]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[https://adview.online/dispatch/job/feed/top-tier-operational-improvement-consultants-any-industry-business-or-consulting-experience?utm_source=feed-200&utm_medium=postjobfree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[Top Tier Operational Improvement Consultants - any industry, business or consulting experience]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[<p><strong>About The Company:</strong></p> <p>This company brings together the world's most talented individuals from a wide range of backgrounds spanning engineering, science, mathematics, business &amp; economics, languages, law, social sciences and beyond. With emotional intelligence and a unique approach, they work in partnership with their clients to deliver market leading operational, financial and quality improvements. They implement transformational, award-winning change across a wide range of sectors for some of the world's most successful, innovative organisations. Projects vary in size and complexity, but they are high-profile, multi-million pound programmes, which are carried out on a unique ‘no results, no fees’ basis. It is challenging and incredibly rewarding work, rooted in analysis, problem solving and insightful communication. The track record of delivering huge results along with an inspiring work culture means headcount and turnover has been growing on average at a rate of 30% annually for the last 12 years.</p> <p><strong>Background to the Role:</strong></p> <p>Continuous success and demand for business means that we are recruiting at all levels across the consulting teams. Applicants do not need to have had previous consulting experience – we are looking for people with a strong academic background and experience in general business, industry or consulting.</p> <p><strong>The Role:</strong></p> <p>All project work with clients commences with an assessment phase to understand the opportunities for organisational or operational improvement. Once the opportunities for improvement have been identified and quantified, a team of consultants will work on the client’s sites to deliver these. A project’s length can vary from several weeks to six months or longer.</p> <p>The programmes consultants work are normally complex, multi-faceted and will involve delivering real and measurable results for our clients. Depending on your previous experience, soon after joining you could be taking ownership for and personally delivering performance improvement in a discrete area of a project, or you may soon be managing an entire site-wide improvement project, or even be managing a number of sites and improvement processes simultaneously. Comprehensive, tailored training is given to all new joiners upon starting and throughout your career.</p> <p>At all levels, client relationship management is an important aspect of the role, and you will work extremely collaboratively with clients. All consultants are responsible for developing relationships with key senior stakeholders and ensuring regular project reviews take place.</p> <p>Beyond day to day client project work, all the people in the company have a broader remit of supporting the growth and development of the consultancy in general. This entrepreneurial spirit is present throughout the company and might involve working with the recruitment team to continue to find us great candidates, or organising internal review meetings or social events, or helping develop our knowledge capture processes. Everyone is encouraged to get involved in growing and developing the company.</p> <p><br><strong>Skills and Attributes:</strong></p> <p>We are looking for candidates from an operational consulting background in top tier firms, with experience.</p> <p>Essential Attributes:</p> <p>Successful candidates must:</p> <ul><li>Be strong, effective communicators at all levels with the ability to build and sustain relationships</li>  <li>Have the ability to work effectively as part of a team, with a collaborative approach</li>  <li>Be flexible and adaptable</li>  <li>Thrive on early responsibility and be self-motivated and driven to succeed</li>  <li>Be highly numerate with a logical mind-set and strong analytical and conceptual skills</li> </ul><p>You should also have:</p> <ul><li>An undergraduate degree - minimum 2:1 from top university, preferable in a numerate subject e.g. Engineering, Maths, Physics, Economics (non-numerate degrees will only be considered if you have A at A Level Maths or equivalent)  </li>  <li>Experience in consultancy or internal roles that develop a similar skill-set (there are many roles and levels and we will consider candidates with varied experience from 1 year through to more experienced candidates)</li> </ul><p><strong>Location and Travel Requirements:</strong></p> <p>Clients are based across the UK and Europe. Therefore travel and time away from home will be necessary Monday to Friday. During this time all reasonable expenses will be covered. You will not work at the weekends and will always be home by 6pm on a Friday.</p>]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[55939.38]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[55939.38]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[annum]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[Management and Consultancy]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[Mindbench]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[2019-08-16]]></expiration-date>
</job>
<job>
	<id><![CDATA[454789885]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[https://adview.online/dispatch/job/feed/junior-consultantconsultant-operations-practice-in-big-3-strategy-house?utm_source=feed-200&utm_medium=postjobfree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[Junior Consultant/Consultant - Operations Practice in Big 3 Strategy House]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[<p>We are working with one of the world's most prestigious consultancy firms on growing their UK Operations practice. We are looking to recruit 4-5 Junior Consultant or Consultant level individuals to focus on Operations cases. Due to recent successes in the Operations practice, we are looking to recruit individuals with both <strong>Industry </strong>and/or <strong>Consulting </strong>experience to deliver against expansion plans.<br><br> These roles are on the generalist career track with alignment to the Operations Practice Area.<br><br><strong>Required Experience:</strong></p> <ul><li><strong>Junior Consultant</strong> -  either consultancy or relevant industry experience.</li>  <li><strong>Consultant</strong> -  ideally a combination of both consultancy and industry experience.</li> </ul><ul><li>Consulting experience (McKinsey, Bain, Booz,  A.T. Kearney, Roland Berger, Oliver Wyman, Accenture, Big 4,  Stroud) <strong>and/or</strong> relevant experience preferably in Industrial/Consumer Goods or Automotive and Logistics Services sector (Tesco, Sainsburys, Next, M&amp;S, Morrisons, Boots, P&amp;G, Unilever, MARS, Kraft or Rolls Royce). </li>  <li>Experience in introduction and implementation of Lean Manufacturing concepts or Six Sigma.</li>  <li>Strong presence - proven leadership skills (more at C level);  demonstrated ability to influence and inspire others</li>  <li>Academic qualifications: Minimum 2:1 University degree (preferably 1st Class) ideally from top UK school, ideally in a related field.</li>  <li>Extensive travel required - to work on projects with our large global clients.</li>  <li>European language beneficial but not essential.</li> </ul><p><strong>How to Apply:</strong><br> Please Email CV to richard@mindbench.co.ukquoting reference number J10001553 and either <strong>C </strong>for Consultant or <strong>JC </strong>for Junior Consultant position.<br><br> Please send your CV to   richard@mindbench.co.uk</p>]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[London]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[City of London]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[London]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[London Based]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[EC3A]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[69145.13]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[69145.13]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[annum]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[Management and Consultancy]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[Mindbench]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[2019-08-16]]></expiration-date>
</job>
<job>
	<id><![CDATA[454789888]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[https://adview.online/dispatch/job/feed/business-analysts-and-consultants-public-sector-focused-consulting-firm?utm_source=feed-200&utm_medium=postjobfree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[Business Analysts and Consultants - Public Sector Focused Consulting firm]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[<p>Are you excited about the power of technology to transform the way that organisations operate and meet their users’ needs? Do you want to make a real difference and bring about meaningful change to a variety of organisations through digital change?</p> <p><br> The company:<br> They are a small but fast-growing consultancy, with clients and partners across the criminal justice sector, local authorities, charities, and a range of private sector organisations in areas such as financial services and technology. This is an exciting time to join an early-stage company and help shape its future direction.</p> <p><br> The role:<br> They are looking for ambitious and keen people with excellent interpersonal, problem-solving and analytical skills to join our friendly and high-performing team. They need people who are digitally savvy and passionate about the role of technology in making organisations ready for the modern world. You’ll be working with our clients to transform their organisations and the way they deliver services, combining business analysis and digital service design. This is a fantastic opportunity to be involved in some cutting-edge assignments and to build on your existing skills, working with small teams of energetic, intelligent and creative people.<br> They have a comprehensive and successful development programme to help you build the skills you need to operate at an even higher level and a senior team with wide-ranging experiences to coach and share ideas with you.</p> <p>What they are looking for:<br> You’ll need an inquiring mind, great communication and presentation skills, and the drive to succeed. You’ll also need to be good at working with other people, well organised and able to think on your feet. A positive outlook, enthusiasm and willingness to learn are essential.<br> You may have experience from a startup, consultancy or transformation background. You’ll have built up strong skills and experience in mapping or modelling business processes and redesigning services for the digital era. You’ll be able to use common business process mapping techniques, and customer centric approaches to mapping customer journeys.<br> Prior experience of working in a government setting would be advantageous as well as experience of working as part of a cross-functional agile delivery team, working alongside Service Designers, Product Owner, Delivery Manager, and User Researchers.</p> <p>Please send your CV to richard@mindbench.co.uk</p>]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[London]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[City of London]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[London]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[London]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[EC3A]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[43727.45]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[43727.45]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[annum]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[Management and Consultancy]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[Mindbench]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[2019-08-16]]></expiration-date>
</job>
<job>
	<id><![CDATA[454789964]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[https://adview.online/dispatch/job/feed/digital-analyst-specialist-public-sector?utm_source=feed-200&utm_medium=postjobfree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[Digital Analyst - Specialist Public Sector]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[<p><strong>Digital Analyst </strong></p> <p>An exciting opportunity to join a well-respected and growing boutique consulting firm, with an impressive client portfolio.</p> <p>Are you excited about the power of technology to transform the way that organisations operate and meet their users’ needs?</p> <p>Do you want to make a real difference and bring about meaningful change to a variety of organisations through digital change?</p> <p>Prior experience of working in a government setting would be advantageous as well as experience of working as part of a cross-functional agile delivery team, working alongside Service Designers, Product Owner, Delivery Manager, and User Researchers.</p> <p><strong>The company</strong></p> <p>They are a small but fast-growing consultancy, with clients and partners across the criminal justice sector, local authorities, charities, and a range of private sector organisations in areas such as financial services and technology. They help our clients transform their organisations and the way they deliver services.</p> <p><strong>The role</strong></p> <p>They are looking for ambitious and keen people with excellent interpersonal, problem-solving and analytical skills to join our friendly and high-performing team. They need people who are digitally savvy and passionate about the role of technology in making organisations ready for the modern world.</p> <p>You’ll be working with our clients to transform their organisations and the way they deliver services, combining business analysis and digital service design.</p> <p>This is a fantastic opportunity to be involved in some cutting-edge assignments and to build on your existing skills, working with small teams of energetic, intelligent and creative people.</p> <p>They have a comprehensive and successful development programme to help you build the skills you need to operate at an even higher level and a senior team with wide-ranging experiences to coach and share ideas with you.</p> <p><strong>What they are looking for</strong></p> <p>You’ll need an inquiring mind, great communication and presentation skills, and the drive to succeed. You’ll also need to be good at working with other people, well organised and able to think on your feet. A positive outlook, enthusiasm and willingness to learn are essential.</p> <p>You’ll have experience, and may come from a startup, consultancy or transformation background. You’ll have built up strong skills and experience in mapping or modelling business processes and redesigning services for the digital era. You’ll be able to use common business process mapping techniques, and customer centric approaches to mapping customer journeys.  </p> <p>Prior experience of working in a government setting would be advantageous as well as experience of working as part of a cross-functional agile delivery team, working alongside Service Designers, Product Owner, Delivery Manager, and User Researchers.</p> <p>Their Business Analysts have experience of working within a range of industries and sectors and bring a diverse set of skills and experiences. Some of the qualities that contribute to their success in our Company include the ability to apply their skills and experience to a wide range of areas, to pick things up quickly, and to grapple with unknowns and ambiguity. </p> <p>You will need SC Security Clearance for this role or willing and eligible to apply for it. A key requisite for SC clearance is that you should be able to provide evidence of 5 years’ recent residency in the UK. </p> <p>You’ll be able to demonstrate to us how good you are at:</p> <ul><li>Gathering and interpreting information from a range of sources including workshops, interviews and written documents</li>  <li>Working with business users and senior stakeholders to understand and map their services and business processes, including identifying service users, mapping the different stages in a services journey / processes, quantifying the resources and time of each stage, and understanding where the costs in each service are.</li>  <li>Using a range of techniques to analyse situations, and quickly gain actionable insights into how to resolve complex problems and identify transformational opportunities within business services and processes.</li>  <li>Coming up with clever, innovative, and workable new ideas and models – particularly around digital service design</li>  <li>Being adaptable and responsive – you’ll use a range of techniques and see what works, and ideally you’ll be experienced in working in Agile and/or fast moving and complex environments</li>  <li>Presenting your findings and ideas in a way that sets out complex issues very simply and explains your logic</li>  <li>Working with other people to unlock problems and change the way they see things</li>  <li>Developing credibility and expertise quickly in unfamiliar or new environments.</li> </ul><p>This is a very exciting role for the right candidate who is passionate about problem-solving and curious about the world.</p> <p>They can promise that the work will be varied and interesting, and will give you lots of opportunities to develop and grow. They will help you learn and develop, and there is real scope for you to shape the future direction of the company, by leading teams and assignments, and taking responsibility for shaping our services, developing our ways of working and marketing what we can do.</p> <p>In return they will offer a competitive package, and the chance to work on some fascinating assignments with our clients from across the government, not-for-profit and private sectors.</p> <p>Please send your CV to richard@mindbench.co.uk</p>]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[London]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[City of London]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[London]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[Central London]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[EC3A]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[40251.71]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[40251.71]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[annum]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[Management and Consultancy]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[Mindbench]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[2019-08-16]]></expiration-date>
</job>
<job>
	<id><![CDATA[454789980]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[https://adview.online/dispatch/job/feed/consultants-managers-and-senior-managers-fmcg-manufacturing-germany?utm_source=feed-200&utm_medium=postjobfree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[Consultants, Managers and Senior Managers - FMCG, Manufacturing Germany]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[<p>Our client is a major consulting global consulting firm focusing on operational improvement. They have 400 consultants, operating from 27 offices, working in over 75 countries and representing more than 40 different nationalities currently support more than 900 programmes using a unique “tandem approach” with their clients.</p> <p>They offer: </p> <p>A <strong>global</strong> <strong>international group</strong> offering</p> <ul><li>a complete on-boarding process to make you quickly part of our team</li>  <li>a close cooperation with their colleagues for international offices</li>  <li>the possibility to work for the most globally renowned companies, our clients</li>  <li>an extensive excellent development program, both internal and external, (including technical, methodological and soft skills training).</li> </ul><p>Be part of <strong>teams</strong> where you will find</p> <ul><li>a pleasant, relaxed operating environment</li>  <li>a flat hierarchy, with transparent process and short decision lines</li>  <li>a “family” working atmosphere, with serious and fun</li>  <li>a strong team spirit (office days on Mondays, monthly training days and company events such as summer parties or Christmas celebrations, they create opportunities to get to know and exchange in a relaxed atmosphere).</li> </ul><p>Build you <strong>career</strong> in an environment where you will be able to</p> <ul><li>collect experience in a wide range of projects and environments</li>  <li>access strong methodologies as well as numerous training opportunities, that will give you the optimal conditions for your further development</li>  <li>have long term perspectives</li>  <li>develop your competencies with our innovative consulting approach, the 4 dynamic combination, that bring together technical skills, human skills and strategy skills, giving each of our consultant the ability to grow in all dimensions</li> </ul><p>They focus on several areas: </p> <p><strong>Value Dynamics</strong> - Where and how they create and capture more value (e.g. keeping a clear link between strategy and actions asking all the time which value the company programmes and projects are bringing to the shareholders and stakeholders)</p> <p><strong>Flow Dynamics</strong> - How they generate more value developing the tools, methodologies and systems to improve the performance and results of the key value chain processes in terms of flow effectiveness</p> <p><strong>Asset Dynamics - </strong>How they generate more value developing the tools, methodologies and systems to improve the performance and results of the key value chain processes in terms of resource efficiency</p> <p><strong>Human Dynamics</strong> - How they develop and motivate human capital enabling their clients' organisation and leadership to adopt the new values, mind-sets and behaviours needed to successfully drive the new processes</p> <p>Their people bring together hands-on experience and expertise spanning a wide range of sectors and functional capabilities.</p> <p><strong>Job Description:</strong></p> <p>Job Function:</p> <p>Senior Consultants and Managers will be part the German office (Berlin based) and working on key projects, analysing customer requirements, conducting customer workshops to help organisations to solve issues, create value, maximize growth and improve business performance. They will also be identifying options for the organization and suggesting recommendations for change, as well as advising on the implementation of solutions.</p> <p>They will be supporting the delivery of OpEx Programmes &amp; Improvement Projects having as a primary objective to make <strong>continuous </strong>and <strong>breakthrough improvements </strong>possible by enabling managers and their teams to achieve specific goals. On each assignment they will work as part of a consulting team assembled to provide the correct mix of skills needed. They will deliver short term results as well as work with the client to prepare the results of the future.</p> <p><strong>The progression of their clients is their obsession.</strong></p> <p>Skills and Competencies :</p> <p>Key skills</p> <ul><li>Having the ability to analyse complex problems and deliver insightful and practical solutions;</li>  <li>Having the ability to turn data into information which have practical use.</li>  <li>Identifying issues and forming hypotheses and solutions, enjoys understanding a problem and solving it in a systematic manner</li>  <li>Presenting findings and recommendations to clients;</li>  <li>Implementing recommendations/solutions and ensuring the client receives the necessary assistance to carry it all out;</li>  <li>Leading and managing those within the team, including analysts;</li>  <li>Having good project management skills (budget, time &amp; resources);</li>  <li>Liaising with the client to keep them informed of progress and to make relevant decisions;</li>  <li>Experiencing the full project life cycle from concept through to implementation.</li>  <li>Practical, masters the theory and will show “how it is done”.</li>  <li>Proven ability of combining technical and emotional intelligence.</li>  <li>Open to suggestions and honest about mistakes; proactively seeks for feedback.</li>  <li>Keen to learn and work to their standard methods and tools.</li> </ul><p>Additional requirements:</p> <ul><li>A bachelor’s and master’s degree from a reputable university (an Engineering or Business degree, along with an MBA, is favourable);</li>  <li>Excellent written and spoken communication skills in English;</li>  <li>Additional languages are a plus (Spanish, French, Italian…)</li>  <li>Prior management consulting experience is preferred;</li>  <li>Ability to travel 4 days a week with 3-4 nights away from home</li> </ul><p>Has <strong>routinely</strong> <strong>applied</strong> standard methods of operational excellence such as 5S, Kaizen, Kanban, Cause-effect diagram, SMED, OEE incl. losses etc. Can use these methods (candidates that have been part of teams applying the methods without using them themselves will not be considered).</p> <p>Has the ability to train and coach members of the team (client and internal) to apply these methodologies. Has strong <strong>communication skills</strong>: clear and precise communication style, straight to the point. Is an active listener, with the ability to ask the right questions, to speak with energy and conviction. <strong>Strong team member</strong>, actively involved and involving everyone.</p> <p>Is strongly <strong>result-oriented</strong> and has a structured way of working, with a strong focus on result and quality of deliverables. Is attached to its own performance as well as the team’s performance. A high level of motivation, resilience and <strong>integrity</strong>. Has experience in <strong>production companies</strong> with large facilities such as automotive, chemical, metal production, metalworking, pharmaceuticals, etc. no focus in assembly chain.</p> <p>Please send you CV to richard@mindbench.co.uk</p>]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[Berlin]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[61362.34]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[61362.34]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[annum]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[Management and Consultancy]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[Mindbench]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[2019-08-16]]></expiration-date>
</job>
<job>
	<id><![CDATA[454790787]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[https://adview.online/dispatch/job/feed/analysts-for-procurement-specialist-consulting-firm?utm_source=feed-200&utm_medium=postjobfree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[Analysts for Procurement Specialist Consulting Firm]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[<p><strong>London based Management Consultancy – Analyst</strong></p> <p><br> Our clients are procurement experts, and they help clients to identify, deliver and sustain improvement opportunities. Their international team combines unparalleled procurement expertise and industry experience with a unique blend of intellectual capital and technology to deliver real results and advance our clients’ procurement capability. Their service offering includes a range of deployment models, from focussed consulting engagements to long-term managed services, all facilitated and powered by their procurement technology and the analytics team.</p> <p>About the role<br> They are looking for highly analytical and structured thinkers to join our growing analytics team on a permanent basis The analytics team is a core function of the client and performs a wide range of analytical tasks for existing and prospective clients. The team are expected to work from our London office, with occasional travel to client locations (UK and worldwide, less than 15% of the time).</p> <p>Job description<br> • Managing end-to-end analytical engagement for clients (e.g. spend insight service)<br> • Supporting business development function with spend analytics<br> • Working with project teams on various ad hoc and long-term analytical assignments<br> • Analysing, compiling and classifying large data sets from various sources, using Excel or SQL<br> • Visualising analyses, using Tableau technology<br> • Preparing client presentations and reports in PowerPoint<br> • Engaging with the project teams and the clients to communicate findings</p> <p>Desired Skills and Experience<br> • Exemplary academic background with ‘A’ grades in A-Level Mathematics and/or Science subjects<br> • A degree in numerically intense discipline, such as Engineering, Mathematics or Science at a top-tier UK University<br> • Genuine interest and affinity for numbers and a knack for data analytics<br> • Problem solving skills and a can-do attitude<br> • Advanced knowledge of analytical tools and programmes (Excel, Access, MySQL etc.) and solid knowledge of the Office suite<br> • Previous experience of Tableau is beneficial, but not essential</p> <p>• European languages, especially German useful </p> <p>Please send your CV to richard@mindbench.co.uk</p>]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[London]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[City of London]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[London]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[Central London]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[EC3A]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[41067.55]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[41067.55]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[annum]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[Management and Consultancy]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[Mindbench]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[2019-08-16]]></expiration-date>
</job>
<job>
	<id><![CDATA[454791204]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[https://adview.online/dispatch/job/feed/strategy-consultant-top-pharma-strategy-consulting-firm-munich?utm_source=feed-200&utm_medium=postjobfree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[Strategy Consultant - top Pharma Strategy Consulting firm, Munich]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[<p>Our  client is a growing specialist strategy consultign firm who are growing internationally and are looking to augment their team in Germany. </p> <p>We have a requirement for a good German speaking Strategy Consultant to join them in Germany. The position would be on a Consultant or Associate Consultant rank depending on experience of the candidate (no Senior Consultant opening).</p> <p>Requirement:</p> <p>- Master degree, preferably PHD or MBA</p> <p>- Top 10% in university</p> <p>- 2-4 years experience in life science management consulting</p> <p>- prior Tier 1 (Mck, BCG, Bain) or Tier 2+ (LEK, Monitor Deloitte, Strategy&amp;, AT Kearney, ZS Associates) [note: pls limit strictly to these companies]</p> <p>- experience in commercial topics</p> <p>- analytically strong</p> <p>- IQ and EQ</p> <p>- curious and open minded personality</p> <p>- some prior international experience</p> <p>- fluent in English, second language preferred</p> <p>- based already in Munich (no removal package available)</p> <p>Base salary would be ~90k€ (plus/minus max. 10% depending on experience) plus 10% bonus.</p> <p>Please send your CV to richard@mindbench.co.uk</p>]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[Munich]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[66079.97]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[66079.97]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[annum]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[Management and Consultancy]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[Mindbench]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[2019-08-16]]></expiration-date>
</job>
<job>
	<id><![CDATA[454792119]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[https://adview.online/dispatch/job/feed/consultants-education-strategy?utm_source=feed-200&utm_medium=postjobfree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[Consultants - Education Strategy]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[<p><strong>Report to Director of UK Office at high growth, global management consultancy firm with opportunity for significant immediate impact</strong></p> <p>Our client are a global boutique consultancy who are a leader in the Education sector and are looking to grow their business across the UK. They seek to add a Senior Consultant to the UK team as they move to the next stage.</p> <p><strong>Company</strong><br><br> The company focuses on delivering strategic benchmarking, analysis and insights to Executive Teams in leading Higher Education institutions within the UK, Australian, New Zealand and Canadian markets. They have seen 8 years of consistent growth and are entering their fourth year in the UK market, with ambitious plans to continue expansion worldwide including Europe, USA and Asia. To achieve these ambitions the business needs to grow its current team of high-quality professionals and strategists in a flat, collaborative structure.<br><br><strong>The Role</strong><br><br> If you are strategically minded, highly analytical, and have a passion for delivering valued insights and building deep and on-going client relationships, then this may be the role for you. The role will be instrumental in the development and growth of a leading high-growth boutique consultancy, reporting directly to the UK Managing Director, representing a significant opportunity for development and career progression to the right candidate.<br><br> In this role, reporting directly to the UK Managing Director you will:<br><br> Take a leading role in the strategic growth and development of the UK business.<br> Lead diagnostics on operational performance in core business function.<br> Work collaboratively with senior clients, including facilitating workshops and delivering value-added insights and recommendations.<br> Use your business experience and consulting skills to draw out and test insights from data models.<br> Produce high quality reports and presentation materials, and present your findings to very senior clients and at large scale senior management meetings<br> Develop strong, trusted relationships with client executives and project teams<br> Jointly manage a dynamic and growing team to deliver high quality consulting<br> Work with and become an expert in cutting edge analytics technologies<br><br><br><strong>Requirements for success</strong><br><br> Your professional experience should include:<br><br> Working at a top consultancy, including managing senior client relationships, and structuring and leading consulting projects (ideally in the area of business services)<br> Generating meaningful insights (including using statistical methods) from large sets of quantitative and qualitative data to support executive decision making.<br> Producing high quality reports and presentations to communicate results and recommendations<br> Developing and delivering business in an entrepreneurial environment (desirable)<br> Working in or with the Higher Education sector (desirable)</p>]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[London]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[City of London]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[London]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[London]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[EC3A]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[66157.63]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[66157.63]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[annum]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[Management and Consultancy]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[Mindbench]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[2019-08-16]]></expiration-date>
</job>
<job>
	<id><![CDATA[454792712]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[https://adview.online/dispatch/job/feed/senior-analyst-client-brand-insights?utm_source=feed-200&utm_medium=postjobfree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[Senior Analyst - Client & Brand Insights]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[<p>Our client is a growing specialist research firm which focuses on providing research and insight on professional services firms. In this role you will be working in the interpreting the data they have about clients’ perceptions to make informed conclusions and presenting these conclusions to our clients.</p> <p>Specifically the type of work that is involved in the role includes: </p> <ul><li>Brand benchmarking: understanding buyers’ views of professional services firms, allowing our customers to understand how they’re perceived versus their competitors.</li>  <li>Message testing: testing marketing messages/campaign ideas with senior executives to understand what resonates, what is credible, what cuts through the noise—and crucially, why.</li>  <li>Client feedback: talking to a firm’s clients to understand the firm’s performance.</li>  <li>Researching strategic brand questions (e.g. should a firm launch a sub-brand?) through the eyes of clients.</li> </ul><p><br> Your responsibilities will include:<br> - Analysis: Make sense of large amounts of data (both qualitative and quantitative) and tease<br> out the stories and trends hidden within it. Develop a good understanding of the professional services market, including sector-wide trends and what’s going on in specific firms.<br> - Data visualisation : Make effective use of data visualisation to tell a story using charts and<br> graphics. For this you will need to have an advanced knowledge of Excel.<br> - Writing: Write reports (in PowerPoint or Word format) that conform to Source’s house style<br> and uphold the integrity of our research using qualitative and/or quantitative data, but<br> which also shimmer with personality and brilliance.<br> - Presentations: Create presentations for clients, using proprietary or custom data sets, and<br> answer their questions. You need to be comfortable using PowerPoint to create engaging<br> and informative presentations and delivering these to audiences of all shapes and sizes.<br> - Blogging: Write blogs that entertain and entice our readership.<br> - Working on bespoke projects: Work on some of the tailored research projects we do for our<br> clients. This could include designing surveys, interviewing senior clients, or analysing and<br> writing up the results.<br> - Project management : Manage the delivery of projects, from briefing colleagues to<br> producing the analysis and presenting to clients.<br> - Interviews: Conduct research interviews, typically with either consulting firms or their<br> clients, over the telephone or face to face. You’ll be expected to take notes, write them up<br> and process them according to whatever system we have in place for doing so at the time.<br> - Reviewing: Occasionally they might need you to review, sense-check, or edit other people’s<br> reports.</p> <p><br> What they are looking for: <br> - They need a highly numerate and analytical person capable of working with data that can be<br> incomplete or imperfect, and who can tell compelling stories from a body of hard data. </p> <p>- They need someone with an ability to zoom in and zoom out, capable of drilling down into the detail when required while never losing sight of the big picture.</p> <p>- They need someone with good judgement who can find the stories within our research that matter to our customers. You will need to be creative and have three to five years’ experience doing strategy work in the management consulting industry.</p> <p>They want our organisation to consist of people who:<br> ● Are generous with their time in order to help each other (and our customers) succeed<br> ● Take the wheel when needed<br> ● Have a positive attitude<br> ● Can always be objective and honest<br> ● Keep an eye on the future<br> ● Are always professional<br> ● Have a sense of fairness<br> ● Trust each other<br> ● Ask, listen and hear<br> ● Are approachable<br> ● Are curious, and who want to learn<br> ● Are constantly looking for ways to improve things (products and processes)<br> ● Develop products we can be proud of<br> ● Have an intuitive sense of what’s important<br> ● Demonstrate leadership by example<br> ● Laugh a lot</p> <p>Please send your CV to richard@mindbench.co.uk</p>]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[London]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[City of London]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[London]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[Central London]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[EC3A]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[27117.29]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[27117.29]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[annum]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[Management and Consultancy]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[Mindbench]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[2019-08-16]]></expiration-date>
</job>
<job>
	<id><![CDATA[454792718]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[https://adview.online/dispatch/job/feed/management-consultant-16?utm_source=feed-200&utm_medium=postjobfree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[Management Consultant]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[<p>When we ask someone to join The Berkeley Partnership, it’s a big moment, for us and for them.</p> <p>We work with big, high profile clients, shaping and delivering complex and transformational change. Our partners and consultants help these organisations tackle their most critical challenges, often by working as an integral part of their teams. Our focus is always on making change happen, making it successful and making it last. Our people focus on building trusting, long term client relationships and only selling work that clients need and want. We truly believe this is key to our long-term success over the past 27 years, and our repeat business supports this.</p> <p>That’s why we can’t afford to compromise on the quality of people we hire. At Berkeley we nurture talented consultants rather than hire in at the most senior levels, so it is important to us that we hire people at the right point in their career. We look for high achievers with 6-10 years’ consulting experience working in high quality consulting firms. Joiners will have a proven project leadership track record, and the ability to build strong relationships with blue-chip clients.</p> <p>But meeting our requirements is only part of the story. Life at The Berkeley Partnership is very different from larger firms. Our people are encouraged to reach out for help, and to support others in turn. Consultants are highly trusted and have freedom, but partners are close on hand for guidance and support as needed. There’s a strong focus on personal and professional development, with a partner to consultant ratio of 1:3. There are just two levels, Partner and Consultant and if the offer of Partnership comes, you’ll know it means something.</p> <p>As a partnership, we can shape the kind of firm we want to work in. We offer our consultants the chance to develop themselves professionally across a range of sectors and types of consulting work. Our trusting, warm and open culture makes Berkeley both a professional and sociable place to work, with little bureaucracy. You’ll need to be adaptable and open minded about different ways of working and projects or industry sectors that are outside of your comfort zone. Your focus will simply be on doing the best possible consulting work for our clients.</p> <p>We know a career in consulting is often demanding and sometimes all-consuming. But we’re focused on getting to smart outcomes rather than hours on the job. We recognise our people have a constantly changing range of life circumstances. Some of our consultants and partners work part-time – whether parents or not.  Whether you want to start at Berkeley on four days per week, say, or just want to know that Berkeley will support that in the future, you can trust Berkeley to understand your needs. And we make a clear commitment about travel: we won’t send anyone away on long term out-of-town assignments against their wishes.</p> <p>You’ll find our recruitment process thorough and demanding but friendly too.  If you feel you are the right person for us and are ready for a significant career move, do please come and learn more about us click here.</p>]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[London]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[City of London]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[London]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[London]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[EC3A]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[41456.65]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[41456.65]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[annum]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[Management and Consultancy]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[The Berkeley Partnership LLP]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[https://adview.online/img/recruiters/3e/3e244e1_3800544.png]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[2019-08-16]]></expiration-date>
</job>
<job>
	<id><![CDATA[454795937]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[https://adview.online/dispatch/job/feed/senior-analyst-emerging-trends?utm_source=feed-200&utm_medium=postjobfree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[Senior Analyst - Emerging Trends]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[<p>Opportunity to join a growing advisory boutique. The client plans and conducts research at the cutting edge of the professional services industry in order to build their knowledge of the most important emergent trends that are likely to affect it. You’ll support, and sometimes lead, the creation of new intellectual frameworks through which emerging trends can be explained, and will write reports and present your work to the leaders of professional services firms around the world.</p> <p><br> Your responsibilities will include:<br> - Analysis: Make sense of large amounts of data (both qualitative and quantitative) and tease<br> out the stories and trends hidden within it. It is crucial to have a good understanding of the<br> professional services market, including sector-wide trends and what’s going on in specific<br> firms.<br> - Writing: Write reports (in Word or PowerPoint format) that conform to their house style<br> and uphold the integrity of our research using qualitative and/or quantitative data, but<br> which also shimmer with personality and brilliance.<br> - Presentations: Create presentations for clients and answer their questions. You need to be<br> comfortable using PowerPoint to create engaging and informative presentations and<br> delivering these to audiences of all shapes and sizes.<br> - Blogging: Write blogs that entertain and entice our readership.<br> - Custom research: Work on some of the custom research projects they undertake for our<br> clients. This could include designing surveys, interviewing senior clients, or analysing and<br> writing up the results.<br> - Project management : Manage the delivery of projects, from briefing colleagues to<br> producing the analysis and presenting to clients.<br> - Interviews: Conduct research interviews, typically with either consulting firms or their<br> clients, over the telephone or face to face. You’ll be expected to take notes, write them up<br> and process them according to whatever system they have in place for doing so at the time.<br> - Reviewing: Occasionally they might need you to review, sense-check, or edit other people’s<br> reports.</p> <p>Opportunity for development:<br> At the moment, our their Directors are looking after this area of our business so the next step would be to become Product Manager, adding a commercial element to the role. In addition to the creation of content and the delivery, there is a real opportunity to take part in the positioning of their Emerging Trends offering in the market.</p> <p>This is the sort of person they need:</p> <p>They need a highly analytical person capable of identifying trends, creating concepts, and helping their clients think about complex issues in a straightforward way. You should be able to communicate effectively and persuasively. They need someone with an ability to zoom in and zoom out, capable of drilling down into the detail when required while never losing sight of the big picture. They need someone with good judgement--who can find the stories within our research that matter to their customers. </p> <p><br> They want their organisation to consist of people who:<br> ● Are generous with their time in order to help each other (and our customers) succeed<br> ● Take the wheel when needed<br> ● Have a positive attitude<br> ● Can always be objective and honest<br> ● Keep an eye on the future<br> ● Are always professional<br> ● Have a sense of fairness<br> ● Trust each other<br> ● Ask, listen and hear<br> ● Are approachable<br> ● Are curious, and who want to learn<br> ● Are constantly looking for ways to improve things (products and processes)<br> ● Develop products they can be proud of<br> ● Have an intuitive sense of what’s important<br> ● Demonstrate leadership by example<br> ● Laugh a lot</p> <p>Please send your CV to richard@mindbench.co.uk</p>]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[London]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[City of London]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[London]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[Central London]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[EC3A]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[25644.99]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[25644.99]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[annum]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[Management and Consultancy]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[Mindbench]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[2019-08-16]]></expiration-date>
</job>
<job>
	<id><![CDATA[454797236]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[https://adview.online/dispatch/job/feed/sales-director-sd?utm_source=feed-200&utm_medium=postjobfree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[Sales Director SD/811/02]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[<p>Our client are a leading Logistics and Supply Chain business with a national network of operation. Due to continued growth they wish to appoint a Sales Director.</p> <p><strong>The Role</strong></p> <ul><li>You will be responsible for the strategic sales direction, driving profitable sales growth through existing channels and new markets.</li>  <li>To develop and manage relationships with key accounts, liaising with the management team to ensure all relevant matters effecting future sales and service performance are kept under review.</li> </ul><p><strong>The Person</strong></p> <ul><li>You will have a proven track record of building collaborative relationships within the supply chain and logistics sectors. A good commercial awareness and the ability to take a strategic perspective of the business, you will be capable of dealing with highly complex multi-million pound contract negotiations.</li>  <li>You will have a successful background in developing robust pipelines of business. A natural sales leader capable of setting and delivering sales targets which will deliver key new market penetration.</li> </ul>]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[90000.00]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[90000.00]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[annum]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[Logistics and Warehousing]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[Barnaby Stewart Executive Search]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[https://adview.online/img/recruiters/2d/2da6872_3743808.png]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[2019-08-16]]></expiration-date>
</job>
<job>
	<id><![CDATA[454797237]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[https://adview.online/dispatch/job/feed/sales-director-ref-sd?utm_source=feed-200&utm_medium=postjobfree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[Sales Director Ref: SD/811/28]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[<p>Our client is a well-established leading provider of 3PL logistics and Supply Chain solutions to a Blue Chip client base throughout the UK. With ambitious plans for growth, they wish to appoint a Sales Director who will report directly into the Managing Director.</p> <p><strong>The Role</strong></p> <ul><li>Reporting directly into the Managing Director you will have full strategic sales responsibility with the goal of building a robust pipeline of new business, whilst managing key customer relationships.</li> </ul><ul><li>The company has ambitious plans to grow the business and you will play a pivotal part within that.</li> </ul><p><strong>The Person</strong></p> <ul><li>You will have a proven track record of sales delivery within a Supply Chain solutions business. Whilst an understanding of the food sector would be useful, our client would consider any type of Supply Chain sector experience.</li> </ul><ul><li>You will be s results driven individual who enjoys achieving set goals and objectives. A creative individual with the ability to adapt and continually move the business forward.</li> </ul>]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[90000.00]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[90000.00]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[annum]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[Retail and Wholesale]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[Barnaby Stewart Executive Search]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[https://adview.online/img/recruiters/2d/2da6872_3743808.png]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[2019-08-16]]></expiration-date>
</job>
<job>
	<id><![CDATA[454797239]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[https://adview.online/dispatch/job/feed/international-sales-manager-536?utm_source=feed-200&utm_medium=postjobfree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[International Sales Manager]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[<ul><li>Fantastic opportunity to join a growing business area within the wider group</li>  <li>Exciting career potential for an ambitious individual</li> </ul><p><strong>About Our Client</strong></p> <p>Birch Chemicals is part of the Singleton Birch family of companies. For more information on Singleton Birch and our parent company history click here.</p> <p>The company began life as Innovo in 2000, based in Surrey, UK. Innovo was bought by Singleton Birch in 2009, moved to the Melton Ross, North Lincolnshire site and became Birch Chemicals in 2018.</p> <p>Birch Chemicals Limited specialises in the manufacture of microfine calcium oxide desiccants and calcium hydroxide curing agents. These products are used mainly in the rubber, plastics and powder coatings industries.</p> <p>The raw material for the Innovox additive range is lime, which is produced on the same site by Singleton Birch before being micronized and classified. This gives a high level of quality assurance, consistency, control and traceability.</p> <p>Our shared site operation with Singleton Birch reduces lead times from production to packaging, which gives higher quality end products with consistently low moisture levels.</p> <p>Birch Chemicals operates an Investors in People registered training system, which focuses on worker safety and ongoing development of skills. Product quality is paramount and training helps us to achieve this. Everyone understands the importance of our products in your process.</p> <p>Research and Development plays a large part in shaping the future of our product range and we continually strive to improve our existing products and introduce new innovations.</p> <p>Birch Chemicals has excellent logistics connections for ease of global distribution.</p> <p><strong>Job Description</strong></p> <p>The International Sales Manager will be responsible for the continued growth of Birch Chemicals global distribution partners. This is a growing business area, so you will be expected to attend global sales conferences in order to develop new and existing sales opportunities. The nature of the role will require a technically astute individual that is able to work with end user clients as well as distributors in order to change specifications / recipes and increase sales.</p> <p>Additional responsibilities include:</p> <ul><li>Regular global travel to long haul destinations.</li>  <li>Multiple stakeholder client engagement; in-order to develop long standing relationships with multiple sites within the defied global customer base.</li>  <li>Global travel to support key distributor partners at trade shows and exhibitions, in order to offer your technical expertise.</li>  <li>Taking responsibility for sourcing and developing new applications for a product range that has lots of growth potential.</li>  <li>Sourcing and vetting new distributor partners that match the capability and global objectives of the business.</li> </ul><p><strong>The Successful Applicant</strong></p> <p>The successful International Sales Manager will demonstrate competencies in the following areas:</p> <ul><li>A technical aptitude, with the ability to present and communicate technical information to multiple stakeholders.</li>  <li>Knowledge of the rubber / plastic industry would be advantageous, albeit this is not a specific requirement.</li>  <li>Someone with a technical degree, or equivalent work experience would be a distinct advantage.</li>  <li>Previous experience of managing and dealing with international distribution partners is a must.</li>  <li>Able to travel extensively internationally, up to 50% of the time.</li>  <li>A natural new business hunter that is able to build long term client relationships.</li>  <li>Self-motivated individual that is able to work independently, but also with a close knit team.</li>  <li>Strong communication skills, with the ability to build strong internal and external relationships.</li> </ul><p><strong>What's on Offer</strong></p> <p>Competitive package depending upon experience</p> <p><br> Where specific UK qualifications are required we will take into account overseas equivalents. All third party applications will be forwarded to Michael Page.</p> <p><br><b>Ref Code:</b> MPJT14013857Z</p>]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[England]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[28346.12]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[28346.12]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[annum]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing and Production]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[Birch Chemicals]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[2019-08-16]]></expiration-date>
</job>
<job>
	<id><![CDATA[454797240]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[https://adview.online/dispatch/job/feed/director-of-operations-dro?utm_source=feed-200&utm_medium=postjobfree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[Director of Operations DRO/811/03]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[<p>Barnaby Stewart Care have partnered with an established, innovative and expanding social care provider to search for a Director of Operations. Specialising in registered care and supported living services to adults with learning disabilities and autism, they now seek to appoint an experienced healthcare leader to develop and support in its exciting growth plans.</p> <p><strong>The Role</strong></p> <ul><li>You will provide strategic and operational leadership to deliver excellence to service users and continue the development of the business through effective operational management.</li>  <li>You will take overall responsibility for the effective and safe delivery of a portfolio of operational services, including the development of new ones across your defined region.</li>  <li>You will embrace the business culture and work closely with key stakeholders including CQC, local authority and CCG commissioners as well as the central support functions.</li> </ul><p><strong>The Person </strong></p> <ul><li>You will be an experienced manager within learning difficulties and autism who is already operating at director level or will consider a regional manager looking for a step up.</li>  <li>You will have experience of managing and leading teams in a multi-site care environment with the ability to deliver results and operate in a Person-Centred way.</li>  <li>You will have a strong understanding of the latest KLOE’s and have managed services to achieve Good/Outstanding levels of care.</li> </ul>]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[London]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[City of London]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[London]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[London (Central) London (Greater)]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[EC3A]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[100000.00]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[100000.00]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[annum]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[Health, Security and Safety]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[Barnaby Stewart Executive Search]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[https://adview.online/img/recruiters/2d/2da6872_3743808.png]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[2019-08-16]]></expiration-date>
</job>
<job>
	<id><![CDATA[454797241]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[https://adview.online/dispatch/job/feed/business-development-director-bdd?utm_source=feed-200&utm_medium=postjobfree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[Business Development Director BDD/811/13]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[<p>Our client is a leading manufacturer and supplier of engineering systems and components into the Civil and Military Aerospace and Defence sectors. Due to restructuring within a couple of their business units, they now wish to appoint an experienced Sales Director.</p> <p><strong>The Role</strong></p> <ul><li>Reporting directly into the Managing Director you will have full strategic sales responsibility for their UK business and broader International regions.</li>  <li>Leading the sales and bidding team, you will be responsible for achieving annual sales targets, whilst delivering new business growth within both existing and new customers.</li>  <li>You will make a significant strategic contribution to the business, which will include the identification of emerging international markets.</li> </ul><p><strong>The Person</strong></p> <ul><li>Ideally you will be of graduate calibre with a proven track record of sales delivery within the Aerospace or Defence sectors.</li> </ul><ul><li>You will be comfortable operating within a major multinational business, with the ability to develop a detailed commercial understanding of the groups’ clients, both existing and prospective.</li> </ul><ul><li>You will have experience of dealing with multimillion-dollar complex bid cycles, with the ability to exceed the company expectations in terms of revenue growth.</li> </ul>]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[90000.00]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[90000.00]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[annum]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing and Production]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[Barnaby Stewart Executive Search]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[https://adview.online/img/recruiters/2d/2da6872_3743808.png]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[2019-08-16]]></expiration-date>
</job>
<job>
	<id><![CDATA[454797242]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[https://adview.online/dispatch/job/feed/sales-director-sdir?utm_source=feed-200&utm_medium=postjobfree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[Sales Director SDir/811/45]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[<p>Our client is a leading player within the print packaging sector, due to further growth they are looking to strengthen their existing team.</p> <p><strong>The Position </strong></p> <ul><li>Reporting directly to the Managing Director you will be responsible for all key accounts, maximising opportunities and profitability.</li> </ul><ul><li>You will be responsible for negotiating profitable contracts and delivery of sales targets throughout the UK.</li> </ul><ul><li>To motivate and enthuse the sales force and organise appropriate needs based training.</li> </ul><p><strong>The Person</strong></p> <ul><li>A dynamic, energetic individual who can lead from the front.</li> </ul><ul><li>You will have a sales background within the print &amp; packaging sector ideally with experience of the food and drink sectors.</li> </ul><ul><li>Commercially astute you will be keen to join a company in which the delivery of corporate objectives in a team environment is both recognised and highly remunerated.</li> </ul><p>In the first instance please forward relevant CV’s by post or email including your current remuneration package quoting SDir/811/45 to:-</p> <p>Barnaby Stewart Senior Executive Search Ltd</p>]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[75000.00]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[75000.00]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[annum]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing and Production]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[Barnaby Stewart Executive Search]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[https://adview.online/img/recruiters/2d/2da6872_3743808.png]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[2019-08-16]]></expiration-date>
</job>
<job>
	<id><![CDATA[454797753]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[https://adview.online/dispatch/job/feed/servicenow-developer-contract?utm_source=feed-200&utm_medium=postjobfree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[ServiceNow Developer (Contract)]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[<p>  <strong>Client</strong></p>  <p>  My client a leading financial services provider with global operations is currently searching for a ServiceNow Developer to join them on a contract basis in London. You'll be joining a large scale infrastructure change programme, within the ServiceNow Implementation workstream.</p>  <p>  The ideal candidate will have a strong recent ServiceNow development experience, knowledge of financial services and can display longevity on their CV.</p>  <p>  Skills</p>  <ul><li>  Strong ServiceNow Development expertise</li>  <li>  Strong knowledge of programming languages (JavaScriupt, HTML, CSS, .NET etc)</li>  <li>  Knowledge of infrastructure</li>  <li>  Experience within an end to end ServiceNow implementation project</li>  <li>  Knowledge of financial services</li>  </ul>]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[London]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[City of London]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[London]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[London London EC1P]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[EC3A]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[475.00]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[575.00]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[week]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[-N/A-]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[Alexander Ash Ltd]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[2019-08-16]]></expiration-date>
</job>
<job>
	<id><![CDATA[454797754]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[https://adview.online/dispatch/job/feed/lead-dev-netcoreangular-7azuredocker-contract?utm_source=feed-200&utm_medium=postjobfree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[Lead Dev .NETCore/Angular 7/Azure/Docker (Contract)]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[<p>  C#/.NET Core/Angular 7/Azure/Docker/Up To £550 per day</p>  <p>  Our Leading<strong> Logistics Client</strong> based in <strong>Central London</strong> are looking for a <strong>Technical Lead</strong> to kick start one of their <strong>Greenfield projects.</strong></p>  <p>  This role is a hands on role and you will be required to code as well as lead the teams, responsibilities would vary from making technical decisions for the project on a daily basis to peer code reviews etc.</p>  <p>  They are looking for someone who has the ability to work in a enterprise environments where you will be managing internal and external stakeholders. This is a great opportunity to work closely with the wider business and see your applications making real and significant change in the industry.</p>  <p>  Our client is willing to <strong>pay up to £550 per day</strong> for a <strong>initial 12 months contract</strong> with the view to extend.</p>  <p>  <strong>Technical Stack:</strong></p>  <ul><li>  C#</li>  <li>  .NETCore</li>  <li>  Angular 7</li>  <li>  TDD</li>  <li>  CI/CD</li>  <li>  MicroServices architecture</li>  <li>  Azure (Functions, Cosmos DB, Redis, Key Vault, SQL Azure, Data Lake)</li>  <li>  Docker</li>  <li>  Kubernetes</li>  </ul><p>  If this advert has piqued your interest please don't hesitate to contact me as <strong>there are interview slots this week!</strong></p>  <p>  (see below)</p>  <p>  C#/Angular 7/.NET Core/SQL/Azure/Docker/Up To £550 per day</p>]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[London]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[City of London]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[London]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[London London EC1P]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[EC3A]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[500.00]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[550.00]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[week]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[-N/A-]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[Gravitas Recruitment Group]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[2019-08-16]]></expiration-date>
</job>
</jobs>
