<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version='2.0' xmlns:atom='http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom'><channel><atom:link href='https://jobs.danone.com/feeds//?locale=en_US' rel='self' type='application/rss+xml' /><title>DANONE - Custom Search </title><link>https://jobs.danone.com/feeds//?locale=en_US</link><description>Custom RSS Feed for DANONE</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 05:35:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><language>en-us</language><image><url></url><title><![CDATA[DANONE - Custom Search ]]></title><link>https://jobs.danone.com/feeds//?locale=en_US</link></image><ttl>720</ttl>
<item><title><![CDATA[Supply Planning Platform Manager (Paris, 75, FR)]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>.</p>
<p align="center"> </p>

<p align="center"><strong>Looking to have a transversal role with a real impact on the deployment of our strategy?</strong></p>

<p align="center"><strong>Willing to work in a challenging environment at the heart of the business? </strong></p>

<p align="center"><strong>Enjoying transversal and exposed role with multiple contacts?</strong></p>

<p align="center"> </p>

<p align="center"><span style="font-size: 14px;"><strong>Become our Europe Supply Planning Manager </strong></span></p>

<p align="center"><span style="font-size: 14px;"><strong>in Danone Dairy Division!</strong></span></p>

<p> </p>

<p align="center"> </p>

<p align="center">Job located in Paris area :Saint-Ouen (93) and from May 2020 in Rueil-Malmaison (92).</p>

<p> </p>

<p> </p>

<p><strong>Objectives</strong></p>

<p> </p>

<p>Reporting to Europe Supply Planning Director, you contribute to Operations performance through capacity management in Europe for your platform “Set dairy products & Desserts” (Danone and Danette brands) in order to support our Dairy strategy. Representing 450KT/year and accounting for 700M€ of net sales.</p>

<p>The objective is to secure the right strategy in terms of capacity over different factories in Europe and bring innovative solutions to the business teams on everyday challenges.</p>

<p> </p>

<p> </p>

<p><strong>Missions</strong></p>

<p> </p>

<p>With the help of your teams based in France (1p) and in close collaboration with the EU supply Planning team (10p) you will:</p>

<p> </p>

<p><strong>Manage European factories Capacity for your platform: </strong></p>

<ul>
	<li>Run strategical meetings with European plant directors (France, Spain, Germany) and Projects teams to assess capabilities</li>
	<li>Define products’ future (volumes definition and distribution) in relation with these capabilities and topline action plans</li>
	<li>Bring plants to change their technologies or reallocate volumes on other plants in case of specific products launches</li>
	<li>Participate to long term development plan of the platform</li>
</ul>

<p style="margin-left: 18pt;"> </p>

<p><strong>Develop fresh solutions to the supply planning teams</strong></p>

<ul>
	<li>Improve and build new tools for the supply planning team to use on day-2-day</li>
	<li>Train and share best practices among the supply planning community to leverage the performance and retention of the team</li>
</ul>

<p> </p>

<p><strong>Work in close coordination with operation teams</strong></p>

<ul>
	<li>To deliver the next breakthrough innovation for Danone</li>
	<li>To find more efficient ways of working</li>
</ul>

<p><strong>Develop your team </strong>within FR and in Europe to define career path for years to come</p>

<p align="center"> </p>

<p> </p>

<p>Trips : 25% of local and international travels.</p>

<p> </p>

<p><strong>We offer:</strong></p>

<ul>
	<li>A global vision on a European and complex scope</li>
	<li>A key role in the development of a strategic business and with impact on our Operations</li>
	<li>A high level of exposure and wide range of connections  (Marketing,  R&D, Sourcing & Projects, Plants Directors, Supply chain, Demand Planning, Activity management …)</li>
</ul>

<ul>
	<li>Diversified career opportunities within a big international company
	<p align="center"> </p>

	<p><strong>Your profile :</strong></p>
	</li>
</ul>

<ul>
	<li>10 years mini of experience with at least 5 yrs in Supply Chain ideally in demand, supply or production planning.</li>
	<li>Agility, strong relationship skills and a good ability to influence and challenge stakeholders</li>
	<li>Fluent in English & French and ideally exposition to an international environment</li>
	<li>“Hands on” and synthetic approach coupled with strategic thinking.  </li>
	<li>Comfortable dealing with big sets of data and complex problems solving.</li>
</ul>

<p> </p>

<p><strong>Danone, "One Planet, One Health"... what about you?</strong></p>

<p>Danone is a company committed to inspiring mission: "Bringing health through food to as many". This ambition takes the commitments on a daily basis around social and environmental issues with local communities, farmers, our partners...</p>

<p>Danone is a world leader on 4 professions: dairy products and plant, infant nutrition, water, and medical nutrition. With present products on + 130 markets, Danone has generated 22 billion euros of sales in 2016. Our portfolio includes brands renowned internationally (Evian, Activia, Actimel, Alpro, Danette, Aptamil...).</p>

<p>Come grow with passionate and enthusiastic teams! You'll find an environment that the proximity and encourages taking the initiative. Come and contribute to a rich project sense.</p>

<p> </p>

<p align="center"><strong>Come lead with us the "Food Revolution"!</strong></p>
<p>.</p>
]]></description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 0:00:00 GMT</pubDate><link>https://jobs.danone.com/job/Paris-Supply-Planning-Platform-Manager-75/504845801/?feedId=null&amp;utm_source=J2WRSS&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=J2W_RSS</link><guid>https://jobs.danone.com/job/Paris-Supply-Planning-Platform-Manager-75/504845801/?feedId=null&amp;utm_source=J2WRSS&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=J2W_RSS</guid></item>
<item><title><![CDATA[Supply Planning Platform Manager (Paris, 75, FR)]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>.</p>
<p align="center"><strong><em>Looking to have a transversal role with a real impact on the deployment of our strategy ?</em></strong></p>

<p align="center"><strong><em>Willing to work in a challenging environment at the heart of the business ? </em></strong></p>

<p align="center"><strong><em>Enjoying transversal and exposed role with multiple contacts ?</em></strong></p>

<p align="center"> </p>

<p align="center"><span style="font-size: 16px;"><strong>Become our Europe Supply Planning Manager </strong></span></p>

<p align="center"><span style="font-size: 16px;"><strong>in Danone Dairy Division !</strong></span></p>

<p> </p>

<p><strong>Objectives</strong></p>

<p> </p>

<p>Reporting to Europe Supply Planning Director, you contribute to Operations performance through capacity management in Europe for your platform “Set dairy products & Desserts” (Danone and Danette brands) in order to support our Dairy strategy. Representing 200KT/year and accounting for 700M€ of net sales.</p>

<p>The objective is to ensure the right level of service in delivery to customers & inventory for France & UK (volumes, timing, costs) in a context of complex distribution network.  At the same time you will also connect to Set & Desserts platform teams cross countries and factories.</p>

<p> </p>

<p> </p>

<p><strong>Missions</strong></p>

<p> </p>

<p>With the help of your teams based in France (8p) and UK (2p), you will :</p>

<p> </p>

<p><strong>Work in close coordination with topline teams</strong> (sales & marketing)</p>

<ul>
	<li>Develop demand knowledge on your Brands and on the European countries selling these 2 brands (France, Spain, UK, Germany, Austria…) : Activation periods, promotion level, new products launches…</li>
	<li>Follow up Business evolution and main challenges (countries and platform levels) and bring your support to Topline steering committees on brands</li>
</ul>

<p><strong>Manage European factories Capacity for your platform : </strong></p>

<ul>
	<li>Run strategical meetings with European plant directors (France, Spain, Germany)and Projects teams to assess capabilities</li>
	<li>Define products’ future (volumes definition and distribution) in relation with these capabilities and topline action plans</li>
	<li>Bring plants to change their technologies or reallocate volumes on other plants in case of specific products launches</li>
	<li>Participate to long term development plan of the platform</li>
</ul>

<p><strong>Manage Crisis coordination </strong>(eg : shortage) with all stakeholders to find and implement action plans</p>

<p><strong>Contribute to projects on related planning topics </strong>(productivity, Engineering, quality…)and coordinate Supply for sourcing changes</p>

<p><strong>Support your teams</strong> in the change and implementation of our new European organization and WOW </p>

<p align="center"> </p>

<p align="center">Job located in Paris area (Saint-Ouen). 15% of local and international travels.</p>

<p> </p>

<p><strong>We offer :</strong></p>

<ul>
	<li>A global vision on a European and complex scope</li>
	<li>A key role in the development of a strategic business and with impact on our Operations</li>
	<li>A high level of exposure and wide range of connections  (Marketing,  R&D, Sourcing & Projects, Plants Directors, Supply chain, Demand Planning, Activity management …)</li>
</ul>

<ul>
	<li>Diversified career opportunities within a big international company
	<p align="center"> </p>

	<p align="center"><strong>You have mini 10 years of experience with at least 5 yrs in Supply Chain<br />
	ideally in demand, supply or production planning. </strong></p>

	<p align="center"><strong>You demonstrate agility, strong relationship skills and<br />
	a good ability to influence and challenge stakeholders </strong></p>

	<p align="center"><strong>You have a “hands on” and synthetic approach coupled with strategic thinking.<br />
	You are comfortable dealing with big sets of data and complex problems solving.</strong></p>

	<p align="center"><strong>You are fluent in English & French and ideally have been exposed to an international environment</strong></p>
	</li>
</ul>

<p> </p>

<p> </p>

<p><strong>Learn more about Danone...</strong></p>

<p>Danone is a global food company holding top positions in healthy food through its four businesses: Fresh Dairy Products, Early Life Nutrition, Waters, and Medical Nutrition. Its mission, bringing health through food to as many people as possible, embodies commitment to human progress and business success. It gives meaning to the work of our 100,000 Danoners worldwide on an everyday basis.</p>

<p>For passionate people looking for autonomy and exciting career opportunities, Danone truly has something special inside.</p>

<p> </p>

<p>For more information about Danone, its people and its business, please visit danone.com We have something special inside, do you?</p>
<p>.</p>
]]></description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 0:00:00 GMT</pubDate><link>https://jobs.danone.com/job/Paris-Supply-Planning-Platform-Manager-75/504845901/?feedId=null&amp;utm_source=J2WRSS&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=J2W_RSS</link><guid>https://jobs.danone.com/job/Paris-Supply-Planning-Platform-Manager-75/504845901/?feedId=null&amp;utm_source=J2WRSS&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=J2W_RSS</guid></item>
<item><title><![CDATA[Europe Activity Manager (Paris, 75, FR)]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>.</p>
<p align="center"><strong><em>Looking to have a transversal role with a real impact on the deployment of our strategy ?</em></strong></p>

<p align="center"><strong><em>Willing to work in a challenging environment at the heart of the business ? </em></strong></p>

<p align="center"><strong><em>Enjoying transversal and exposed role with multiple contacts ?</em></strong></p>

<p align="center"> </p>

<p align="center"><span style="font-size:14.0px"><strong>Become our European Activity Manager </strong></span></p>

<p align="center"><span style="font-size:14.0px"><strong>in Danone for our Dairy Business!</strong></span></p>

<p> </p>

<p align="center">Job located in Paris area : Saint-Ouen (93) and then in Rueil-Malmaison (92) from May 2020.</p>

<p> </p>

<p> </p>

<p><strong>Objectives</strong></p>

<p> </p>

<p>Within our Essential Plant Based and Dairy products, and reporting to our Europe Supply Chain Director, you contribute to Dairy Operations performance through coordinating major European projects (Visual Identity System, global Innovations) to ensure guaranteed leadtime and cost.</p>

<p> </p>

<p>Working with Central Marketing team and 5 CBUs (Category Business Units: France, UBN (UK&I /Benelux), CEN (Central Europe and Nordics), AIG (Austria, Italy, Germany and Greece), Iberia (Spain/Portugal) coordinating over 4000 pack changes a year with 23 factories (Danone and 3PMs), central and local premedia agencies (PMA) and Printers.</p>

<p> </p>

<p> </p>

<p> </p>

<p><strong>Missions</strong></p>

<p> </p>

<p>With the help of your team based in France (1p), you will:</p>

<ul>
	<li><strong>Lead the Operational coordination for the major global EU projects of packs development (visual identity, Inno/Reno/Promo) from “GO Launch” phase till “1st Production”</strong></li>
</ul>

<ul>
	<li>Work  in collaboration with project leader (Marketing), Purchasing (C&P), Sourcing and Project (OPP) and production sites…</li>
	<li>Build the processes to detect, evaluate and alert about the risks and deviations vs project timelines</li>
	<li>Develop and optimize methods & processes at EU level to improve project execution from a cross-functional perspective
	<p> </p>
	</li>
</ul>

<ul>
	<li><strong>Accountable for Graphic Chain process and project coordination at EU level. </strong>

	<ul>
		<li>Create the graphic chain forecast process & mitigations plans.</li>
		<li>Follow steps in the Graphic chain process of all the departments involved, providing the necessary support to the users in order to achieve the target in time</li>
		<li>Work in close collaboration with your counterparts in the other divisions (graphic chain process improvement and tool merge, benchmark…)</li>
		<li>Graphic chain tool management and development (new versions, internal training...)
		<p> </p>
		</li>
	</ul>
	</li>
</ul>

<ul>
	<li><strong>Manage and develop global PMAs (Pre-media agencies)</strong></li>
</ul>

<ul>
	<li>Operation SPOC for global PMAs. Accountable for PMA supplier performance and capacity management together with Procurement (C&P) at EU level.</li>
</ul>

<p> </p>

<ul>
	<li><strong>Material planning relationship with the CBUs/DanTrade (C&P)</strong>

	<ul>
		<li>Contribute to improve supplier performance in collaboration with Cycles & Procurement and animate procurement process through R&P forecast accuracy improvement to improve supplier service level, DIO Raws&Packs and Obsoletes.
		<p> </p>
		</li>
	</ul>
	</li>
</ul>

<ul>
	<li><strong>Lead and Animate EU Activity management (producing) network with CBU representatives</strong>

	<ul>
		<li>Align on yearly priorities to improve tool and processes with local Activity management team in the clusters</li>
		<li>Share best practices, innovations (e.g. digital printing) accross CBUs</li>
		<li>Develop training material on graphic chain and printers and share with CBUs
		<p align="center"> </p>

		<p><strong>Trips</strong> : 15% of local and international travels.</p>

		<p> </p>

		<p><strong>We offer:</strong></p>
		</li>
	</ul>
	</li>
</ul>

<ul>
	<li>A global vision on a European complex scope</li>
	<li>A key role in contributing to our Business Growth</li>
	<li>A high level of exposure and wide range of connections both Inside (Marketing, Sourcing & Projects, Factories, Procurement and 5 CBUs …) and Outside (PMAs, Printers, 3PMs)</li>
</ul>

<ul>
	<li>Diversified career opportunities within a big international company
	<p align="center"> </p>

	<p><strong>Your profile : </strong></p>
	</li>
</ul>

<ul>
	<li>Master degree level with 10 years mini of experience with at least 3y in Operations (ideally in activity management, planning or customer collaboration), Projects, R&I portfolio management or in Marketing/Trade Marketing</li>
	<li>Strong project management skills</li>
	<li>Agility, strong relationship skills and ability to influence and challenge stakeholders</li>
	<li>A “hands on” approach coupled with strategic thinking and complex problems solving approach</li>
	<li>Fluent in English</li>
</ul>

<p> </p>

<p> </p>

<p><strong>Danone, "One Planet, One Health"... what about you?</strong></p>

<p>Danone is a company committed to inspiring mission: "Bringing health through food to as many". This ambition takes the commitments on a daily basis around social and environmental issues with local communities, farmers, our partners...</p>

<p>Danone is a world leader on 4 professions: dairy products and plant, infant nutrition, water, and medical nutrition. With present products on + 130 markets, Danone has generated 22 billion euros of sales in 2016. Our portfolio includes brands renowned internationally (Evian, Activia, Actimel, Alpro, Danette, Aptamil...).</p>

<p>Come grow with passionate and enthusiastic teams! You'll find an environment that the proximity and encourages taking the initiative. Come and contribute to a rich project sense.</p>

<p> </p>

<p align="center"><strong>Come lead with us the "Food Revolution"!</strong></p>
<p>.</p>
]]></description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 0:00:00 GMT</pubDate><link>https://jobs.danone.com/job/Paris-Europe-Activity-Manager-75/504848501/?feedId=null&amp;utm_source=J2WRSS&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=J2W_RSS</link><guid>https://jobs.danone.com/job/Paris-Europe-Activity-Manager-75/504848501/?feedId=null&amp;utm_source=J2WRSS&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=J2W_RSS</guid></item>
<item><title><![CDATA[Europe Activity Manager (Paris, 75, FR)]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>.</p>
<p align="center"><strong><em>Looking to have a transversal role with a real impact on the deployment of our strategy ?</em></strong></p>

<p align="center"><strong><em>Willing to work in a challenging environment at the heart of the business ? </em></strong></p>

<p align="center"><strong><em>Enjoying transversal and exposed role with multiple contacts ?</em></strong></p>

<p align="center"> </p>

<p align="center"><span style="font-size: 14px;"><strong>Become our European Activity Manager </strong></span></p>

<p align="center"><span style="font-size: 14px;"><strong>in Danone for our Dairy Business!</strong></span></p>

<p> </p>

<p align="center">Job located in Paris area : Saint-Ouen (93) and then in Rueil-Malmaison (92) from May 2020.</p>

<p> </p>

<p> </p>

<p><strong>Objectives</strong></p>

<p> </p>

<p>Within our Essential Plant Based and Dairy products, and reporting to our Europe Supply Chain Director, you contribute to Dairy Operations performance through coordinating major European projects (Visual Identity System, global Innovations) to ensure guaranteed leadtime and cost.</p>

<p> </p>

<p>Working with Central Marketing team and 5 CBUs (Category Business Units: France, UBN (UK&I /Benelux), CEN (Central Europe and Nordics), AIG (Austria, Italy, Germany and Greece), Iberia (Spain/Portugal) coordinating over 4000 pack changes a year with 23 factories (Danone and 3PMs), central and local premedia agencies (PMA) and Printers.</p>

<p> </p>

<p> </p>

<p> </p>

<p><strong>Missions</strong></p>

<p> </p>

<p>With the help of your team based in France (1p), you will:</p>

<ul>
	<li><strong>Lead the Operational coordination for the major global EU projects of packs development (visual identity, Inno/Reno/Promo) from “GO Launch” phase till “1<sup>st</sup> Production”</strong></li>
</ul>

<ul>
	<li>Work  in collaboration with project leader (Marketing), Purchasing (C&P), Sourcing and Project (OPP) and production sites…</li>
	<li>Build the processes to detect, evaluate and alert about the risks and deviations vs project timelines</li>
	<li>Develop and optimize methods & processes at EU level to improve project execution from a cross-functional perspective
	<p> </p>
	</li>
</ul>

<ul>
	<li><strong>Accountable for Graphic Chain process and project coordination at EU level. </strong>

	<ul>
		<li>Create the graphic chain forecast process & mitigations plans.</li>
		<li>Follow steps in the Graphic chain process of all the departments involved, providing the necessary support to the users in order to achieve the target in time</li>
		<li>Work in close collaboration with your counterparts in the other divisions (graphic chain process improvement and tool merge, benchmark…)</li>
		<li>Graphic chain tool management and development (new versions, internal training...)
		<p> </p>
		</li>
	</ul>
	</li>
</ul>

<ul>
	<li><strong>Manage and develop global PMAs (Pre-media agencies)</strong></li>
</ul>

<ul>
	<li>Operation SPOC for global PMAs. Accountable for PMA supplier performance and capacity management together with Procurement (C&P) at EU level.</li>
</ul>

<p> </p>

<ul>
	<li><strong>Material planning relationship with the CBUs/DanTrade (C&P)</strong>

	<ul>
		<li>Contribute to improve supplier performance in collaboration with Cycles & Procurement and animate procurement process through R&P forecast accuracy improvement to improve supplier service level, DIO Raws&Packs and Obsoletes.
		<p> </p>
		</li>
	</ul>
	</li>
</ul>

<ul>
	<li><strong>Lead and Animate EU Activity management (producing) network with CBU representatives</strong>

	<ul>
		<li>Align on yearly priorities to improve tool and processes with local Activity management team in the clusters</li>
		<li>Share best practices, innovations (e.g. digital printing) accross CBUs</li>
		<li>Develop training material on graphic chain and printers and share with CBUs
		<p align="center"> </p>

		<p><strong>Trips</strong> : 15% of local and international travels.</p>

		<p> </p>

		<p><strong>We offer:</strong></p>
		</li>
	</ul>
	</li>
</ul>

<ul>
	<li>A global vision on a European complex scope</li>
	<li>A key role in contributing to our Business Growth</li>
	<li>A high level of exposure and wide range of connections both Inside (Marketing, Sourcing & Projects, Factories, Procurement and 5 CBUs …) and Outside (PMAs, Printers, 3PMs)</li>
</ul>

<ul>
	<li>Diversified career opportunities within a big international company
	<p align="center"> </p>

	<p><strong>Your profile : </strong></p>
	</li>
</ul>

<ul>
	<li>Master degree level with 10 years mini of experience with at least 3y in Operations (ideally in activity management, planning or customer collaboration), Projects, R&I portfolio management or in Marketing/Trade Marketing</li>
	<li>Strong project management skills</li>
	<li>Agility, strong relationship skills and ability to influence and challenge stakeholders</li>
	<li>A “hands on” approach coupled with strategic thinking and complex problems solving approach</li>
	<li>Fluent in English</li>
</ul>

<p> </p>

<p> </p>

<p><strong>Danone, "One Planet, One Health"... what about you?</strong></p>

<p>Danone is a company committed to inspiring mission: "Bringing health through food to as many". This ambition takes the commitments on a daily basis around social and environmental issues with local communities, farmers, our partners...</p>

<p>Danone is a world leader on 4 professions: dairy products and plant, infant nutrition, water, and medical nutrition. With present products on + 130 markets, Danone has generated 22 billion euros of sales in 2016. Our portfolio includes brands renowned internationally (Evian, Activia, Actimel, Alpro, Danette, Aptamil...).</p>

<p>Come grow with passionate and enthusiastic teams! You'll find an environment that the proximity and encourages taking the initiative. Come and contribute to a rich project sense.</p>

<p> </p>

<p align="center"><strong>Come lead with us the "Food Revolution"!</strong></p>
<p>.</p>
]]></description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 0:00:00 GMT</pubDate><link>https://jobs.danone.com/job/Paris-Europe-Activity-Manager-75/504848601/?feedId=null&amp;utm_source=J2WRSS&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=J2W_RSS</link><guid>https://jobs.danone.com/job/Paris-Europe-Activity-Manager-75/504848601/?feedId=null&amp;utm_source=J2WRSS&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=J2W_RSS</guid></item>
</channel></rss>