<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><source><jobs>

<job>
<location>Dearborn, MI, United States</location><title>Java Developer</title><city>Dearborn</city><state>MI</state><zip>48120</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Full Time</job_type><posted_at>2020-10-04</posted_at><job_reference>6874_34020ecd1e29e8f1c93c369e00310738</job_reference><company>ProIT Inc.</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/5hfny5b?cs=e3e&amp;jg=1jcf&amp;bid=TMQKNCFaov4fFLqS_v4dTg==</url>
<body>Job Description   Java Developer Dearborn MI Fulltime Only We are looking for a Java Developer with experience on Hadoop and kafka Java, Springboot Cloud experience ndash PCF preferred (could be any other cloud as well) Experience with connecting to Hadoop Experience with Kafka Other - GIT, CICD, TDD. 5+ years      With Regards,   Shrutika Saini Account Manager PRO IT, INC. Phone 636-529-2137    mailto207Cnbsp  www.proit-inc.com  httpsnam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com?urlhttp3A2F2Fwww.proit-inc.com2Fampdata027C017Cvsingh40netwoven.com7Ce1b03c39ecf54d69dc6808d816a9b7177C85f66ea08fe448b9a1a78633937d534a7C17C07C637284265484808473ampsdatanVt0bBbDVoZYxS1lsPZAZvUd2BLPplqL0O1CPN56cdg03Dampreserved0</body>
<cpc>0.21</cpc><CompanyLogo>https://assets.dice.com/external/images/empLogos/c3445c93ba6c666beffeabcc17e4bf1f.png</CompanyLogo>
<HTMLDescription>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;&lt;html&gt;&lt;head&gt;&lt;/head&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Job Description&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Java Developer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dearborn MI&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fulltime Only&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a Java Developer with experience on Hadoop and kafka&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Java, Springboot&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cloud experience &amp;ndash; PCF preferred (could be any other cloud as well)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with connecting to Hadoop&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with Kafka&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Other - GIT, CI/CD, TDD.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;5+ years&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;With Regards,&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Shrutika Saini&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Account Manager&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;PRO IT, INC.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;Phone:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;/ 636-529-2137&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:%20%7C&amp;nbsp;&quot;&gt; |&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.proit-inc.com%2F&amp;amp;data=02%7C01%7Cvsingh%40netwoven.com%7Ce1b03c39ecf54d69dc6808d816a9b717%7C85f66ea08fe448b9a1a78633937d534a%7C1%7C0%7C637284265484808473&amp;amp;sdata=nVt0bBbDVoZYxS1lsPZAZvUd%2BLPplqL0O1CPN56cdg0%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0&quot;&gt;www.proit-inc.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt; - provided by Dice</HTMLDescription></job>

<job><location>Austin, TX, United States</location><title>IT Infrastructure Project Manager</title><city>Austin</city><state>TX</state><zip>73301</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Full Time</job_type><posted_at>2020-10-06</posted_at><job_reference>6874_eac73745b09d45d7a6ab912d139e4c7c</job_reference><company>Apex Systems</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/4vo3s0n?cs=e3e&amp;jg=1jyp&amp;bid=qMBw6_6-q3t3yU513qcCDg==</url>
<body>Job Type Contract-to-h? ire  Contract Length 9 Mont? hs   Location Remote2? 6nbsp  ?3CpOnly if below qualifications are met, please send2? 0Word resume to  ?   The Projectnbsp3? BManager will have an exciting new role helping to transform2? 0the IT organization! This role will ensure projects meet ob? jectives on time and on budget by increasing adoption. The2? 0primary responsibility will be creating and implementing change2? 0management strategies and plans that maximize adoption and mini? mize resistance. The Project Manager will work to drive? adoption, higher ultimate utilization and greater proficiency2? 0of the changes that impact team members in the organization2? 0to increase benefit realization, value creation, ROI and th? e achievement of desired outcomes.  While2? 0the Project Manager does not have supervisory responsibili? ty, this person will need to navigate the organization to ? succeed and be a very independent contributor. The position ? may also provide direct support and coaching to leaders as t? hey help their direct reports through the change initiative.3? Cp   Respons? ibilities  Manage en? d-to-end project lifecycle  Apply a struct? ured methodology to execute project  organizational change ma? nagement activities  Identify and manage stake? holders  Assess the project  change impac? t  Conduct stakeholder interviews and complete? change management assessments  Create an ov? erall project  change management strategy  ?  Consult and coach project teams   Eva? luate and ensure user readiness  Define and?20measure success metrics and monitor change progress?0A  Qualifications ?0D  Minimum ten years of hands on experien? ce in IT project management  Expereince? with system projects (Windows, Azure, Data Center)?  Cisco network experience  Unified Communications (UC) Must have experience with Waterfal methodology ?  Experience managing complex infrastructure-based projects  Strong oral and written communication skills,? including presentation skills (MS Visio, MS PowerPoint, M? S Word, MS Excel)  Ability to work ind? ependently and manage multiple assignments  0? D  Preferred ?09 PMP, or other relevant certification(s) is a plus?3Cli  Strong problem-solving skills with t? he ability to exercise mature judgement  Dem? onstrated ability to manage ambiguity and apply problem-solving?20skills  Demonstrated ability to employ resea? rch and analytical thinking  Demonstrated capa? bilities in teamwork and leadership  ?   0? A  ?3Cp   Apex Systems is an equal ? opportunity employer. We do not discriminate or allow discrimi? nation on the basis of race, color, religion, creed, s? ex (including pregnancy, childbirth, breastfeeding, or relat? ed medical conditions), age, sexual orientation, gender id? entity, national origin, ancestry, citizenship, genetic info? rmation, registered domestic partner status, marital status,2? 0disability, status as a crime victim, protected veteran sta? tus, political affiliation, union membership, or any other2? 0characteristic protected by law. Apex will consider qualified2? 0applicants with criminal histories in a manner consistent with?20the requirements of applicable law. If you have visited ou? r website in search of information on employment opportunities2? 0or to apply for a position, and you require an accommodat? ion in using our website for a search or application, plea? se contact our Employee Services Department at employeeservicesapexsyste? msinc.com or</body><cpc>0.19</cpc><CompanyLogo>https://assets.dice.com/external/images/empLogos/a9df3b9fc08560e06178c0e33acb9086.png</CompanyLogo>
<HTMLDescription>&lt;b&gt;Job Type: Contract-to-h? ire&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Contract Length: 9 Mont? hs &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Location: Remote%2? 6nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;%?3Cp&gt;&lt;b&gt;Only if below qualifications are met, please send%2? 0Word resume to &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Project&amp;nbsp%3? BManager will have an exciting new role helping to transform%2? 0the IT organization! This role will ensure projects meet ob? jectives on time and on budget by increasing adoption. The%2? 0primary responsibility will be creating and implementing change%2? 0management strategies and plans that maximize adoption and mini? mize resistance. The Project Manager will work to drive? adoption, higher ultimate utilization and greater proficiency%2? 0of the changes that impact team members in the organization%2? 0to increase benefit realization, value creation, ROI and th? e achievement of desired outcomes.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;While%2? 0the Project Manager does not have supervisory responsibili? ty, this person will need to navigate the organization to ? succeed and be a very independent contributor. The position ? may also provide direct support and coaching to leaders as t? hey help their direct reports through the change initiative.%3? C/p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Respons? ibilities:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Manage en? d-to-end project lifecycle&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Apply a struct? ured methodology to execute project \ organizational change ma? nagement activities&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Identify and manage stake? holders&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Assess the project \ change impac? t&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Conduct stakeholder interviews and complete? change management assessments&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Create an ov? erall project \ change management strategy&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;? &lt;li&gt;Consult and coach project teams&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Eva? luate and ensure user readiness&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Define and%?20measure success metrics and monitor change progress&lt;/li&gt;%?0A&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Qualifications&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; %?0D &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Minimum ten years of hands on experien? ce in IT project management&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Expereince? with system projects (Windows, Azure, Data Center)? &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Cisco network experience &lt;li&gt;Unified Communications (UC)&lt;/li&gt; Must have experience with Waterfal methodology&lt;/li&gt; ? &lt;li&gt;Experience managing complex infrastructure-based projects &lt;li&gt;Strong oral and written communication skills,? including presentation skills (MS Visio, MS PowerPoint, M? S Word, MS Excel)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Ability to work ind? ependently and manage multiple assignments&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;%0? D &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Preferred&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;ul&gt; %?09&lt;li&gt;PMP, or other relevant certification(s) is a plus%?3C/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Strong problem-solving skills with t? he ability to exercise mature judgement&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Dem? onstrated ability to manage ambiguity and apply problem-solving%?20skills&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to employ resea? rch and analytical thinking&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Demonstrated capa? bilities in teamwork and leadership&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; ? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;%0? A&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;%?3Cp&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Apex Systems is an equal ? opportunity employer. We do not discriminate or allow discrimi? nation on the basis of race, color, religion, creed, s? ex (including pregnancy, childbirth, breastfeeding, or relat? ed medical conditions), age, sexual orientation, gender id? entity, national origin, ancestry, citizenship, genetic info? rmation, registered domestic partner status, marital status,%2? 0disability, status as a crime victim, protected veteran sta? tus, political affiliation, union membership, or any other%2? 0characteristic protected by law. Apex will consider qualified%2? 0applicants with criminal histories in a manner consistent with%?20the requirements of applicable law. If you have visited ou? r website in search of information on employment opportunities%2? 0or to apply for a position, and you require an accommodat? ion in using our website for a search or application, plea? se contact our Employee Services Department at employeeservices@apexsyste? msinc.com or - provided by Dice</HTMLDescription>
</job>


<job><location>Woodlawn, MD, United States</location><title>MongoDB Elasticache Python Database Developer / Architect</title><city>Woodlawn</city><state>MD</state><zip>21207</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Full Time</job_type><posted_at>2020-10-04</posted_at><job_reference>6874_4f32d2b9f36669d103ad6b733466c79e</job_reference><company>INADEV</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/4exthc9?cs=e3e&amp;jg=1jd1&amp;bid=qMBw6_6-q3t3yU513qcCDg==</url><body>INADEV is a recognized SBA 8(a) certified SDB based in McLean, VA since 2011. We provide high quality agile digital services, cloud based solutions, and full end to end operational services to multiple Federal agencies such as Department of Homeland Security (IS), Social Security Administration, US Census Bureau, Food and Drug Administration, and large commercial entities such as Echostar.  or sEAD status with the ability to obtain a Public Trust security clearance is required.  Must be available for in-person interview and work onsite in Woodlawn MD.  Key Required Skills      Mongo DB open source, Elasticache, NoSQL   Position Description     Designing, Building, and automating the MongoDB Architecture for open source MongoDB. The ideal candidate has worked with modern open source NewSQL and NoSQL platforms, cloud deployment models and test-driven development in a fast-paced agile environment. Experience on automating AWS ElastiCache provisioning, administration and maintenance. Experience in using Python to automate infrastructure tasks Designing and develop logical physical database designs from customer requirements. Provide advice and support to development resources. Provide guidance in the creation and modification of standards and procedures. Supporting the standing standards, policies and procedures of the customer team. Provide mentorship to group members and will be expected to help develop and support mid and junior level staff. After hours on-call support and will be required to apply production packages during non-peak hours.                Required Skills Designing, Building, and automating the MongoDB Architecture for open source MongoDB. Experience in using Python to automate infrastructure tasks Experience on automating ElastiCache provisioning, administration and maintenance Expert MongoDB architectural knowledge Considered a leader in the field Experience working with relational data modeling using tools like Erwin Experience working with AWS database services including RDS, EC2, S3, Infrastructure and configuration automation.    Desired Skills Ansible Automation experience Jenkins GitBitbucket ConfluenceJIRA Working in Agile and DEVOPS environment.    Education       Bachelors degree from an accredited college in a related discipline or equivalent work years  We offer a full benefits package. This includes but is not limited to We will contribute 400 to 800 towards your healthcare plan. We have multiple plans available to fit your life for Medical, Vision, Dental  Prescription.  Employer paid Life Insurance  LongShort Disability Insurance  3 weeks PTO, roll over up to 200 hours 8 paid holidays and 2 paid floating holidays 401k, vested immediately, we match up to 3 Excellent work life balance  A commitment to creating a fulfilling work environment  No 3rd party Recruitersagencies please.    Physical Demands Reasonable accommodations may be made to enable individuals with disabilities to perform the essential functions    INADEV Corporation does not discriminate against qualified individuals based on their status as protected veterans or individuals with disabilities and prohibits discrimination against all individuals based on their race, color, religion, sex, sexual orientationgender identity, or national origin.</body><cpc>0.19</cpc><CompanyLogo>https://assets.dice.com/external/images/empLogos/0bad5a16001ee8e628afb40c7740ba50.png</CompanyLogo><HTMLDescription>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;&lt;html&gt;&lt;head&gt;&lt;/head&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;p&gt;INADEV is a recognized SBA 8(a) certified SDB based in McLean, VA since 2011. We provide high quality agile digital services, cloud based solutions, and full end to end operational services to multiple Federal agencies such as Department of Homeland Security (====IS), Social Security Administration, US Census Bureau, Food and Drug Administration, and large commercial entities such as Echostar.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;====&amp;nbsp;or&amp;nbsp;====s/EAD status with the ability to obtain a Public Trust security clearance is required.&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Must be available for in-person interview and work onsite in Woodlawn MD.&lt;/u&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Key Required Skills:&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mongo DB open source, Elasticache, NoSQL&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Position Description:&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Designing, Building, and automating the MongoDB Architecture for open source MongoDB.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The ideal candidate has worked with modern open source NewSQL and NoSQL platforms, cloud deployment models and test-driven development in a fast-paced agile environment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience on automating AWS ElastiCache provisioning, administration and maintenance.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience in using Python to automate infrastructure tasks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Designing and develop logical physical database designs from customer requirements.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Provide advice and support to development resources.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Provide guidance in the creation and modification of standards and procedures. Supporting the standing standards, policies and procedures of the customer team.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Provide mentorship to group members and will be expected to help develop and support mid and junior level staff.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;After hours on-call support and will be required to apply production packages during non-peak hours.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Required Skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Designing, Building, and automating the MongoDB Architecture for open source MongoDB.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience in using Python to automate infrastructure tasks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience on automating ElastiCache provisioning, administration and maintenance&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Expert MongoDB architectural knowledge&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Considered a leader in the field&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience working with relational data modeling using tools like Erwin&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience working with AWS database services including RDS, EC2, S3,&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Infrastructure and configuration automation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Desired Skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ansible Automation experience&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Jenkins&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Git/Bitbucket&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Confluence/JIRA&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Working in Agile and DEVOPS environment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education:&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bachelors degree from an accredited college in a related discipline or equivalent work years&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We offer a full benefits package. This includes but is not limited to:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;We will contribute $400 to $800&amp;nbsp;towards your healthcare plan. We have&amp;nbsp;multiple plans available&amp;nbsp;to fit your life for Medical, Vision, Dental &amp;amp; Prescription.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Employer paid Life Insurance &amp;amp; Long/Short Disability Insurance&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;3 weeks PTO, roll over up to 200 hours&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;8 paid holidays and 2 paid floating holidays&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;401k, vested&amp;nbsp;immediately, we match up to 3%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent work life balance&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A commitment to creating a fulfilling&amp;nbsp;work environment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;No 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;nbsp;party Recruiters/agencies please.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Physical Demands&lt;/strong&gt;: Reasonable accommodations may be made to enable individuals with disabilities to perform the essential functions&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;INADEV Corporation does not discriminate against qualified individuals based on their status as protected veterans or individuals with disabilities and prohibits discrimination against all individuals based on their race, color, religion, sex, sexual orientation/gender identity, or national origin.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt; - provided by Dice</HTMLDescription></job>


<job><location>Baltimore, MD, United States</location><title>Senior UNIX System Administrator</title><city>Baltimore</city><state>MD</state><zip>21201</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Full Time</job_type><posted_at>2020-10-06</posted_at><job_reference>6874_50b0320271c32d373bddaa233671e4a4</job_reference><company>University of Maryland</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/4xbcwhn?cs=e3e&amp;jg=2nx5&amp;bid=ubUnnIfdRsq5krX1vsvoZQ==</url><body>The Center for Information Technology Services (CITS) is currently seeking a Senior UNIX Systems Administrator to provide UNIX-based server administration in a hybrid environment. The selected candidate will work both independently and on a team responsible for the installation, support and maintenance of physical, virtual, and cloud servers. Will enforce IT system policies and procedures, and will have responsibility for the integrity and security of enterprise systems. Will collaborate with other IT staff, to ensure deliverance of high quality services. The University of Maryland, Baltimore (UMB) offers a comprehensive and competitive benefits package to eligible employees. This position receives an annual leave package starting with 22 accrued vacation days, 14 floating and observed holidays, 15 sick days, and 3 personal days comprehensive health insurance and retirement options professional learning and development opportunities flexible schedules and teleworking options and tuition remission for employees and their dependents at any of the University System of Maryland schools. Essential Functions Oversees and performs server administration, installation and maintenance, such duties as systems patching and implementing server based security based on industry best practices.  Documents day-to-day operational procedures and protocols associated with hardware and operating system environments, as well as reviews system monitoring and logging of abnormalities.  Ensures security and integrity of operating system to increased efficiency for users, applications, operating systems management, etc. Assists in the evaluation of new technologies and products.   Makes recommendations for upgrades to hardware and software based on existing operations, pending needs and available budget.  Provides technical support for application, web and database servers and resolves system related issues.  Responsible for interfacing with other campus staff and department team members to ensure integration of systems and applications. Frequently has project leadership responsibilities and provides training to other IT professionals.  Performs other duties as assigned.    Qualifications Education Bachelors in Information Technology, Computer Science, Systems Administration, Computer Engineering or related field.     Experience Five (5) years of experience with proficient knowledge of at least one (1) UnixLinux operating system, preferably RHELCentOS or Solaris.   Knowledge, Skills, and Abilities   Familiarity with multiple information technologies that include operating systems, server virtualization, cloud based infrastructure, automation, and middleware with expertise in several of the technologies. Preferences include RedHatCentOS Linux, Solaris, VMWare, X86 hardware and AWS. Familiarity with high availability, disaster recovery, and load balancer concepts is a plus. Familiarity with wired and wireless networking hardware and architectures. Familiarity with Virtual LAN (VLAN) setup and configuration, Virtual Private Networks, routing, IPV4, IPV6, etc. Proficiency with various network protocols such as TCPIP, NFS, DNS, SSH, (S)FTP, etc. Proficiency in system security, OS hardening and authentication protocols such as LDAP and Shibboleth. Proficiency in scripting languages such as  Python, Perl, UNIX shell scripting (bash, ksh, etc.) Familiarity with server configuration and automation tools such as Ansible, Puppet, Chef, Cobbler, Kickstart, Cloudformation, etc. Familiarity with open source tools, applications and development practices such as MySQL, Apache, Tomcat.  Ability to identify and address intricate performance enhancement issues that have potential impact for the campus community. Knowledge of office automation tools such as word processors, spreadsheets, and presentation software. Ability to work effectively in a multi-member project team including the ability to cooperate with other team members, work within the scope of the divided tasks, and report progress to project leader. Ability to work effectively on multiple on-going projects and the ability to estimate time for tasks in consultation with senior staff. Good writing and presentation skills. Good analytical, interpersonal, and communication skills. Ability to adapt to changing priorities and quickly learn new skills and techniques. Experience with cloud based infrastructure architecture and deployment.    Equal OpportunityAffirmative Action Employer. Minorities, women, protected veterans and individuals with disabilities are encouraged to apply.</body><cpc>0.20</cpc><HTMLDescription>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;&lt;html&gt;&lt;head&gt;&lt;/head&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Center for Information Technology Services (CITS) is currently seeking a &lt;strong&gt;Senior UNIX Systems Administrator&lt;/strong&gt; to provide UNIX-based server administration in a hybrid environment.&amp;nbsp;The selected candidate will work both independently and on a team responsible for the installation, support and maintenance of physical, virtual, and cloud servers.&amp;nbsp;Will enforce IT system policies and procedures, and will have responsibility for the integrity and security of enterprise systems. Will collaborate with other IT staff, to ensure deliverance of high quality services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The University of Maryland, Baltimore (UMB) offers a comprehensive and competitive benefits package to eligible employees. This position receives an annual leave package starting with 22 accrued vacation days, 14 floating and observed holidays, 15 sick days, and 3 personal days; comprehensive health insurance and retirement options; professional learning and development opportunities; flexible schedules and teleworking options; and tuition remission for employees and their dependents at any of the University System of Maryland schools.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Essential Functions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Oversees and performs server administration, installation and maintenance, such duties as systems patching and implementing server based security based on industry best practices.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Documents day-to-day operational procedures and protocols associated with hardware and operating system environments, as well as reviews system monitoring and logging of abnormalities.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ensures security and integrity of operating system to increased efficiency for users, applications, operating systems management, etc.&amp;nbsp; Assists in the evaluation of new technologies and products.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Makes recommendations for upgrades to hardware and software based on existing operations, pending needs and available budget.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Provides technical support for application, web and database servers and resolves system related issues.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Responsible for interfacing with other campus staff and department team members to ensure integration of systems and applications.&amp;nbsp;Frequently has project leadership responsibilities and provides training to other IT professionals.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Performs other duties as assigned.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education:&lt;/strong&gt; Bachelors in Information Technology, Computer Science, Systems Administration, Computer Engineering or related field. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience:&lt;/strong&gt; Five (5) years of experience with proficient knowledge of at least one (1) Unix/Linux operating system, preferably RHEL/CentOS or Solaris.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Knowledge, Skills, and Abilities&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with multiple information technologies that include operating systems, server virtualization, cloud based infrastructure, automation, and middleware with expertise in several of the technologies.&amp;nbsp; Preferences include:&amp;nbsp; RedHat/CentOS Linux, Solaris, VMWare, X86 hardware and AWS.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with high availability, disaster recovery, and load balancer concepts is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with wired and wireless networking hardware and architectures. Familiarity with Virtual LAN (VLAN) setup and configuration, Virtual Private Networks, routing, IPV4, IPV6, etc.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Proficiency with various network protocols such as: TCP/IP, NFS, DNS, SSH, (S)FTP, etc.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in system security, OS hardening and authentication protocols such as LDAP and Shibboleth.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in scripting languages such as: &amp;nbsp;Python, Perl, UNIX shell scripting (bash, ksh, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with server configuration and automation tools such as Ansible, Puppet, Chef, Cobbler, Kickstart, Cloudformation, etc.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with open source tools, applications and development practices such as MySQL, Apache, Tomcat.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ability to identify and address intricate performance enhancement issues that have potential impact for the campus community.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of office automation tools such as word processors, spreadsheets, and presentation software.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ability to work effectively in a multi-member project team including the ability to cooperate with other team members, work within the scope of the divided tasks, and report progress to project leader.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ability to work effectively on multiple on-going projects and the ability to estimate time for tasks in consultation with senior staff.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Good writing and presentation skills.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Good analytical, interpersonal, and communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ability to adapt to changing priorities and quickly learn new skills and techniques.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with cloud based infrastructure architecture and deployment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Equal Opportunity/Affirmative Action Employer. Minorities, women, protected veterans and individuals with disabilities are encouraged to apply.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt; - provided by Dice</HTMLDescription></job>

<job><location>Annapolis, MD, United States</location><title>Cloud Linux Systems Engineer - Telco (CTH)</title><city>Annapolis</city><state>MD</state><zip>21401</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Contractor</job_type><posted_at>2020-10-05</posted_at><job_reference>6874_b50dc74a87ff37c2209d6e5862b635b8</job_reference><company>iSpace, Inc</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/5dyz91i?cs=e3e&amp;jg=2ou4&amp;bid=q4vrqYs61qv7kasNeA5Aeg==</url><body>Cloud Linux Systems Engineer with Telco Experience in Annapolis, MD Contract to Hire Option to work remotely until the social distancing efforts are lifted A current LinkedIn profile that matches the resume is required for this position This senior-level professional is a seasoned individual that works on complex development assignments and delivers solutions qualified for in-networkhosted Telecom product operation. Candidate is expected to have a firm grasp of system administration, network protocols, networking issues and solutions, system monitoring, configuration management, databases, cloud deployments, image building for cloud environment to quickly come up with solutions to facilitate product operation. The candidate may act as a member of quick-response deployment-support team and will often work under demanding deadlines, operating as a team member as well as independently to resolve complex problems. Candidate will be working in a agile environment where heshe is expected to carry out both development and testing.   RESPONSIBILITIES    Work with other Design Engineers to plan, design and implement systems in a heterogeneous, distributed computing environment Design, implement and Test supporting platform software components that include components that involve integration, configuration management and deployment automation of various software components for cloud deployments, OpenStack in specific VMcontainer image building Implement platform services system administration setting up networking and troubleshooting network issues system monitoring databases  Proficiency working in an OpenStackContainer environments Provides leadership in enabling and enforcing security controls on VMs, servers, network, and cloud architectures and analyze security issues and identify fixes based on vulnerability reports Implement solutions for high-availability for products to survive in mission-critical environments. Other duties as assignedenspensp    SKILLS REQUIRED 5 years of Industry experience in telecom industry OpenStack cloud deployment DockerContainers Ansible js UnixLinux (CentOS, RedHat) system administration Packer Agile development Development or DevOps experience Cisco Networking Network security and system security experience BashBourne shell scripting and standard Unix tools (sed, awk, Expect etc.) Building, automating, and supporting distributed computing environments. Database(Postgres) configuration and management    Having the following experience is a plus Source code management tools such as Perforce, Git Atlassian Tools (Jira, Confluence, FisheyeCrucible) VM Ware deployment Python KickstartPXE BootGrub CFEngine Logical Volume Manager YUM Repositories</body><cpc>0.22</cpc><CompanyLogo>https://assets.dice.com/external/images/empLogos/7f79466727321b50133fb52e8f5c16df.jpg</CompanyLogo><HTMLDescription>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;&lt;html&gt;&lt;head&gt;&lt;/head&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cloud Linux Systems Engineer with Telco Experience in &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Annapolis, MD&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contract to Hire&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Option to work remotely until the social distancing efforts are lifted&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A current LinkedIn profile that matches the resume is required for this position&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This senior-level professional is a seasoned individual that works on complex development assignments and delivers solutions qualified for in-network/hosted Telecom product operation.&amp;nbsp; Candidate is expected to have a firm grasp of system administration, network protocols, networking issues and solutions, system monitoring, configuration management, databases, cloud deployments, image building for cloud environment to quickly come up with solutions to facilitate product operation. The candidate may act as a member of quick-response deployment-support team and will often work under demanding deadlines, operating as a team member as well as independently to resolve complex problems. Candidate will be working in a agile environment where he/she is expected to carry out both development and testing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RESPONSIBILITIES:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work with other Design Engineers to plan, design and implement systems in a heterogeneous, distributed computing environment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Design, implement and Test supporting platform software components that include components that involve&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;integration, configuration management and deployment automation of various software components for cloud deployments, OpenStack in specific&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;VM/container image building&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Implement platform services&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;system administration&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;setting up networking and troubleshooting network issues&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;system monitoring&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;databases&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Proficiency working in an OpenStack/Container environments&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Provides leadership in enabling and enforcing security controls on VMs, servers, network, and cloud architectures and analyze security issues and identify fixes based on vulnerability reports&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Implement solutions for high-availability for products to survive in mission-critical environments.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Other duties as assigned&amp;ensp;&amp;ensp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SKILLS REQUIRED:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;5 years of Industry experience in telecom industry&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;OpenStack cloud deployment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Docker/Containers&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ansible&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;js&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Unix/Linux (CentOS, RedHat) system administration&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Packer&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Agile development&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Development or DevOps experience&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cisco Networking&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Network security and system security experience&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bash/Bourne shell scripting and standard Unix tools (sed, awk, Expect etc.)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Building, automating, and supporting distributed computing environments.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Database(Postgres) configuration and management&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Having the following experience is a plus:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Source code management tools such as Perforce, Git&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Atlassian Tools (Jira, Confluence, Fisheye/Crucible)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;VM Ware deployment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Python&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Kickstart/PXE Boot/Grub&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;CFEngine&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Logical Volume Manager&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;YUM Repositories&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt; - provided by Dice</HTMLDescription></job>

<job><location>Jersey City, NJ, United States</location><title>Application Architect - Java/BPM or RPA</title><city>Jersey City</city><state>NJ</state><zip>07097</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Contractor</job_type><posted_at>2020-10-07</posted_at><job_reference>6874_c805b78fffac1432b592dfc51a4946e2</job_reference><company>Comptech Associates Inc</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/5frpaws?cs=e3e&amp;jg=1jcf&amp;bid=TMQKNCFaov4fFLqS_v4dTg==</url><body>Please mail your resume to Contact  732-412-1389   Job title Application Architect Location Whitehouse station or Jersey City, NJ Duration 6+ months Job description The Application Architect will be responsible for defining the solution and technically leading large programs to success. Responsibilities bull Develop flexible, adaptable, modular and reusable business solution architecture designs in collaboration with product delivery and operation support teams. bull Work with project managers and engineers to ensure alignment of program deliverables to defined solution bull Work with developers closely to review code, enforce best practices, debug critical issues, and conduct performance testing to deliver efficient and performant applications. bull Responsible for identifying technology risk and corresponding mitigation strategies bull Implement appropriate solution architecture governance processes and tools while maintaining a key focus on design patterns and technology standards. bull Act as an enabler of Agile and DevOps practices in collaboration with product delivery and operation support teams. bull Explore, evaluate and promote technology innovation within the enterprise. bull Evaluate, learn and assist teams with open source technology solutions. Knowledge, Skills and Abilities bull Bachelor&apos;s Degree, Computer Science or Engineering degrees preferred bull Hands on architect who is comfortable working with engineers at codedetailed design level. bull Coding experiences and skills preferred -Java, Kafka, MQ, Javascript, Angular, Node.js, Azure, AWS, Business Process Management (BPM), Robotic Process Automation (RPA), API Management (API-M). bull Ability to guide and mentor development teams on sound design and coding principles, best practices in API based, Micro Services and Cloud environments. bull Ability to work with development teams closely together to review code, debug issues, and conduct performance testing to build efficient and performant applications. bull Experience in application modularisation and modernisation including adoption of Micro Service Architecture models bull Experience with workflow automation or robotic process automation implementations using Business Process Management(BPM) tools like Open Text App Works or Robotic Process Automation tools like WorkFusion bull Working experience with WorkFusion IDP (Intelligent Document Processing) or Soroco RPA is preferred bull Experience in Integration Architectures from Service Bus to API Mediation and Event Bus models bull Working Experience with API management tools like Azure API-M or APIGEE required bull Ability to abstract-up to harvest patterns and articulate design decisions with senior audience (CIO level) bull Extensive knowledge and experience of underwriting platform architectures, from blueprint to solution design and implementation bull Experience in Information Security and Risk Management bull Experience in cloud solution design and implementation of IaaS, PaaS and SaaS and hybrid models bull Understanding of platform design and technology considerations to build out an ecosystem for producers and consumers Key Attributes bull Demonstrated ability to communicate effectively both orally and in writing and to interact effectively with internal and external individuals. bull Demonstrated ability to communicate effectively both orally and in writing and to interact effectively with internal and external stakeholders. bull Strong business acumen, instinct and understanding of products, risk appetite and niches. bull Track record of high achievement in a team-based and results-oriented culture bull Proven track record in relationship-building and driving change in a matrixed work environment. bull Demonstrated passion and ability to leverage technology to evolve and meet client needs bull Exceptional analytical and critical thinking skills, with thorough attention to detail. bull Excellent planning, documentation and problem solving skills. bull Project management ability and drive-for-results orientation.</body><cpc>0.21</cpc><CompanyLogo>https://assets.dice.com/external/images/empLogos/d6b8e85f56b8b9dfea8fca7b745717e5.jpg</CompanyLogo><HTMLDescription>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;&lt;html&gt;&lt;head&gt;&lt;/head&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;wordsection1&quot; style=&quot;margin: 0cm; margin-bottom: .0001pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 9.0pt;&quot;&gt;Please mail your resume to Contact : 732-412-1389&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;wordsection1&quot; style=&quot;margin: 0cm; margin-bottom: .0001pt;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;wordsection1&quot; style=&quot;margin: 0cm; margin-bottom: .0001pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 9.0pt;&quot;&gt;Job title: Application Architect&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 9.0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location: Whitehouse station or Jersey City, NJ&lt;br /&gt;Duration: 6+ months&lt;br /&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 10.0pt;&quot;&gt;Job description: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 10.0pt;&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 10.5pt; font-family: &apos;72&apos;,serif;&quot;&gt;The Application Architect will be responsible for defining the solution and technically leading large programs to success.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-family: &apos;72&apos;,serif;&quot;&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Develop flexible, adaptable, modular and reusable business solution architecture designs in collaboration with product delivery and operation support teams.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Work with project managers and engineers to ensure alignment of program deliverables to defined solution&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Work with developers closely to review code, enforce best practices, debug critical issues, and conduct performance testing to deliver efficient and performant applications.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Responsible for identifying technology risk and corresponding mitigation strategies&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Implement appropriate solution architecture governance processes and tools while maintaining a key focus on design patterns and technology standards.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Act as an enabler of Agile and DevOps practices in collaboration with product delivery and operation support teams.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Explore, evaluate and promote technology innovation within the enterprise.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Evaluate, learn and assist teams with open source technology solutions.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-family: &apos;72&apos;,serif;&quot;&gt;Knowledge, Skills and Abilities&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Bachelor&apos;s Degree, Computer Science or Engineering degrees preferred&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Hands on architect who is comfortable working with engineers at code/detailed design level.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Coding experiences and skills preferred -Java, Kafka, MQ, Javascript, Angular, Node.js, Azure, AWS, Business Process Management (BPM), Robotic Process Automation (RPA), API Management (API-M).&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Ability to guide and mentor development teams on sound design and coding principles, best practices in API based, Micro Services and Cloud environments.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Ability to work with development teams closely together to review code, debug issues, and conduct performance testing to build efficient and performant applications.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Experience in application modularisation and modernisation including adoption of Micro Service Architecture models&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Experience with workflow automation or robotic process automation implementations using Business Process Management(BPM) tools like Open Text App Works or Robotic Process Automation tools like WorkFusion&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Working experience with WorkFusion IDP (Intelligent Document Processing) or Soroco RPA is preferred&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Experience in Integration Architectures from Service Bus to API Mediation and Event Bus models&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Working Experience with API management tools like Azure API-M or APIGEE required&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Ability to abstract-up to harvest patterns and articulate design decisions with senior audience (CIO level)&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Extensive knowledge and experience of underwriting platform architectures, from blueprint to solution design and implementation&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Experience in Information Security and Risk Management&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Experience in cloud solution design and implementation of IaaS, PaaS and SaaS and hybrid models&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Understanding of platform design and technology considerations to build out an ecosystem for producers and consumers&lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-family: &apos;72&apos;,serif;&quot;&gt;Key Attributes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Demonstrated ability to communicate effectively both orally and in writing and to interact effectively with internal and external individuals.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Demonstrated ability to communicate effectively both orally and in writing and to interact effectively with internal and external stakeholders.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Strong business acumen, instinct and understanding of products, risk appetite and niches.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Track record of high achievement in a team-based and results-oriented culture&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Proven track record in relationship-building and driving change in a matrixed work environment.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Demonstrated passion and ability to leverage technology to evolve and meet client needs&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Exceptional analytical and critical thinking skills, with thorough attention to detail.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Excellent planning, documentation and problem solving skills.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull; Project management ability and drive-for-results orientation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt; - provided by Dice</HTMLDescription></job>

<job><location>Milwaukee, WI, United States</location><title>Software Engineer (SaaS &amp; Data)</title><city>Milwaukee</city><state>WI</state><zip>53201</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Contractor</job_type><posted_at>2020-10-07</posted_at><job_reference>6874_60453382fd81be21e3573d9ef514b890</job_reference><company>Codeworks L.L.C</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/3vhp34o?cs=e3e&amp;jg=1jcf&amp;bid=TMQKNCFaov4fFLqS_v4dTg==</url><body>Codeworks is a local IT Services firm in SE Wisconsin, known for our strong commitment to quality and for our direct client relationships.    Our financial services client located in downtown Milwaukee is looking to engage an experienced Software Engineer on 6+ month contract basis. As a Software Engineer, this individual will provide technical development and support with SaaS vendors.  They will work closely with vendors for exchanging data.  Looking for someone to understand the Vendor and the extensive data movement. Other responsibilities will include Develop integrated solutions, modernizing, consolidating and coordinating independently-designed applications to meet business needs. Partner with Architecture to develop best practices. Analyze businessfunctional specifications to deliver quality solutions via SaaS. Work on projects in a collaborative setting, following an Agile development approach.   Qualified candidates will have multiple years of experience with the following  Understanding of databases, various techniques for extracting data, managing data and sending data to the vendor Proficiency with ETL data movement, SSRS or PowerBI for reporting Knowledge of SSO and other security related options for internal and external use of SaaS applications. Knowledge of C.Net to support a large non-vendor application Agile mindset with experience working with Scrum and JIRA  Experience with or willingness to learn the following JavaScript, CSS, Object Oriented Design Patterns, RESTful API, SQL, Linux, Ansible, Jenkins, andor CICD. Any knowledge with networking (system processintegration) or PCLAN knowledge is a plus.    If this type of role sounds exciting to you and a good fit for your background, qualified candidates should send their resumes to careerscodeworks-inc.com  mailtocareerscodeworks-inc.com .  Attn Laura. Local candidates will be given first priority. Candidates must be available to work directly for Codeworks.    About CODEWORKS Headquartered in Milwaukee, WI with an additional office in Madison, WImdashCodeworks has more than 20 years of experience successfully serving Fortune 1000 companies in Wisconsin, as well as, our client&apos;s national locations. Our Recruiting team consists of highly skilled Talent Specialists skilled at evaluating, advising, and connecting IT professionals with new career opportunities that facilitate career growth.</body><cpc>0.21</cpc><CompanyLogo>https://assets.dice.com/external/images/empLogos/420cccd4070838f3fbd2f2528213c6ab.png</CompanyLogo><HTMLDescription>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;&lt;html&gt;&lt;head&gt;&lt;/head&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Codeworks is a local IT Services firm in SE Wisconsin, known for our strong commitment to quality and for our direct client relationships.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our financial services client located in downtown Milwaukee is looking to engage an experienced Software Engineer on 6+ month contract basis.&amp;nbsp; As a Software Engineer, this individual will provide&amp;nbsp;technical development and support with SaaS vendors.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; They will work closely with vendors for exchanging data. &amp;nbsp;Looking for someone to understand the Vendor and the extensive data movement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other responsibilities will include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Develop integrated solutions, modernizing, consolidating and coordinating independently-designed applications to meet business needs.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Partner with Architecture to develop best practices.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Analyze business/functional specifications to deliver quality solutions via SaaS.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work on projects in a collaborative setting, following an Agile development approach.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualified candidates will have multiple years of experience with the following: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Understanding of databases, various techniques for extracting data, managing data and sending data to the vendor&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Proficiency with ETL data movement, SSRS or PowerBI for reporting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of SSO and other security related options for internal and external use of SaaS applications.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of C#/.Net to support a large non-vendor application&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Agile mindset with experience working with Scrum and JIRA&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with or willingness to learn the following; JavaScript, CSS, Object Oriented Design Patterns, RESTful API, SQL, Linux, Ansible, Jenkins, and/or CICD.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Any knowledge with networking (system process/integration) or PC/LAN knowledge is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If this type of role sounds exciting to you and a good fit for your background, qualified candidates should send their resumes to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:careers@codeworks-inc.com&quot;&gt;careers@codeworks-inc.com&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Attn:&amp;nbsp; Laura.&amp;nbsp; Local candidates will be given first priority.&amp;nbsp; &lt;strong&gt;Candidates must be available to work directly for Codeworks.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;About CODEWORKS:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Headquartered in Milwaukee, WI with an additional office in Madison, WI&amp;mdash;Codeworks has more than 20 years of experience successfully serving Fortune 1000 companies in Wisconsin, as well as, our client&apos;s national locations. Our Recruiting team consists of highly skilled Talent Specialists skilled at evaluating, advising, and connecting IT professionals with new career opportunities that facilitate career growth.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt; - provided by Dice</HTMLDescription></job>

<job><location>Plano, TX, United States</location><title>Senior Full Stack Developer (Business Intelligence)</title><city>Plano</city><state>TX</state><zip>75023</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Full Time</job_type><posted_at>2020-10-04</posted_at><job_reference>6874_2e9d9031f2fe9e46c37325d6ca986aed</job_reference><company>Alkami Technology</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/4tu3t9k?cs=e3e&amp;jg=2ou4&amp;bid=q4vrqYs61qv7kasNeA5Aeg==</url><body>Alkami builds and delivers the nationrsquos most innovative cloud-based digital banking (online and mobile apps) for Credit Unions and Banks with over 6M users on our platform. Through our bold investments in technology and people, our clients confidently grow, adapt quickly and build thriving digital banking communities to compete against the Megabanks. Founded 10 years ago with headquarters in Plano, Alkami is one of the fastest growing software companies in Texas and among the fastest growing privately held technology companies in the U.S. To share just a few of our recent recognitions Best Place to Work in Fintech Inc. 500 Americarsquos Fastest-Growing Private Companies Deloitte Technology Fast 500 Tech Titans Top 5 and, SMU Cox Caruth Institute Dallas 100. With every Alkamist having ownership in Alkami, we are obsessively intentional about our culture optimistic-perseverance, caring-collaboration, transparent-communication, courageous-innovation, trusted-accountability and real-fun. Beyond intentional culture, our commitment is to attract and retain amazing talent by fostering a high-growth, dynamic and rewarding environment providing great benefits making meaningful investments in learning and development offering free lunches every work day celebrating our successes together in remarkable ways and, ACTing together by taking time to give back and volunteer. Position Overview We are looking for a hardworking Senior Analytics Engineer for a key position on an exciting mission-critical team. You will be the technical lead of a team responsible for a strategic project producing modern web tools with dashboards and reports for business analytics that integrate to a cloud native Enterprise Data Warehouse and Business Intelligence tool.  You will work closely with your Product Owner to understand and refine business requirements and be the primary technical point of contact for the team. This position coordinates and organizes development efforts surrounding sprint work to ensure the successful delivery of the teamrsquos commitments. You will have around 50 to 70 of your time dedicated to developing planned sprint tasks. This will require sound technical judgement to design and implement solutions to business requirements that adhere to standard practices and long term technical vision defined by Alkamirsquos Architecture group. You must exercise critical thinking skills to troubleshoot and resolve production issues in a timely manner. You are expected to treat others with respect and operate with integrity and high moral standards. Key Responsibilities  Duties Lead an AnalyticsSoftware Engineering team to design, develop and deliver analytics features and enhancements Ability to communicate effectively with various stakeholders in the organization Refine business requirements into clearly defined technical specifications Ensure team is organized and focused on the right tasks to deliver sprint commitments Design scalable and performant technical solutions capable of handling large data sets, complex analytics and multiple users  Identify project risks and work with the team to address them in a timely manner   Develop solutions to complex problems Team player and collaborator with the ability to mentor junior team members Ability to act as a servant leader to the team Ability to be adaptable and flexible  Ability to resolve conflicts timely without affecting team morale Hungry but humble Strong work ethic High degree of accountability and ownership Other assigned duties.  Qualifications 8+ years of Javascript, HTML, CSS 8+ years of general development experience 3+ years working with Javascript frameworks such as Vue.js, React.js, Angular.js 3+ years .NET Framework, C Experience integrating to APIs Experience working with SQL Server 2008+, including writing queries, stored procedures, creating tables, indexes and foreign keys and query tuning and optimization Excellent understanding of SOA principles, including experience implementing REST andor WCF services Experience working with ORM frameworks (such as ADO.NET Entity Framework, LINQ to SQL, and NHibernate) Experience working with SCM systems (such as Git, Subversion, Mercurial, VSS, or TFS) in continuous integration environments (such as Jenkins, Bamboo, CruiseControl or TeamCity) Experience implementing N-tier architecture designs in distributed environments Experience working with unit testing tools (NUnit) and familiarity with Test-Driven Development  Desired Skills 8+ years of experience in designing and developing Business IntelligenceAnalytics solutions Experience working with large data sets, data analysis, data architecture, and data pipelines Exposure to Business Intelligence tools (MicroStrategy, Tableau, Power BI) Cloud native development experience highly desired - AWS is a bonus  Cool Things to Know Not Just Any Company Alkami has an awesome diverse and inclusive environment. We have a FUN culture and offer great benefits. Did you know every Alkamist has ownership in Alkami? We also have on and off site employee events and activities. Free Lunch Who said there is no free lunch? At Alkami, every day we offer free lunch Relocation Unfortunately we don&apos;t offer relocation assistance. We are ready for you to contribute from our super cool Plano, TX location. Work Authorization We cannot offer employer sponsorship at this time candidates must be eligible to work in the US for full-time employment. Recruiters We are not looking for outside recruiting firms to help us in this search mdash we know who you are and we love you, but we donrsquot need you right now.  The Important Stuff Alkami Technology is an Equal Opportunity Employer and Prohibits Discrimination and Harassment of Any Kind Alkami is committed to the principle of equal employment opportunity for all employees and to providing employees with a work environment free of discrimination and harassment. All employment decisions at Alkami are based on business needs, job requirements and individual qualifications, without regard to race, color, religion or belief, national, social or ethnic origin, sex (including pregnancy), age, physical, mental or sensory disability, HIV Status, sexual orientation, gender identity andor expression, marital, civil union or domestic partnership status, past or present military service, family medical history or genetic information, family or parental status, or any other status protected by the laws or regulations in the locations where we operate. Alkami will not tolerate discrimination or harassment based on any of these characteristics. Alkami encourages applicants of all ages.</body><cpc>0.22</cpc><CompanyLogo>https://assets.dice.com/external/images/empLogos/743dd8e1ee9b0abe65c8902913483e5e.jpg</CompanyLogo><HTMLDescription>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;&lt;html&gt;&lt;head&gt;&lt;/head&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alkami builds and delivers the nation&amp;rsquo;s most innovative cloud-based digital banking (online and mobile apps) for Credit Unions and Banks with over 6M users on our platform. Through our bold investments in technology and people, our clients confidently grow, adapt quickly and build thriving digital banking communities to compete against the Megabanks. Founded 10 years ago with headquarters in Plano, Alkami is one of the fastest growing software companies in Texas and among the fastest growing privately held technology companies in the U.S. To share just a few of our recent recognitions:&amp;nbsp; Best Place to Work in Fintech;&amp;nbsp; Inc. 500 America&amp;rsquo;s Fastest-Growing Private Companies; Deloitte Technology Fast 500; Tech Titans Top 5; and, SMU Cox Caruth Institute Dallas 100.&amp;nbsp; With every Alkamist having ownership in Alkami, we are obsessively intentional about our culture: optimistic-perseverance, caring-collaboration, transparent-communication, courageous-innovation, trusted-accountability and real-fun.&amp;nbsp; Beyond intentional culture, our commitment is to attract and retain amazing talent by fostering a high-growth, dynamic and rewarding environment; providing great benefits; making meaningful investments in learning and development; offering free lunches every work day; celebrating our successes together in remarkable ways; and, ACTing together by taking time to give back and volunteer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Position Overview&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a hardworking Senior Analytics Engineer for a key position on an exciting mission-critical team. You will be the technical lead of a team responsible for a strategic project producing modern web tools with dashboards and reports for business analytics that integrate to a cloud native Enterprise Data Warehouse and Business Intelligence tool.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You will work closely with your Product Owner to understand and refine business requirements and be the primary technical point of contact for the team. This position coordinates and organizes development efforts surrounding sprint work to ensure the successful delivery of the team&amp;rsquo;s commitments. You will have around 50% to 70% of your time dedicated to developing planned sprint tasks. This will require sound technical judgement to design and implement solutions to business requirements that adhere to standard practices and long term technical vision defined by Alkami&amp;rsquo;s Architecture group. You must exercise critical thinking skills to troubleshoot and resolve production issues in a timely manner. You are expected to treat others with respect and operate with integrity and high moral standards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Responsibilities &amp;amp; Duties&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lead an Analytics/Software Engineering team to design, develop and deliver analytics features and enhancements&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ability to communicate effectively with various stakeholders in the organization&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Refine business requirements into clearly defined technical specifications&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ensure team is organized and focused on the right tasks to deliver sprint commitments&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Design scalable and performant technical solutions capable of handling large data sets, complex analytics and multiple users&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Identify project risks and work with the team to address them in a timely manner&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Develop solutions to complex problems&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Team player and collaborator with the ability to mentor junior team members&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ability to act as a servant leader to the team&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ability to be adaptable and flexible&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ability to resolve conflicts timely without affecting team morale&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hungry but humble&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong work ethic&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;High degree of accountability and ownership&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Other assigned duties.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;8+ years of Javascript, HTML, CSS&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;8+ years of general development experience&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;3+ years working with Javascript frameworks such as Vue.js, React.js, Angular.js&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;3+ years .NET Framework, C#&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience integrating to APIs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience working with SQL Server 2008+, including writing queries, stored procedures, creating tables, indexes and foreign keys and query tuning and optimization&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent understanding of SOA principles, including experience implementing REST and/or WCF services&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience working with ORM frameworks (such as ADO.NET Entity Framework, LINQ to SQL, and NHibernate)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience working with SCM systems (such as Git, Subversion, Mercurial, VSS, or TFS) in continuous integration environments (such as Jenkins, Bamboo, CruiseControl or TeamCity)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience implementing N-tier architecture designs in distributed environments&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience working with unit testing tools (NUnit) and familiarity with Test-Driven Development&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Desired Skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;8+ years of experience in designing and developing Business Intelligence/Analytics solutions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience working with large data sets, data analysis, data architecture, and data pipelines&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Exposure to Business Intelligence tools (MicroStrategy, Tableau, Power BI)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cloud native development experience highly desired - AWS is a bonus&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cool Things to Know&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Not Just Any Company&lt;/strong&gt;: Alkami has an awesome diverse and inclusive environment. We have a FUN culture and offer great benefits. Did you know every Alkamist has ownership in Alkami? We also have on and off site employee events and activities.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Free Lunch&lt;/strong&gt;: Who said there is no free lunch? At Alkami, every day we offer free lunch&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Relocation&lt;/strong&gt;: Unfortunately we don&apos;t offer relocation assistance. We are ready for you to contribute from our super cool Plano, TX location.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Work Authorization&lt;/strong&gt;: We cannot offer employer sponsorship at this time; candidates must be eligible to work in the US for full-time employment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Recruiters&lt;/strong&gt;: We are not looking for outside recruiting firms to help us in this search &amp;mdash; we know who you are and we love you, but we don&amp;rsquo;t need you right now.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Important Stuff&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Alkami Technology is an Equal Opportunity Employer and Prohibits Discrimination and Harassment of Any Kind:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Alkami is committed to the principle of equal employment opportunity for all employees and to providing employees with a work environment free of discrimination and harassment. All employment decisions at Alkami are based on business needs, job requirements and individual qualifications, without regard to race, color, religion or belief, national, social or ethnic origin, sex (including pregnancy), age, physical, mental or sensory disability, HIV Status, sexual orientation, gender identity and/or expression, marital, civil union or domestic partnership status, past or present military service, family medical history or genetic information, family or parental status, or any other status protected by the laws or regulations in the locations where we operate. Alkami will not tolerate discrimination or harassment based on any of these characteristics. Alkami encourages applicants of all ages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt; - provided by Dice</HTMLDescription></job>

<job><location>, , United States</location><title>Integrity Science Engineer</title><city></city><state></state><zip></zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Contractor</job_type><posted_at>2020-10-04</posted_at><job_reference>6874_3e2c9ddfe9295ec43218aa125eaa674e</job_reference><company>SGS Consulting</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/5fookow?cs=e3e&amp;jg=1s8z&amp;bid=q4vrqYs61qv7kasNeA5Aeg==</url><body>Duties Dive into the world of big data and trend analysis to solve complex problems and improve Facebook community experiences! Learn how to scale and automate abuse detection processesmdash Come join us at Facebook! We are looking for engineers with extensive experience investigating and analyzing online abuse, and actively implementing countermeasures. Our focus on data analysis and machine learning as well as our knowledge of the robust infrastructure of our back-end systems allows us to collaborate seamlessly with engineering, data science, and operations teams to build tools and techniques necessary to enforce content quality at scale. Integrity Science Engineers have the opportunity to work on many of the most challenging, complicated, and high-visibility integrity risks the company faces. Our work impacts the billions of people who use Facebook products The potential for impact with this work is substantial, as outcomes could affect the billions of people who use our products. Successful candidates for this team have a bias toward action and enjoy finding patterns amid chaos, making quick decisions, and aren&apos;t afraid of being wrong. The perfect candidate will have a background in a quantitative or technical field, will have experience working with large data sets, and will have in-depth experience in data-driven decision making. You are scrappy, focused on results, a self-starter, and have demonstrated success in using analytics to reduce abuse and negative user experiences across the platform.   Responsibilities Identify and investigate online bad actors with the interest and capability to target Facebook and its users Work closely with others to identify sources of abusive behavior and take countermeasures to stop abuse Lead technical investigations from start-to-finish and effectively communicate actionable results to different audience types Manage multiple projects at once while prioritizing time based on team priorities     Skills Minimum Qualification 2+ years experience doing quantitative analysis Experience investigating and acting on high-impact threats and online threat actors Experience with relational databases and SQL Experience thinking critically and qualifying assessments with solid communications skills Experience coding in at least one of the following PHP, Python, Haskell, or Java.     Preferred Qualification Experience prioritizing and executing with minimal direction or oversight Experience working across the broader integritysecurityTrust  Safety community Experience in adversarial space like fraud and spam. Proven track record of managing and executing on short term and long term projects Development experience in Haskell. Familiarity with cross-platform integrity threats Demonstrated understanding of security and integrity risks, and how they apply to Facebook and its users   Education   Minimum BABS in Computer Science, MathFinance, Physics, Applied Economics, Statistics or other technical field.  Preferred Advanced degrees in Computer Science, MathFinance, Physics, Applied Economics, Statistics or other technical field.</body><cpc>0.22</cpc><CompanyLogo>https://assets.dice.com/external/images/empLogos/9219eb8ac30a492ac535766fd5715e76.gif</CompanyLogo><HTMLDescription>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;&lt;html&gt;&lt;head&gt;&lt;/head&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Duties:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dive into the world of big data and trend analysis to solve complex problems and improve Facebook community experiences! Learn how to scale and automate abuse detection processes&amp;amp;mdash; Come join us at Facebook! We are looking for engineers with extensive experience investigating and analyzing online abuse, and actively implementing countermeasures. Our focus on data analysis and machine learning as well as our knowledge of the robust infrastructure of our back-end systems allows us to collaborate seamlessly with engineering, data science, and operations teams to build tools and techniques necessary to enforce content quality at scale. Integrity Science Engineers have the opportunity to work on many of the most challenging, complicated, and high-visibility integrity risks the company faces. Our work impacts the billions of people who use Facebook products The potential for impact with this work is substantial, as outcomes could affect the billions of people who use our products. Successful candidates for this team have a bias toward action and enjoy finding patterns amid chaos, making quick decisions, and aren&apos;t afraid of being wrong. The perfect candidate will have a background in a quantitative or technical field, will have experience working with large data sets, and will have in-depth experience in data-driven decision making. You are scrappy, focused on results, a self-starter, and have demonstrated success in using analytics to reduce abuse and negative user experiences across the platform.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Identify and investigate online bad actors with the interest and capability to target Facebook and its users&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work closely with others to identify sources of abusive behavior and take countermeasures to stop abuse&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lead technical investigations from start-to-finish and effectively communicate actionable results to different audience types&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Manage multiple projects at once while prioritizing time based on team priorities&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Skills: Minimum Qualification&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;2+ years experience doing quantitative analysis&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience investigating and acting on high-impact threats and online threat actors&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with relational databases and SQL&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience thinking critically and qualifying assessments with solid communications skills&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience coding in at least one of the following: PHP, Python, Haskell, or Java.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Preferred Qualification&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience prioritizing and executing with minimal direction or oversight&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience working across the broader integrity/security/Trust &amp;amp; Safety community&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience in adversarial space like fraud and spam.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Proven track record of managing and executing on short term and long term projects&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Development experience in Haskell.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with cross-platform integrity threats&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated understanding of security and integrity risks, and how they apply to Facebook and its users&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Education:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Minimum&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;BA/BS in Computer Science, Math/Finance, Physics, Applied Economics, Statistics or other technical field.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Preferred&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Advanced degrees in Computer Science, Math/Finance, Physics, Applied Economics, Statistics or other technical field.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt; - provided by Dice</HTMLDescription></job>

<job><location>Newport News, VA, United States</location><title>MS Access Database Analyst</title><city>Newport News</city><state>VA</state><zip>23601</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Full Time</job_type><posted_at>2020-10-05</posted_at><job_reference>6874_aac12f02d747c8366cbffa2a940caa71</job_reference><company>iQuasar LLC</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/514z5gm?cs=e3e&amp;jg=1k1q&amp;bid=ubUnnIfdRsq5krX1vsvoZQ==</url><body>ProSol, LLC is seeking to fill Microsoft Access Database Analyst for our customer in Newport News, VA. ProSol delivers rapid, reliable solutions that contribute to the success of the U.S. Government. With on-site support at multiple locations worldwide, ProSol specializes in the core areas of Special Operations Planning  Support  httpwww.prosol1.comoperations-planning-and-support , Cyber Security  Information Technology  httpwww.prosol1.comcyber-and-information-technology  and Training  Education  httpwww.prosol1.comtraining-and-education  Services. We offer competitive compensation and benefits including Health, Vision, and Dental Insurance, matching 401k plan, and other benefits given below, excellent training, and a vibrant working environment. Our employees are exceptional, giving us a competitive advantage by innovating solutions with a strong sense of mission and integrity. One of our clients in Newport News, VA needs a Microsoft Access Database Analyst for a contract position. Position Microsoft Access Database Analyst Location Newport News, VA Position Type Contract position Travel NA Job Description The Microsoft Access Database Analyst will support the Supervisor of Shipbuilding, Conversion and Repair, USN, Newport News (SSNN) Information Technology which consists of a legacy Department of Defense Information processing network capabilities residing at the Component Enterprise Data Center (CEDC) consisting of Government and Commercial Off the Shelf (COTS) IT applications, systems and services, Windows Active Directory Servers, File Storage, Citrix Systems, SharePoint, and Primavera and the SUPSHIP Microsoft Access Database (SSMAD) server, a standard Windows File Server connected to the Navy Marine Corps Intranet (NMCI).   The legacy network is designated as a mission assurance category III, Unclassified Navy Nuclear Propulsion Information (U-NNPI Network hosted by Windows Active Directory Domain Controllers with the top-level domain and is comprised of a multitude of mission critical Government and Commercial Off-The-Shelf(COTS IT applications, Systems and Services, Windows Active Directory Servers, Email, File Storage, Blackberry Enterprise Services, Internet Access, Citrix Systems, SharePoint, Networked Printers, as well as Laptop and Desktop Computers. SSNN IT currently supports end users, Personal Computers, Smartphone hand-held devices and Printers at various locations throughout the Newport News Shipbuilding (NNS) complex.   The candidate must have the ability to operate effectively under pressure adhering to the ProSol Core Values of Agility rapid adaptation to the changing requirements and environment of our clients Excellence Service quality that exceeds the expectations of our clients Integrity Accountability and honestyminusalways doing the right thing and Long-Term Commitment Unquestioned loyalty and dedication to our clients, partners and employees.   Responsibilities Provide Microsoft SharePoint Operations and Functions Support. Provide services for Microsoft (MS) AccessInfoPath design and development. All Access Applications System support shall be documented using command ticketing system. Build framework and features for MS AccesslnfoPath data reporting tools. Design, customize, and develop templates, tables, queries, and reports for MS Access. Design, customize, and brand look and feel development services utilizing MS AccesslnfoPath templates, tables, queries, reports and page layouts. Provide expertise to support the implementation for MS AccesslnfoPath databases and reporting tools. Provide expertise to support the implementation of MS AccessInfoPath databases and reporting tools from data exported from the Command work tracking program Technical Support Management. Provide expertise to support the implementation of an automated MS AccesslnfoPath database and reporting tool for data extracted from Technical Support Management and from the Command work tracking program Technical Support Management. Develop test plans for user acceptance testing. Develop test procedures for new enhancements. Provide technical software information as to the design and sustainment for custom MS Access software solutions. Work with technical writers by providing technical software information as to the design and sustainment of custom - developed MS Access software solutions.   Qualifications The Microsoft AccessInfoPath Analyst shall possess at least 2 years in designing, customizing, and branding utilizing MS AccessInfoPath templates, tables, queries, reports and page layouts. Baseline Security+ CE certification and Certification in Microsoft Access Core Database Management and Microsoft lnfoPath training certificate. The individuals current experience must be within the past year working in the DoD Cybersecurity environment.   Clearance - Top Secret Employee Benefits ProSol, LLC  offers a comprehensive benefits program including various options in these plans Medical, Dental, Vision Insurance Paid HolidayAnnualSickPersonalLeave Short-Term Long-Term Disability Insurance Disability Insurance Life Insurance Employee Assistance Program Travel Assistance Program Education Assistance Performance and Incentive Bonuses    If you are interested in this position, please send me a copy of your latest resume at   mailto  with the information requested below Also, please let me know what timenumber is best to call to discuss this great opportunity. In case you are not interested in this position or this is not a right fit for you, please feel free to share this opportunity with your friendsnetworks or anyone you know who may be interested in this position. Thank you!    - Availability to start a new job - Best Rates - Contact  Please donrsquot hesitate to contact me for any question (s) you may have. All employment is decided on the basis of qualifications, merit, and business need.   Best Regards Shane Sofi Senior Recruitment Professional www.prosol1.com Ox 525 Direct 703-936-0049  httpsbusinesssupport.vonage.comclick2callme?keyOXVADCKvvXoeIODjKDampcompanyiQuasar20LLCamptypeemail  Hours 630 a.m. to 330 p.m. EST     An Equal Opportunity Employer ProSol, LLC is proud to be an Equal Employment Opportunity Employer. We do not discriminate based on race, religion, color, national origin, political affiliation, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, age, maritalparental veteran status, disability, genetic information, membership in an employee organization, retaliation, military service, other non-merit factors, or any other applicable characteristics protected by law.</body><cpc>0.20</cpc><CompanyLogo>https://assets.dice.com/external/images/empLogos/cc555393dc03fd5b63e62b827eab58f6.jpg</CompanyLogo><HTMLDescription>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;&lt;html&gt;&lt;head&gt;&lt;/head&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;ProSol, LLC &lt;/em&gt;is seeking to fill Microsoft Access Database Analyst for our customer in Newport News, VA. ProSol delivers rapid, reliable solutions that contribute to the success of the U.S. Government. With on-site support at multiple locations worldwide, ProSol specializes in the core areas of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.prosol1.com/operations-planning-and-support&quot;&gt;Special Operations Planning &amp;amp; Support&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.prosol1.com/cyber-and-information-technology&quot;&gt;Cyber Security &amp;amp; Information Technology&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.prosol1.com/training-and-education&quot;&gt;Training &amp;amp; Education&lt;/a&gt; Services. We offer competitive compensation and benefits including Health, Vision, and Dental Insurance, matching 401k plan, and other benefits given below, excellent training, and a vibrant working environment. Our employees are exceptional, giving us a competitive advantage by innovating solutions with a strong sense of mission and integrity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of our clients in &lt;strong&gt;Newport News, VA&lt;/strong&gt; needs a &lt;strong&gt;Microsoft Access Database Analyst &lt;/strong&gt;for a contract position.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Position: &lt;/strong&gt;Microsoft Access Database Analyst&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location: &lt;/strong&gt;Newport News, VA&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Position Type: &lt;/strong&gt;Contract position&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Travel: &lt;/strong&gt;N/A&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Job Description&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Microsoft Access Database Analyst will support the Supervisor of Shipbuilding, Conversion and Repair, USN, Newport News (SSNN) Information Technology which consists of a legacy Department of Defense Information processing network; capabilities residing at the Component Enterprise Data Center (CEDC) consisting of Government and Commercial Off the Shelf (COTS) IT applications, systems and services, Windows Active Directory Servers, File Storage, Citrix Systems, SharePoint, and Primavera; and the SUPSHIP Microsoft Access Database (SSMAD) server, a standard Windows File Server connected to the Navy Marine Corps Intranet (NMCI).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The legacy network is designated as a mission assurance category III, Unclassified Navy Nuclear Propulsion Information (U-NNPI} Network hosted by Windows Active Directory Domain Controllers with the top-level domain and is comprised of a multitude of mission critical Government and Commercial Off-The-Shelf(COTS} IT applications, Systems and Services, Windows Active Directory Servers, Email, File Storage, Blackberry Enterprise Services, Internet Access, Citrix Systems, SharePoint, Networked Printers, as well as Laptop and Desktop Computers. SSNN IT currently supports end users, Personal Computers, Smartphone hand-held devices and Printers at various locations throughout the Newport News Shipbuilding (NNS) complex.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The candidate must have the ability to operate effectively under pressure adhering to the ProSol Core Values of Agility: rapid adaptation to the changing requirements and environment of our clients; Excellence: Service quality that exceeds the expectations of our clients; Integrity: Accountability and honesty&amp;minus;always doing the right thing; and Long-Term Commitment: Unquestioned loyalty and dedication to our clients, partners and employees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Provide Microsoft SharePoint Operations and Functions Support.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Provide services for Microsoft (MS) Access/InfoPath design and development.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;All Access Applications System support shall be documented using command ticketing system.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Build framework and features for MS Access/lnfoPath data reporting tools.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Design, customize, and develop templates, tables, queries, and reports for MS Access.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Design, customize, and brand look and feel development services utilizing MS Access/lnfoPath templates, tables, queries, reports and page layouts.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Provide expertise to support the implementation for MS Access/lnfoPath databases and reporting tools.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Provide expertise to support the implementation of MS Access/InfoPath databases and reporting tools from data exported from the Command work tracking program Technical Support Management.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Provide expertise to support the implementation of an automated MS Access/lnfoPath database and reporting tool for data extracted from Technical Support Management and from the Command work tracking program Technical Support Management.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Develop test plans for user acceptance testing.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Develop test procedures for new enhancements.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Provide technical software information as to the design and sustainment for custom MS Access software solutions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work with technical writers by providing technical software information as to the design and sustainment of custom - developed MS Access software solutions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Microsoft Access/InfoPath Analyst shall possess at least 2 years in designing, customizing, and branding utilizing MS Access/InfoPath templates, tables, queries, reports and page layouts.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Baseline &lt;strong&gt;Security+ CE&lt;/strong&gt; certification and;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Certification in Microsoft Access: Core Database Management and Microsoft lnfoPath training certificate.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The individuals current experience must be within the past year working in the DoD Cybersecurity environment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Clearance: - &lt;/strong&gt;Top Secret&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Employee Benefits:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;ProSol, LLC &lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;offers a comprehensive benefits program including various options in these plans:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Medical, Dental, Vision Insurance&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Paid Holiday/Annual/Sick/PersonalLeave&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Short-Term/ Long-Term Disability Insurance&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Disability Insurance&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Life Insurance&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Employee Assistance Program&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Travel Assistance Program&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Education Assistance&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Performance and Incentive Bonuses&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in this position, please send me a copy of your latest resume at &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt; with the information requested below: Also, please let me know what time/number is best to call to discuss this great opportunity. In case you are not interested in this position or this is not a right fit for you, please feel free to share this opportunity with your friends/networks or anyone you know who may be interested in this position. Thank you!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;- Availability to start a new job&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;- Best Rates&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;- Contact #&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please don&amp;rsquo;t hesitate to contact me for any question (s) you may have. &lt;em&gt;All employment is decided on the basis of qualifications, merit, and business need.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Best Regards&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shane Sofi&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Recruitment Professional&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;www.prosol1.com&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ox 525&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Direct: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://businesssupport.vonage.com/click2callme?key=OXVADCKvvXoeIODjKD&amp;amp;company=iQuasar%20LLC&amp;amp;type=email&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;703-936-0049&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hours: 6:30 a.m. to 3:30 p.m. EST&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;An Equal Opportunity Employer&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;ProSol, LLC&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;is proud to be an Equal Employment Opportunity Employer. We do not discriminate based on race, religion, color, national origin, political affiliation, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, age, marital/parental /veteran status, disability, genetic information, membership in an employee organization, retaliation, military service, other non-merit factors, or any other applicable characteristics protected by law.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt; - provided by Dice</HTMLDescription></job>

<job><location>Ogden, UT, United States</location><title>.Net Engineer</title><city>Ogden</city><state>UT</state><zip>84201</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Full Time</job_type><posted_at>2020-10-07</posted_at><job_reference>6874_2ac5308284591c66b9c34cf617a5612f</job_reference><company>PrincePerelson &amp; Associates</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/4n0a2hc?cs=e3e&amp;jg=2ou4&amp;bid=q4vrqYs61qv7kasNeA5Aeg==</url><body>The Software Engineer is responsible numerous projects and using C, JavaScript, Typescript, and other .NET programming languages. You will work with other members of the team in executing and completing projects. Responsible for exemplifying excellent customer service and the company core values, culture, policy and procedures at all times. Skill Requirements Bachelorrsquos Degree in Computer Science, Technology, or related field or equivalent combination of education and experience 2 - 5 years of work experience as a Software Engineer or Software Developer Experience with JavaScript frameworks (Angular, Vue) Experience with RESTful API (C, .NET Core) Experience developing AI driven chat bot solutions preferred Solid foundational knowledge of relational databases (SQL Server) Experience with test-driven development (TDD)  Essential Job Functions Build and support critical customer facing systems Utilize artificial intelligence to optimize business processes Drive the planning and implementation of projects Execute full software development life cycle (SDLC) using Agile methodology Write well-designed, testable code Maintain professionalism and integrity</body><cpc>0.22</cpc><CompanyLogo>https://assets.dice.com/external/images/empLogos/90642f88a6d92fdc7684fa1cda134925.png</CompanyLogo><HTMLDescription>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;&lt;html&gt;&lt;head&gt;&lt;/head&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Software Engineer is responsible numerous projects and using C#, JavaScript, Typescript, and other .NET programming languages. You will work with other members of the team in executing and completing projects. Responsible for exemplifying excellent customer service and the company core values, culture, policy and procedures at all times.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Skill Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s Degree in Computer Science, Technology, or related field or equivalent combination of education and experience&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;2 - 5 years of work experience as a Software Engineer or Software Developer&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with JavaScript frameworks (Angular, Vue)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with RESTful API (C#, .NET Core)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience developing AI driven chat bot solutions preferred&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Solid foundational knowledge of relational databases (SQL Server)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with test-driven development (TDD)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Essential Job Functions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Build and support critical customer facing systems&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Utilize artificial intelligence to optimize business processes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Drive the planning and implementation of projects&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Execute full software development life cycle (SDLC) using Agile methodology&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Write well-designed, testable code&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Maintain professionalism and integrity&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt; - provided by Dice</HTMLDescription></job>

<job><location>Atlanta, GA, United States</location><title>Cognos BI Developer</title><city>Atlanta</city><state>GA</state><zip>30318</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Contractor</job_type><posted_at>2020-10-07</posted_at><job_reference>6874_678bae8ec516700aa45db35987011df1</job_reference><company>PSR Associates, Inc.</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/5ii4ex7?cs=e3e&amp;jg=1jcf&amp;bid=TMQKNCFaov4fFLqS_v4dTg==</url><body>PSR Associates, Inc. is an IT consulting firm specializing in Staffing and Recruiting Services. People. Solutions. Results. Founded in 2003, PSR Associates, Inc. is headquartered in Atlanta, GA, with additional offices in Tampa, FL Washington, D.C. Charlotte, NC Austin, TX and Irvine, CA. Trusted, connected, experienced and fast, PSR Associates delivers the right talent to help leading companies perform at their best!  Cognos BI Developer Position Description   Our customer seeks a business intelligence developer to help support an environment using Cognos  other IBM products and to design, build  deliver BI solutions using Cognos Analytics 11. The developer will help track down and improve or eliminate bottlenecks in the BI reporting  ETL environment.   Impact  Influence This position will interact on a consistent basis with Other BI developers and analysts, project managers database administrators, customers, and department management.   Key Responsibilities Interpret user needs and design report format consistent with those needs. Identify and search databases and other sources as necessary to collect data required to produce reports. Organize source data in manner that facilitates data analysis and report production. Perform data analysis and produce reports. Confer with users regarding data needs. Perform other related duties as assigned. Support a business intelligence environment using Cognos  other IBM products Troubleshooting of report issues and performance issues that are critical Work with DBAs, report authors and system administrators to track down and improve or eliminate bottlenecks in the BI reporting  ETL environment To design, build  deliver BI solutions using Cognos Analytics 11.x Provide technical support to Cognos power users.  Specialized skills required for this job 2+ years of Cognos Report development experience 1 year with the latest version Cognos Analytics 11.x 2-3 years of experience with Framework Manager. Proficient with writing Oracle sqls. Troubleshooting of report issues and performance issues. Experience with building Dashboards and familiar with other BI tools like Tableau, Power BI. 3 yearsrsquo experience w C++ 3 yearsrsquo experience wJava</body><cpc>0.21</cpc><CompanyLogo>https://assets.dice.com/external/images/empLogos/bd1e7c17a861fef30bc280d80f2035b3.png</CompanyLogo><HTMLDescription>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;&lt;html&gt;&lt;head&gt;&lt;/head&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PSR Associates, Inc. is an IT consulting firm specializing in Staffing and Recruiting Services. People. Solutions. Results. Founded in 2003, PSR Associates, Inc. is headquartered in Atlanta, GA, with additional offices in Tampa, FL; Washington, D.C.; Charlotte, NC; Austin, TX; and Irvine, CA. Trusted, connected, experienced and fast, PSR Associates delivers the right talent to help leading companies perform at their best!&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cognos BI Developer Position Description&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;Our customer seeks a business intelligence developer to help support an environment using Cognos &amp;amp; other IBM products and to design, build &amp;amp; deliver BI solutions using Cognos Analytics 11. The developer will help track down and improve or eliminate bottlenecks in the BI reporting &amp;amp; ETL environment.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Impact &amp;amp; Influence:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This position will interact on a consistent basis with: Other BI developers and analysts, project managers database administrators, customers, and department management.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Interpret user needs and design report format consistent with those needs.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Identify and search databases and other sources as necessary to collect data required to produce reports.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Organize source data in manner that facilitates data analysis and report production.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Perform data analysis and produce reports.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Confer with users regarding data needs.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Perform other related duties as assigned.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Support a business intelligence environment using Cognos &amp;amp; other IBM products&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Troubleshooting of report issues and performance issues that are critical&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work with DBAs, report authors and system administrators to track down and improve or eliminate&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;bottlenecks in the BI reporting &amp;amp; ETL environment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;To design, build &amp;amp; deliver BI solutions using Cognos Analytics 11.x&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Provide technical support to Cognos power users.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specialized skills required for this job:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;2+ years of Cognos Report development experience&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1 year with the latest version Cognos Analytics 11.x&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;2-3 years of experience with Framework Manager.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Proficient with writing Oracle sqls.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Troubleshooting of report issues and performance issues.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with building Dashboards and familiar with other BI tools like Tableau, Power BI.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;3 years&amp;rsquo; experience w/ C++&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;3 years&amp;rsquo; experience w/Java&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt; - provided by Dice</HTMLDescription></job>

<job><location>Bethesda, MD, United States</location><title>Security Specialist</title><city>Bethesda</city><state>MD</state><zip>20810</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Full Time</job_type><posted_at>2020-10-03</posted_at><job_reference>6874_3a532d5f71548b4a1530f372576d413b</job_reference><company>S2Technologies, LLC</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/59mlabf?cs=e3e&amp;jg=1jcf&amp;bid=TMQKNCFaov4fFLqS_v4dTg==</url><body>S2Technologies is currently sourcing for qualified candidates to join our team. We are currently looking for candidates having training and experience performing as Security Specialist. Active Top Secret with SCI required and CI Poly preferred.  The qualified candidate shall perform the following tasksmiddot Provides security administrative support to the assigned Special Security Office.middot Assists in the review and coordination of DD254 Industrial Security requirements for CORs.middot Assists in the preparation and upload of security clearance packages on contractors and civilian federal employees in TITAN and PS3 databases.middot Assists in the monitoring of the progress of clearances through the security clearance and facility-access process and coordinates with SEC and partner agencies to submit monthly status checks.middot Relays requests for additional required information on processing candidates to COR and contracting companyrsquos Facility Security Officer (FSO), then forward received information back to DODIC CUSTOMER Security Staff for DIA Adjudication Branch.middot Assists in ensuring contractor personnel meet the clearance requirement for contracts or notifies COR of out-of-scope investigations.middot Informs CORs, contract Program Manager(s), and Government Points of Contact when a proposed contractor employee has been granted a security clearance.middot Assists in badging civilian, military and contractor personnel and with the in and out processing of personnel.middot Assists in providing security administrative advice and guidance in developing, presenting and devising resolution to office policy and procedures. These personnel may require Special Access Program (SAP) access.Required Knowledge, Skills and AbilitiesExperience middot At least five (5) years of security administrative support experience.-        - Experience working with JPAS, reviewing DD254s and reviewing security clearance paperwork is highly desired - At least five (5) years of experience with government security databases (e.g. JADE, Scattered Castles, JPAS)middot Training and experience working with SAPs.middot Experience with SCIF accreditations and inspections.middot Experience developing and implementing security training to meet SAP requirements.middot Experience performing GSSO or CPSO functions for government and contractor customersmiddot Special Program Security Certification (SPSC)middot Active TS with SCI eligibility requiredEducationTraining - High School Diploma required, Bachelorrsquos degree in a related field of study, DoD or Military service highly desired middot Completion of prerequisites for access to JPAS (PII Course) -Highly qualified candidates will have completed the CDSE Orientation to SAP Security Compliance Inspections (SA210.01) course. middot Completion of Instructor led Center for Development of Security Excellence (CDSE)middot Introduction to Special Access Programs Course (SA101.01) is highly desired.Certifications - NA S2Technologies is an equal opportunity employer. We celebrate diversity and are committed to creating an inclusive environment for all employees. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, or national origin.</body><cpc>0.21</cpc><CompanyLogo>https://assets.dice.com/external/images/empLogos/3184b6aa65f27f2a5b26ab01e0adb8aa.png</CompanyLogo><HTMLDescription>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;&lt;html&gt;&lt;head&gt;&lt;/head&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;S2Technologies is currently sourcing for qualified candidates to join our team. We are currently looking for candidates having training and experience performing as&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Security Specialist.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Active Top Secret with SCI required and CI Poly preferred.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The qualified candidate shall perform the following tasks:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;middot; Provides security administrative support to the assigned Special Security Office.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;middot; Assists in the review and coordination of DD254 Industrial Security requirements for CORs.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;middot; Assists in the preparation and upload of security clearance packages on contractors and civilian federal employees in TITAN and PS3 databases.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;middot; Assists in the monitoring of the progress of clearances through the security clearance and facility-access process and coordinates with SEC and partner agencies to submit monthly status checks.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;middot; Relays requests for additional required information on processing candidates to COR and contracting company&amp;rsquo;s Facility Security Officer (FSO), then forward received information back to DOD/IC CUSTOMER Security Staff for DIA Adjudication Branch.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;middot; Assists in ensuring contractor personnel meet the clearance requirement for contracts or notifies COR of out-of-scope investigations.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;middot; Informs CORs, contract Program Manager(s), and Government Points of Contact when a proposed contractor employee has been granted a security clearance.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;middot; Assists in badging civilian, military and contractor personnel and with the in and out processing of personnel.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;middot; Assists in providing security administrative advice and guidance in developing, presenting and devising resolution to office policy and procedures. These personnel may require Special Access Program (SAP) access.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Required Knowledge, Skills and Abilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;middot; At least five (5) years of security administrative support experience.-&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;- Experience working with JPAS, reviewing DD254s and reviewing security clearance paperwork is highly desired&lt;br /&gt;-&amp;nbsp;At least five (5) years of experience with government security databases (e.g. JADE, Scattered Castles, JPAS)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;middot; Training and experience working with SAPs.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;middot; Experience with SCIF accreditations and inspections.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;middot; Experience developing and implementing security training to meet SAP requirements.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;middot; Experience performing GSSO or CPSO functions for government and contractor customers&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;middot; Special Program Security Certification (SPSC)&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;middot; Active TS with SCI eligibility required&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education/Training&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- High School Diploma required, Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in a related field of study, DoD or Military service highly desired&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; Completion of prerequisites for access to JPAS (PII Course)&lt;br /&gt;-Highly qualified candidates will have completed the CDSE Orientation to SAP Security Compliance Inspections (SA210.01) course.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;middot; Completion of Instructor led Center for Development of Security Excellence (CDSE)&lt;div&gt;&amp;middot; Introduction to Special Access Programs Course (SA101.01) is highly desired.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Certifications -&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;N/A&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;S2Technologies is an equal opportunity employer. We celebrate diversity and are committed to creating an inclusive environment for all employees. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, or national origin.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt; - provided by Dice</HTMLDescription></job>

<job><location>, , United States</location><title>Direct Client Federal Govt Req:: Need UI/UX Developer 100 % REMOTE!!!!</title><city></city><state></state><zip></zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Full Time</job_type><posted_at>2020-10-06</posted_at><job_reference>6874_30c6af128de282ffa50764234b6ecf38</job_reference><company>RK Consultancy Services, Inc</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/5flmzdd?cs=e3e&amp;jg=1s8z&amp;bid=q4vrqYs61qv7kasNeA5Aeg==</url><body>Hi, We are a service provider to large government agencies, and I have a Federal agency in Washington DC looking to bring an Sr. LeadUIUX developer! RoleSr. Lead UIUX developer   Location Remote   Duration 3 to 4 Years Contract     Required Experience Experience developing with front-end JavaScript-based technologies Experience working with Web Worker API Combined experience working with IndexedDB API andor Web Storage API Experience building web applications that leverage RESTful APIs Experience working on web security for offline applications Experience working on UX design patterns for offline applications. Desired Skills Detail-oriented and excellent concentration ability An analytical mindset and critical thinking Demonstrable ability to discover and fix errors in code . Strong communication skills. Ability to work independently and in team settings         Experience working with the AgileScrum Methodology Responsible for application design, coding, testing, debugging, and documentation. Has full technical knowledge of all phases of web-based applications systems analysis and programming. Instructs, directs, and checks the work of other systems analysis and programming personnel. Responsible for quality assurance review    ROHIT KUMAR  RK CONSULTANCY SERVICES, INC. 3800 American Blvd W  Suite 1500  Minneapolis, MN 55431 Direct Fax  mailto  www.rkcs.com  httpwww.rkcs.com  Serving Twin Cities and surrounding area clients since 1998hellip MBE, NMSDC, DBE, SBA 8(A)      DISCLAIMERThis is not an unsolicited mail and if it is not intended for you or you are not interested in receiving our e-mails please reply with a &quot;REMOVE&quot; in the subject line or lsquoUNSCRIBErsquo and mention all the e-mail addresses to be removed with any e-mail addresses, which might be diverting the e-mails to you. We are extremely sorry if our email has caused any inconvenience to you.The information contained in this electronic message and any attachments to this message are intended for the exclusive use of the addressee(s) and may contain proprietary, confidential or privileged information. If you are not the intended recipient, you should not disseminate, distribute or copy this e-mail. Please notify the sender immediately and destroy all copies of this message and any attachments.</body><cpc>0.22</cpc><CompanyLogo>https://assets.dice.com/external/images/empLogos/1500141a44229fcc6610a5560158f0f6.jpg</CompanyLogo><HTMLDescription>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;&lt;html&gt;&lt;head&gt;&lt;/head&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are a service provider to large government agencies, and I have a Federal agency in Washington DC looking to bring an&lt;strong&gt; Sr. LeadUI/UX developer&lt;/strong&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Role:Sr. Lead UI/UX developer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location: Remote&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Duration: 3 to 4 Years Contract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Required Experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience developing with front-end JavaScript-based technologies&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience working with Web Worker API&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Combined experience working with IndexedDB API and/or Web Storage API&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience building web applications that leverage RESTful APIs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience working on web security for offline applications&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience working on UX design patterns for offline applications.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Desired Skills Detail-oriented and excellent concentration ability&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;An analytical mindset and critical thinking Demonstrable ability to discover and fix errors in code .&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ability to work independently and in team settings&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience working with the Agile/Scrum Methodology&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Responsible for application design, coding, testing, debugging, and documentation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Has full technical knowledge of all phases of web-based applications systems analysis and programming. Instructs, directs, and checks the work of other systems analysis and programming personnel.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Responsible for quality assurance review&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ROHIT KUMAR&amp;nbsp;|&amp;nbsp;RK CONSULTANCY SERVICES, INC.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;3800 American Blvd W | Suite 1500 | Minneapolis, MN 55431&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Direct| Fax|&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;|&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.rkcs.com/&quot;&gt;www.rkcs.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Serving Twin Cities and surrounding area clients since 1998&amp;hellip;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MBE,&amp;nbsp;NMSDC,&amp;nbsp;DBE,&amp;nbsp;SBA&amp;nbsp;8(A)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DISCLAIMER:This is not an unsolicited mail and if it is not intended for you or you are not interested in receiving our e-mails please reply with a &quot;REMOVE&quot; in the subject line or &amp;lsquo;UNSC====RIBE&amp;rsquo; and mention all the e-mail addresses to be removed with any e-mail addresses, which might be diverting the e-mails to you. We are extremely sorry if our email has caused any inconvenience to you.The information contained in this electronic message and any attachments to this message are intended for the exclusive use of the addressee(s) and may contain proprietary, confidential or privileged information. If you are not the intended recipient, you should not disseminate, distribute or copy this e-mail. Please notify the sender immediately and destroy all copies of this message and any attachments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt; - provided by Dice</HTMLDescription></job>

<job><location>Dayton, OH, United States</location><title>Healthcare Business Analyst / UAT Lead</title><city>Dayton</city><state>OH</state><zip>30301</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Contractor</job_type><posted_at>2020-10-06</posted_at><job_reference>6874_c79d8a918e3d106abfccf4e8fd8b9414</job_reference><company>Fortune Global Solutions, LLC</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/45niy1i?cs=e3e&amp;jg=2ou4&amp;bid=q4vrqYs61qv7kasNeA5Aeg==</url><body>Job Title     Product Owner  Business analyst (Healthcare)  Location    Dayton, OH  Duration    6+ Months   Must have Medicaid or Medicare or Marketplace   Product AnalysisValidation Lead Experience with product understanding, data management and analysis in a healthcaresbquo managed care, Medicaid policy or program space ndash all federalstate programs  market place plans ndash their operations  Firm understanding of the nuances of the Medicare care structure and the ability to apply this knowledgesbquo as it appliessbquo to analytic projects  Demonstrates effective translation and interpretation of healthcare payment policy regulations and related product requirements  Knowledge of validation required for all the product features ndash benefits, claims, enrolment, populations, risk etc.,  Develops, executes and maintains manual validation strategy, plan and test cases to validate MedicareMedicaid product ndash benefits, enrollment, claim editing and pricing according to the product specifications  Experience working with reports and insights that inform CMS regarding various products such as Medicare Advantage  Guide or perform monthly updates of key data sources from third parties, including Center for Medicare Services (CMS) and client Business Partner  Experience to assure compliance with Privacy Standards, Medicare Standards, BMS Standards and NCQA Standards Desired (nice to have)   FACETS Systems experience or working with X12 claims  Working knowledge of the CMS Star Rating System, including HEDIS, CAHPS, HOS, PDE, and Administrative Measures</body><cpc>0.22</cpc><CompanyLogo>https://assets.dice.com/external/images/empLogos/b064f7e8b877487c5c2a605efa0d11d5.png</CompanyLogo><HTMLDescription>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;&lt;html&gt;&lt;head&gt;&lt;/head&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Job Title:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Product Owner / Business analyst&amp;nbsp; (Healthcare)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Dayton, OH&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Duration:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 6+ Months&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Must have:&amp;nbsp; Medicaid or Medicare or Marketplace&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Product Analysis/Validation Lead&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Experience with product understanding, data management and analysis in a healthcare&amp;sbquo; managed care, Medicaid policy or program space &amp;ndash; all federal/state programs &amp;amp; market place plans &amp;ndash; their operations &lt;br /&gt;Firm understanding of the nuances of the Medicare care structure and the ability to apply this knowledge&amp;sbquo; as it applies&amp;sbquo; to analytic projects &lt;br /&gt;Demonstrates effective translation and interpretation of healthcare payment policy regulations and related product requirements &lt;br /&gt;Knowledge of validation required for all the product features &amp;ndash; benefits, claims, enrolment, populations, risk etc., &lt;br /&gt;Develops, executes and maintains manual validation strategy, plan and test cases to validate Medicare/Medicaid product &amp;ndash; benefits, enrollment, claim editing and pricing according to the product specifications &lt;br /&gt;Experience working with reports and insights that inform CMS regarding various products such as Medicare Advantage &lt;br /&gt;Guide or perform monthly updates of key data sources from third parties, including Center for Medicare Services (CMS) and client Business Partner &lt;br /&gt;Experience to assure compliance with Privacy Standards, Medicare Standards, BMS Standards and NCQA Standards&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Desired (nice to have) :&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FACETS Systems experience or working with X12 claims &lt;br /&gt;Working knowledge of the CMS Star Rating System, including HEDIS, CAHPS, HOS, PDE, and Administrative Measures&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt; - provided by Dice</HTMLDescription></job>

<job><location>Dallas, TX, United States</location><title>Java - (PERM) - Java Kafka- Real-Time Streaming (1) - DAL/CHI</title><city>Dallas</city><state>TX</state><zip>75201</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Full Time</job_type><posted_at>2020-10-05</posted_at><job_reference>6874_13f3065a64c9ba118a66caa79ae1c570</job_reference><company>Addison Group</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/56r1s9e?cs=e3e&amp;jg=1jcf&amp;bid=TMQKNCFaov4fFLqS_v4dTg==</url><body>Senior Java Engineer with Big DataReal Time Stream Technologies Relocation and Visa Sponsorship available to Dallas Base Salary 140-160K + Bonus   Our client will sponsor H1B Visarsquos for the ideal candidate that demonstrates the right leadership skills, mentorship and has the right ldquocan-dordquo attitude. Here are the technical requirements Core Java 8+  Data Structure, Streaming, Lambda, JVM Performance OOO Concepts REST ndash Must have OAuth2 Security, Various return codes, Gateway Kafka ndash Performance Tuning for high throughput Big Data  Real Time Streaming Data Frameworks Any ndash MapReduce, Apache Spark, Kafka Streams, Apache Flink Testing (Junit) TDD, Experience writing Unit and Integration tests CICD ndash Gradle, Terraform, Ansible, Jenkins, Kubernetes, Helm Cloud ndash Docker, Kubernetes, microservices, security implications    This project is a Greenfield development event that will put the right candidate with other strong developers that love to learn, collaborate and have spirited discussions about the best course of action to make their product the best.</body><cpc>0.21</cpc><CompanyLogo>https://assets.dice.com/external/images/empLogos/7fe63d02187f8fb8ad1aa3554dfdc504.jpg</CompanyLogo><HTMLDescription>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;&lt;html&gt;&lt;head&gt;&lt;/head&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;p&gt;Senior Java Engineer with Big Data/Real Time Stream Technologies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Relocation and Visa Sponsorship available to Dallas&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Base Salary:&amp;nbsp; $140-160K + Bonus&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our client will sponsor H1B Visa&amp;rsquo;s for the ideal candidate that demonstrates the right leadership skills, mentorship and has the right &amp;ldquo;can-do&amp;rdquo; attitude.&amp;nbsp; Here are the technical requirements:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Core Java 8+ = Data Structure, Streaming, Lambda, JVM Performance&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;OOO Concepts&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;REST &amp;ndash; Must have OAuth2 Security, Various return codes, Gateway&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Kafka &amp;ndash; Performance Tuning for high throughput&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Big Data / Real Time Streaming Data Frameworks:&amp;nbsp; Any &amp;ndash; MapReduce, Apache Spark, Kafka Streams, Apache Flink&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Testing (Junit):&amp;nbsp; TDD, Experience writing Unit and Integration tests&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;CI/CD &amp;ndash; Gradle, Terraform, Ansible, Jenkins, Kubernetes, Helm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cloud &amp;ndash; Docker, Kubernetes, microservices, security implications&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This project is a Greenfield development event that will put the right candidate with other strong developers that love to learn, collaborate and have spirited discussions about the best course of action to make their product the best.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt; - provided by Dice</HTMLDescription></job>

<job><location>Montreal, QC, Canada</location><title>Sr. Web Services Developer needed for a 6+ Month Contract in Montreal, QC</title><city>Montreal</city><state>QC</state><zip>H4K 2B3</zip><country>Canada</country><job_type>Contractor</job_type><posted_at>2020-10-06</posted_at><job_reference>6874_94de42df42d10feb43332b346d9b611f</job_reference><company>Sullivan and Cogliano</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/5aqsuty?cs=e3e&amp;jg=2ou4&amp;bid=q4vrqYs61qv7kasNeA5Aeg==</url><body>Sr. Web Services Developer needed for a 6+ Month Contract in Montreal, QC! Candidates must live in Canada and be fluent in French and English! More specifically His tasks consist of developing, TUs and deploying web services. 5 to 10 years of experience  Recognized experience in Web development with the following technologies Experience within a project that has developed reusable components in a &quot;single-page&quot; type application Experience working in an Agile team (Scrum  Kanban) Good understanding of the software lifecycle (SDLC) Good understanding of the tools of the Atlassian suite (Jira, Bitbucket and Confluence) Very good experience with TypeScript, rxjs, ngrx, jest and Angular 8+ Very good experience in back-end Java development (REST, Spring Boot, Apache CXF, Microservices, SOAP, etc.) Experience in the development of wealth management applications Experience in DevOps tools such as Jenkins and Urban code, large Asset. Understanding of ldquocontainerizationrdquo technologies (Docker, Kubernetes, OpenShift), an asset Leadership, initiative, ability to carry out multiple tasks simultaneously and a strong team spirit. Bilingual English (45)  French (45) - Conversations are in French. Given the current situation regarding the coronavirus, it will be 100 telework until further notice. In normal times, the station offers the possibility of teleworking according to the needs of the project.   Sr. Web Services Developer ndash Contrat de 6 mois+ ndash Montreacuteal, QC Plus preacuteciseacutement  Ses tacircches consistent agrave deacutevelopper des tus et agrave deacuteployer des services Web. 5 agrave 10 ans drsquoexpeacuterience Expeacuterience reconnue dans le deacuteveloppement web avec les technologies suivantes  Expeacuterience dans un projet qui a deacuteveloppeacute des composants reacuteutilisables dans une application de type laquo page unique raquo Expeacuterience de travail dans une eacutequipe Agile (Scrum  Kanban) Bonne compreacutehension du cycle de vie du logiciel (SDLC) Bonne compreacutehension des outils de la suite Atlassian (Jira, Bitbucket et Confluence) Tregraves bonne expeacuterience avec TypeScript, rxjs, ngrx, jest et Angular 8+ Tregraves bonne expeacuterience dans le deacuteveloppement java back-end (REST, Spring Boot, Apache CXF, Microservices, SOAP, etc.) Expeacuterience dans le deacuteveloppement drsquoapplications de gestion de patrimoine Expeacuterience dans les outils DevOps tels que Jenkins et Urban code, grand Actif. Comprendre les technologies de laquo conteneurisation raquo (Docker, Kubernetes, OpenShift), un atout Leadership, initiative, capaciteacute agrave accomplir plusieurs tacircches simultaneacutement et un fort esprit drsquoeacutequipe. Anglais bilingue (45)  Franccedilais (45) - Les conversations sont en Franccedilais. Compte tenu de la situation actuelle concernant le coronavirus, il sera 100 teacuteleacutetravail jusqursquoagrave nouvel ordre. En temps normal, la station offre la possibiliteacute de teacuteleacutetravailler en fonction des besoins du projet. Le candidat DOIT vivre au Canada</body><cpc>0.22</cpc><CompanyLogo>https://assets.dice.com/external/images/empLogos/99cf75a2db5981a564c1588f07a69faa.png</CompanyLogo><HTMLDescription>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;&lt;html&gt;&lt;head&gt;&lt;/head&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sr. Web Services Developer needed for a 6+ Month Contract in Montreal, QC!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Candidates must live in Canada and be fluent in French and English!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More specifically:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;His tasks consist of developing, TUs and deploying web services. 5 to 10 years of experience&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recognized experience in Web development with the following technologies:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience within a project that has developed reusable components in a &quot;single-page&quot; type application&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience working in an Agile team (Scrum / Kanban)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Good understanding of the software lifecycle (SDLC)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Good understanding of the tools of the Atlassian suite (Jira, Bitbucket and Confluence)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Very good experience with TypeScript, rxjs, ngrx, jest and Angular 8+&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Very good experience in back-end Java development (REST, Spring Boot, Apache CXF, Microservices, SOAP, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience in the development of wealth management applications&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience in DevOps tools such as Jenkins and Urban code, large Asset.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Understanding of &amp;ldquo;containerization&amp;rdquo; technologies (Docker, Kubernetes, OpenShift), an asset&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leadership, initiative, ability to carry out multiple tasks simultaneously and a strong team spirit.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bilingual English (4/5) / French (4/5) - Conversations are in French.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Given the current situation regarding the coronavirus, it will be 100% telework until further notice. In normal times, the station offers the possibility of teleworking according to the needs of the project.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;_______________________________________&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sr. Web Services Developer &amp;ndash; Contrat de 6 mois+ &amp;ndash; Montr&amp;eacute;al, QC&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Plus pr&amp;eacute;cis&amp;eacute;ment :&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ses t&amp;acirc;ches consistent &amp;agrave; d&amp;eacute;velopper des tus et &amp;agrave; d&amp;eacute;ployer des services Web. 5 &amp;agrave; 10 ans d&amp;rsquo;exp&amp;eacute;rience&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Exp&amp;eacute;rience reconnue dans le d&amp;eacute;veloppement web avec les technologies suivantes :&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Exp&amp;eacute;rience dans un projet qui a d&amp;eacute;velopp&amp;eacute; des composants r&amp;eacute;utilisables dans une application de type &amp;laquo; page unique &amp;raquo;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Exp&amp;eacute;rience de travail dans une &amp;eacute;quipe Agile (Scrum / Kanban)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bonne compr&amp;eacute;hension du cycle de vie du logiciel (SDLC)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bonne compr&amp;eacute;hension des outils de la suite Atlassian (Jira, Bitbucket et Confluence)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tr&amp;egrave;s bonne exp&amp;eacute;rience avec TypeScript, rxjs, ngrx, jest et Angular 8+&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tr&amp;egrave;s bonne exp&amp;eacute;rience dans le d&amp;eacute;veloppement java back-end (REST, Spring Boot, Apache CXF, Microservices, SOAP, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Exp&amp;eacute;rience dans le d&amp;eacute;veloppement d&amp;rsquo;applications de gestion de patrimoine&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Exp&amp;eacute;rience dans les outils DevOps tels que Jenkins et Urban code, grand Actif.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Comprendre les technologies de &amp;laquo; conteneurisation &amp;raquo; (Docker, Kubernetes, OpenShift), un atout&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leadership, initiative, capacit&amp;eacute; &amp;agrave; accomplir plusieurs t&amp;acirc;ches simultan&amp;eacute;ment et un fort esprit d&amp;rsquo;&amp;eacute;quipe.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Anglais bilingue (4/5) / Fran&amp;ccedil;ais (4/5) - Les conversations sont en Fran&amp;ccedil;ais.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Compte tenu de la situation actuelle concernant le coronavirus, il sera 100% t&amp;eacute;l&amp;eacute;travail jusqu&amp;rsquo;&amp;agrave; nouvel ordre. En temps normal, la station offre la possibilit&amp;eacute; de t&amp;eacute;l&amp;eacute;travailler en fonction des besoins du projet.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Le candidat DOIT vivre au Canada&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt; - provided by Dice</HTMLDescription></job>


<job><location>Charlotte, NC, United States</location><title>UX Designer (2D, 3D &amp; VR Experience)</title><city>Charlotte</city><state>NC</state><zip>28201</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Full Time</job_type><posted_at>2020-10-05</posted_at><job_reference>6874_6b8dcfd81ce3c2290a20865f71f7549c</job_reference><company>BSI Solutions</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/5g1f3gm?cs=e3e&amp;jg=2ou4&amp;bid=q4vrqYs61qv7kasNeA5Aeg==</url><body>WHO WE ARE   BSI Solutions, Inc. is a globally recognized innovative focused software company that specializes in partnering with corporations to digitally transform their operations through innovation. We believe in fostering a collaborative working environment with a family-oriented culture that provides exceptional leadership and growth opportunities. If you are interested in joining our family here at BSI Solutions, check out all of the many opportunities we have available and apply!   POSITION SUMMARY   We are looking for a 3DVR UX Designer to design software and platforms that meet peoplersquos needs. You will combine interfaces and workflows to enhance user experience. In this role, you should be an analytical and creative designer who is able to grasp user needs and solve complex problems. You should have strong understanding of user experience design principles and systematic design rationale, 3D interactive development experience, knowledge of prototyping tools like Unity or Unreal, and attention to detail. To be considered, you must provide a portfolio displaying your work in Digital Experience  creating digital experiences across web, mobile, ARVR, voice, gesture, IoT, and video.   WHAT YOUrsquoLL DO   Understand product specifications and user psychology  Conduct concept and usability testing and gather feedback  Create personas through user research and data   Define the right interaction model and evaluate its success  Develop wireframes and prototypes around customer needs  Find creative ways to solve UX problems (e.g. usability, findability)  Work with Software Engineers to implement modernize and state of the art designs   Communicate design ideas and prototypes to developers   Keep abreast of competitor products and industry trends  Gather design requirements from customerclients and successfully transform into a successful product     SKILLSQUALIFICATIONS NEEDED TO SUCCEED   BSc in Design, Computer Science, or a related field (or HCI)  3-5 years of UXUI experience, with experience in mobile and virtual and augmented reality design as well as motion design Strong portfolio of design projects (Required)  Familiarity with interaction design and information architecture  Proficient in design software (e.g. UXPin, Balsamiq, Adobe, Proto.io, etc.)  Knowledge of JavaScript or Angular   Problem-solving aptitude  Analytical mind with a business acumen  Excellent communication skills  Proven ability to deliver results on-time   Familiarity with operating in a Scrum environment       BSI Solutions, Inc. is proud to be an Equal Employment Opportunity and affirmative action employer. We celebrate diversity and do not discriminate based on race, religion, color, national origin, sex, sexual orientation, age, veteran status, disability status, or any other applicable characteristics protected by law.      Get the word out!Get a trackable link to share anywhere.Get Job LinkLocation Charlotte, North CarolinaDepartment InnovationEmployment Type Full-TimeMinimum Experience Entry-levelCompensation 34.00-38.00 per hourlaquoHide Full Job Description</body><cpc>0.22</cpc><CompanyLogo>https://assets.dice.com/external/images/empLogos/55a07297954b6ba79c26cfde5be9e4bd.jpg</CompanyLogo><HTMLDescription>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;&lt;html&gt;&lt;head&gt;&lt;/head&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;jobDetailsDescription&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;jobDetailsDescriptionGroup jobDetailsDescriptionGroup--expanded jobDetailsDescriptionGroup-enter-done&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;jobDetailsDescriptionGroupColumn&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;jobDetailsDescriptionText jobDetailsDescriptionText--expanded&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;BambooRichText&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHO WE ARE:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;BSI Solutions, Inc. is a globally recognized innovative focused software company; that specializes in partnering with corporations to digitally transform their operations through innovation.&amp;nbsp; We believe in fostering a collaborative working environment with a family-oriented culture that provides exceptional leadership and growth opportunities.&amp;nbsp; If you are interested in joining our family here at BSI Solutions, check out all of the many opportunities we have available and apply!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;POSITION SUMMARY:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a 3D/VR UX Designer to design software and platforms that meet people&amp;rsquo;s needs. You will combine interfaces and workflows to enhance user experience. In this role, you should be an analytical and creative designer who is able to grasp user needs and solve complex problems. You should have&amp;nbsp;strong understanding of user experience design principles and systematic design rationale, 3D interactive development experience, knowledge of prototyping tools like Unity or Unreal, and attention to detail.&amp;nbsp;To be considered, you must provide a portfolio displaying your work in&amp;nbsp;Digital Experience | creating digital experiences across web, mobile, AR/VR, voice, gesture, IoT, and video.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHAT YOU&amp;rsquo;LL DO:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Understand product specifications and user psychology&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Conduct concept and usability testing and gather feedback&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Create personas through user research and data&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Define the right interaction model and evaluate its success&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Develop wireframes and prototypes around customer needs&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Find creative ways to solve UX problems (e.g. usability, findability)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work with Software Engineers to implement modernize and state of the art designs&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Communicate design ideas and prototypes to developers&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Keep abreast of competitor products and industry trends&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gather design requirements from customer/clients and successfully transform into a successful product&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SKILLS/QUALIFICATIONS NEEDED TO SUCCEED:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;BSc in Design, Computer Science, or a related field&amp;nbsp;(or HCI)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;3-5 years of UX/UI experience, with experience in mobile and virtual and augmented reality design as well as motion design&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong portfolio of design projects&amp;nbsp;(Required)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with interaction design and information architecture&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Proficient in design software (e.g. UXPin, Balsamiq, Adobe, Proto.io, etc.)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of JavaScript or Angular&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Problem-solving aptitude&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Analytical mind with a business acumen&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Proven ability to deliver results on-time&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with operating in a Scrum environment&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;BSI Solutions, Inc. is proud to be an Equal Employment Opportunity and affirmative action employer. We celebrate diversity and do not discriminate based on race, religion, color, national origin, sex, sexual orientation, age, veteran status, disability status, or any other applicable characteristics protected by law.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;jobDetailsDescriptionRightColumn jobDetailsDescriptionRightColumn--expanded jobDetailsDescriptionRightColumn-enter-done&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;jobDetailsDescription__column&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;jobDetailsDescription__sharing &quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;jobDetailsDescription__sharingIcon&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;jobDetailsDescription__sharin====ontent&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;jobDetailsDescription__sharin====ontentTitle&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get the word out!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;jobDetailsDescription__sharin====ontentSubTitle&quot;&gt;Get a trackable link to share anywhere.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;jobDetailsDescription__sharin====ontentIcons&quot;&gt;&lt;button class=&quot;fab-Button fab-Button--secondary fab-Button--outline&quot; tabindex=&quot;0&quot; type=&quot;submit&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;fab-Button__text&quot;&gt;Get Job Link&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;button class=&quot;fab-Button fab-Button--iconOnly fab-Button--secondary fab-Button--outline&quot; tabindex=&quot;0&quot; type=&quot;submit&quot;&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;button class=&quot;fab-Button fab-Button--iconOnly fab-Button--secondary fab-Button--outline&quot; tabindex=&quot;0&quot; type=&quot;submit&quot;&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;button class=&quot;fab-Button fab-Button--iconOnly fab-Button--secondary fab-Button--outline&quot; tabindex=&quot;0&quot; type=&quot;submit&quot;&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;jobDetailsDescription__details&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;jobDetailsDescription__detail&quot;&gt;&lt;label class=&quot;fab-Label&quot; for=&quot;location&quot;&gt;Location&lt;/label&gt;&lt;p id=&quot;location&quot;&gt;Charlotte, North Carolina&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;jobDetailsDescription__detail&quot;&gt;&lt;label class=&quot;fab-Label&quot; for=&quot;department&quot;&gt;Department&lt;/label&gt;&lt;p id=&quot;department&quot;&gt;Innovation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;jobDetailsDescription__detail&quot;&gt;&lt;label class=&quot;fab-Label&quot; for=&quot;employmentType&quot;&gt;Employment Type&lt;/label&gt;&lt;p id=&quot;employmentType&quot;&gt;Full-Time&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;jobDetailsDescription__detail&quot;&gt;&lt;label class=&quot;fab-Label&quot; for=&quot;experienceLevel&quot;&gt;Minimum Experience&lt;/label&gt;&lt;p id=&quot;experienceLevel&quot;&gt;Entry-level&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;jobDetailsDescription__detail&quot;&gt;&lt;label class=&quot;fab-Label&quot; for=&quot;compensation&quot;&gt;Compensation&lt;/label&gt;&lt;p id=&quot;compensation&quot;&gt;$34.00-$38.00 per hour&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;jobDetailsDescription__toggle&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;jobDetailsDescription__toggle--&amp;laquo; jobDetailsDescription__toggle--up&quot;&gt;&amp;laquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;button class=&quot;fab-TextButton fab-TextButton--small fab-link&quot; tabindex=&quot;0&quot; type=&quot;submit&quot;&gt;Hide Full Job Description&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt; - provided by Dice</HTMLDescription></job>

</jobs><generation_time>2020-10-07 03:35:07 -0400</generation_time><jobs_count>98454</jobs_count></source>