<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jobs xmlns="http://joblookup.com/XMLSchema"
      xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
      xsi:schemaLocation="http://joblookup.com/XMLSchema
      http://joblookup.com/XMLSchemaPartner.xsd">
<job price="0.08">
	<price><![CDATA[0.08]]></price>
	<id><![CDATA[1456]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[http://joblookup.com/uk/dispatch/job/feed/carpenter?utm_source=feed-2&utm_medium=PostJobFree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[Carpenter]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[CSCS Carpenter, carpenter, Construction, Daniel OwenCSCS carpenter required for a large nationwide construction company that specialises in commercial projects.<br><br>Our client is looking for experienced and hardworking Labourers to join a project based in Stamford PE9.This labouring contract is long term with working hours starting from 7:30am.<br><br>Minimum 9 hours but can be long as well and the option to work weekends.Daily responsibilities for the successful Labourers will include:Clearing siteAssisting with general labouring work Requirements for the roleA valid cscs cardThe ability to perform physical manual labourOwn PPE If you feel you would be well<br>- suited for this position please apply, or contact for more information on 0207 593 1660<br>- Emilytags: Carpenter, CSCS, Lowestoft, CONSTRUCTION, BUILDING OPERATIVE, OPERATIVE, WAREHOUSE OPERATIVEREG123]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[Eastern]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[Suffolk]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[Lowestoft]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[Lowestoft]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[NR32]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[permanent]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[full-time]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[Daniel Owen Ltd]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[http://joblookup.com/img/recruiters/36/3640cb2_467.png]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[]]></expiration-date>
	<creation-date><![CDATA[2019-08-22]]></creation-date>
</job>
<job price="0.08">
	<price><![CDATA[0.08]]></price>
	<id><![CDATA[1617]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[http://joblookup.com/uk/dispatch/job/feed/digital-learning-specialist?utm_source=feed-2&utm_medium=PostJobFree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[Digital Learning Specialist]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[Digital Learning Specialist<br>- c£28k<br>- Dudley/TiptonThis is an exciting "blank canvas" role working with a well established national organisation.<br><br>As their first ever in-house Digital Learning Specialist you will be taking a key and lead role as they look to modernise and digitise the way that they engage with their people (at all levels) to deliver learning solutions.<br><br>You will be responsible for:Reviewing the training already delivered (mandatory, soft skills and management development) and advising on where and how it can be improved using digital solutions.Creating exciting and modern training materials.Delivering creative and effective learning through e-learning, podcast, vlogs.Working with colleagues in the HR team to implement an LMS.You must be:A confident communicator able to advise on the technology available to in-house learning professionals, internal Subject Matter Experts and operational stakeholders.Adept at using tools like Adobe Captivate, Compose, Simulate and HTML.Resilient with the patience and tenacity to drive change in a sometimes traditional organisation.It is not essential that you have a learning background as you will find support and development from L&amp;D and HR peers in this area however it will be a challenging role where you can use your digital experience to make a real difference to the organisation.<br><br>Over the next few years they are looking to totally transform the way that they deliver training and you will play a key part in that.<br><br>It could be a career defining role.<br><br>Salary: c£28k + benefits (which will include the chance to work from home and with a good work:life balance) We are keen to receive CV's via this advert in the first instance.<br><br>However should you require more information than the advert provides you can call Diana Sharp at Wright Solutions on 0121 222 5599 (Please quote ref BBBH91 in any correspondence)In compliance with the regulations (April 2004) in place under the Employment Agencies Act, Wright Solutions will require proof of identification.<br><br>A current copy of a passport, driving licence, ID card or NI card will be required as part of the registration process.<br><br>Email and faxed copies are acceptable Did you know we also provide online training courses for a better workplace.<br><br>Video-based training for inclusion, leadership and teamwork.<br><br>Find out more here]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[West Midlands]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[West Midlands]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[Dudley]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[Dudley]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[DY1]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[28000.00]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[29000.00]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[annum]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[Wright Solutions]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[http://joblookup.com/img/recruiters/88/880066f_275.png]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[]]></expiration-date>
	<creation-date><![CDATA[2019-08-22]]></creation-date>
</job>
<job price="0.08">
	<price><![CDATA[0.08]]></price>
	<id><![CDATA[1626]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[http://joblookup.com/uk/dispatch/job/feed/carpenter-2?utm_source=feed-2&utm_medium=PostJobFree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[Carpenter]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[CSCS Carpenter, Carpenter, Construction, Daniel OwenCSCS Carpenter required for a large nationwide construction company that specialises in commercial projects.<br><br>Our client is looking for experienced and hardworking Labourers to join a project based in Stamford PE9.This labouring contract is long term with working hours starting from 7:30am.<br><br>Minimum 9 hours but can be long as well and the option to work weekends.Daily responsibilities for the successful Labourers will include:Clearing siteAssisting with general carpenter jobsRequirements for the roleA valid cscs cardThe ability to perform physical manual labourOwn PPE If you feel you would be well<br>- suited for this position please apply, or contact for more information on 0207 593 1660<br>- Joetags: Carpenter, CSCS, Great yarmouth, CONSTRUCTION, BUILDING OPERATIVE, OPERATIVE, WAREHOUSE OPERATIVEREG123]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[Eastern]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[Norfolk]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[Great Yarmouth]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[Great Yarmouth]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[NR30]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[temporary]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[full-time]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[Daniel Owen Ltd]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[http://joblookup.com/img/recruiters/36/3640cb2_467.png]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[]]></expiration-date>
	<creation-date><![CDATA[2019-08-22]]></creation-date>
</job>
<job price="0.08">
	<price><![CDATA[0.08]]></price>
	<id><![CDATA[1685]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[http://joblookup.com/uk/dispatch/job/feed/labourer-2?utm_source=feed-2&utm_medium=PostJobFree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[Labourer]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[CSCS, Construction, Daniel OwenCSCS labourers required for a large nationwide construction company that specialises in commercial projects.<br><br>Our client is looking for experienced and hardworking Labourers to join a project based in London.<br><br>The site is within the city and is accessible by public transport.This labouring contract is long term with working hours starting from 7:30am.<br><br>Working hours will be between 8-12 hours a day can be long as well and the option to work weekends.Daily responsibilities for the successful Labourers will include:Clearing siteAssisting with general labouring work Requirements for the roleA valid cscs cardThe ability to perform physical manual labourOwn PPE If you feel you would be well<br>- suited for this position please apply, or contact for more information on 0207 593 1660<br>- DylanLON123]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[London]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[City of London]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[London]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[London]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[EC1A]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[11.00]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[12.00]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[hour]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[permanent]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[full-time]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[Daniel Owen Ltd]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[http://joblookup.com/img/recruiters/36/3640cb2_467.png]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[]]></expiration-date>
	<creation-date><![CDATA[2019-08-22]]></creation-date>
</job>
<job price="0.08">
	<price><![CDATA[0.08]]></price>
	<id><![CDATA[10456]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[http://joblookup.com/uk/dispatch/job/feed/working-foreman?utm_source=feed-2&utm_medium=PostJobFree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[Working Foreman]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[Working Foreman Your new company Mountjoy Ltd has been awarded a contract to provide Reactive Maintenance and PPM to buildings in the Horsham area.<br><br>The Contract for Horsham District Council encompasses 156 properties of which 65 are temporary housing.<br><br>The remaining properties consist of offices, commercial buildings, libraries, museums, parks, car parks, public toilets etc.<br><br>Your new role We are seeking a conscientious, enthusiastic and experienced working foreman with a can-do attitude and can-do approach.<br><br>Applicants must have a technical background in a Hard FM environment as an Electrical or Mechanical Technician or Foreman.<br><br>The working Foreman must maintain a professional appearance and attitude and be polite and courteous at all times.<br><br>It is a further requirement that all contract employees must pass a Disclosure and Barring Service (DBS) check.<br><br>Our aim is to maintain high client satisfaction through delivery of maintenance and repairs services ensuring a controlled and safe environment whilst working effectively and in a timely manner and balancing constantly changing priorities.<br><br>This attention to detail and ensuring that we conclude our work, with the right first-time approach in order to maximise and enhance our reputation with our client, is paramount to the success of the contract.<br><br>What you'll need to succeed You will have 3+ years' experience working in a Property Maintenance environment completing reactive and PPM tasks, your main trade will be as an electrical or mechanical technician.<br><br>You will have a technical background in a Hard FM environment as an Engineer or Foreman.<br><br>You will be the technical expert for associated works, providing efficient and effective solutions where required.<br><br>The successful candidate will be able to support and coach a team in the achievement of the standards and quality we are striving for and possess interpersonal skills and the ability to communicate at all levels in a professional and courteous, whilst accepting challenges from colleagues, tenants and our client.<br><br>You will be able to apply a practical approach and solutions to Health &amp; Safety.<br><br>You will be proficient in MS Office, particularly excel, to an intermediate level and be able to understand how Mountjoy's FES system interacts with other systems.<br><br>You will be a team player by understanding what it is to be part of a team sharing experiences and learning.<br><br>What you'll get in return You will receive an annual salary of £40,000<br>- £42,000, a company van, 23 days holiday, Life Assurance, Cycle to work scheme, Childcare Voucher scheme, Company Pension, Buy &amp; Sell Holiday.<br><br>You will also have access to several other benefits that the company offers to its staff.<br><br>What you need to do now If you're interested in this role, click 'apply now' to forward an up-to-date copy of your CV, or call us now.<br><br>Hays Specialist Recruitment Limited acts as an employment agency for permanent recruitment and employment business for the supply of temporary workers.<br><br>By applying for this job you accept the T&amp;C's, Privacy Policy and Disclaimers which can be found at hays.co.uk]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[South East]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[West Sussex]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[West Durrington]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[West Sussex]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[BN13]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[40000.00]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[42000.00]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[annum]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[Hays Recruitment]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[]]></expiration-date>
	<creation-date><![CDATA[2019-08-22]]></creation-date>
</job>
<job price="0.08">
	<price><![CDATA[0.08]]></price>
	<id><![CDATA[11486]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[http://joblookup.com/uk/dispatch/job/feed/payroll-manager-south-cambridge?utm_source=feed-2&utm_medium=PostJobFree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[Payroll Manager - South Cambridge - £35,000]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[Payroll Manager – South Cambridge<br>- £30-35K + benefits A leading South Cambridge-based organisation are seeking the services of a 1st class, experienced Payroll Administrator to join their busy team.<br><br>Key responsibilities Working in a sole capacity as the 'head of' the payroll function.<br><br>Processing end to end client payroll using your own initiative.<br><br>Manage your own portfolio of complex clients.<br><br>Statutory payments<br>- Statutory Sick Pay, Statutory Maternity Pay, PAYE and National Insurance etc.<br><br>Processing of Year End procedures.<br><br>Provide 1st line support for payroll queries.<br><br>Liaise with HMRC when required.<br><br>Process Tax Code changes.<br><br>Manual calculations.<br><br>Qualifications: 2-3 years' experience working in a busy payroll function.<br><br>Grade C and above at GCSE English &amp; Maths.<br><br>CIPP qualified (desirable).<br><br>Ability to work on own initiative, working within a team and the ability to meet deadlines.<br><br>Excellent organisation skills with the ability to multi-task.<br><br>If you are a motivated Payroll professional looking for your next opportunity to join a successful firm, working in a sole who invest in their people and promote within, please don't hesitate to apply now!]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[Eastern]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[Cambridgeshire]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[Cambridge]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[Cambridgeshire]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[CB2]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[30000.00]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[35000.00]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[annum]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[full-time]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[James Gray Associates Ltd]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[]]></expiration-date>
	<creation-date><![CDATA[2019-08-22]]></creation-date>
</job>
<job price="0.08">
	<price><![CDATA[0.08]]></price>
	<id><![CDATA[15363]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[http://joblookup.com/uk/dispatch/job/feed/account-managersenior-account-manager?utm_source=feed-2&utm_medium=PostJobFree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[Account Manager/Senior Account Manager]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[Calling all Account Managers and Senior Account Managers! I'm working on a fantastic opportunity to join a market leading Oxfordshire based agency working with some high profile clients, this agency are at their peak and are looking to expand their team of talented individuals.<br><br>This agency have a national office network and work with some market leading clients across a variety of sectors with some fabulous high profile names.<br><br>Within this role you'd be working as an integral part of the team and the agency offer some brilliant benefits including a really flexible holiday policy, pension, health care, socials and fitness clubs.<br><br>This role is hugely varied, no two days are the same and there are times when it's VERY busy, but they have a great culture and environment where everyone mucks in and achieving goals is a real team effort, they offer great flexibility and some brilliant perks in return and hard work is recognised and rewarded.<br><br>Key responsibilities: Managing a portfolio of clients with the support of an Account Executive Scheduling work internally, ensuring deadlines are always met Managing budgets and forecasting Attending client meetings Working strategically with your clients to ensure you are providing the very best for them They are looking for a candidate who has: Experience within fast paced agency environment A real passion for agency life and a great work ethic The ability to work under pressure and thrive in a busy environment This is a fantastic opportunity to join an award winning integrated agency who are on the lookout to continue to grow to manage their amazing client wins! The role would suit an Account Manager or Senior Account Manager who are looking to join a top notch agency based in a lovely office space! They're based in North Oxfordshire, easily commutable by train (a couple of minutes' walk from the station) and by car from across Oxfordshire, Northamptonshire and South Warwickshire<br>- Banbury, Oxford, Milton Keynes, The Cotswolds, Aylesbury, Daventry, Bicester, Northampton.<br><br>This really is a fab opportunity<br>- if you think this could be the role for you and would like to know more or have a confidential chat, please send through your CV today! Account Manager/Senior Account Manager, Integrated Agency, North Oxfordshire, £25,000<br>- £35,000]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[South East]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[Oxfordshire]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[Oxford]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[Oxfordshire]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[OX1]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[25000.00]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[35000.00]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[annum]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[Blue Skies Marketing Recruitment]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[]]></expiration-date>
	<creation-date><![CDATA[2019-08-22]]></creation-date>
</job>
<job price="0.08">
	<price><![CDATA[0.08]]></price>
	<id><![CDATA[16067]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[http://joblookup.com/uk/dispatch/job/feed/maintenance-engineer-field-service-engineer-1?utm_source=feed-2&utm_medium=PostJobFree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[Maintenance Engineer / Field Service Engineer]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[Job Title: Maintenance Engineer Location : Field Based covering London and surrounding area Salary : £35,000<br>- £40,000 + bonus per annum + van Job Type: Full Time, Permanent The Company is a leading provider of natural and smoke ventilation systems to business and local authority customers across the UK since 1988.<br><br>Job Role: As a Maintenance Engineer working remotely, you will be required to deliver a professional and efficient service in relation to the testing, repair, inspection and maintenance (both planned &amp; reactive) of life safety smoke control systems.<br><br>Main Responsibilities: Test, repair, inspection and maintenance of a wide range of life safety equipment in accordance with the relevant legislation, company specification and manufacturers guidelines Document tasks completed and other relevant information pertaining to the visit, in a service report, recorded using iPhone provided and/or correct paperwork To provide detailed defect reporting and to liaise with clients to resolve defects, advise on the possible causes and solutions to prevent reoccurrence You will be servicing smoke ventilation controls at different sites throughout the south of England.<br><br>You are to provide full assistance to the sales team and maintenance office in the preparation of remedial quotations.<br><br>To liaise with the maintenance office and sales teams highlighting potential sales opportunities for the full range of products and services offered by them The successful Candidate will: Will have a strong ability to fault find and undertake technical assessment with a view to resolving problems Have effective defect reporting with the ability to convey viable suggestions for resolution of issues Good organisational and planning skills to ensure that tasks are completed in an efficient and timely manner whilst working autonomously Needs to be self-driven with an ability to converse with customers and colleagues in a polite and respectful manner Will preferably have a Fire Alarm or Smoke Ventilation qualification Some experience of working within the smoke ventilation/ life safety industry Needs to have a flexible approach Will be required to occasionally work unsociable hours Have an understanding of electrical circuits within control panels An ability to problem-solve, think outside of the box and provide thorough solutions Will have a professional appearance reflecting the company's values Have a Full driving licence (max 6 points) 17th or 18th Edition Electrical qualification or other recognised electrical qualification Gold Card Electrician with testing and inspecting qualifications Site experience, ideally holding a CSCS Card Experience working at height Working Hours: You must be flexible on working hours.<br><br>You will be expected to work Monday through to Fridays and be onsite standard business hours.<br><br>Occasionally you may be required to attend to an emergency callout with little notice dependant on the nature of the defect.<br><br>Benefits: 23 days paid holiday, increasing up to a maximum of 30 days Laptop &amp; iPhone Group Pension Scheme Company funded activities at Christmas and in the summer Development Programme, up to 100% funding for development programmes Company funded Bupa health plan after qualifying period Please click on the APPLY button to send your CV and Cover Letter for this role.<br><br>Candidates with experience of: Field Service Engineer, Service Engineer, Multi-skilled Engineer, Mechanical Engineer, Maintenance Engineer, Mobile Technician, Fault Repair Engineer, Maintenance Technician, Mobile Engineer Controller, Operations Coordinator, Operations Supervisor may also be considered for this role.]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[Eastern]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[Bedfordshire]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[Luton]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[Luton Bedfordshire]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[LU1]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[35000.00]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[40000.00]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[annum]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[Bluetownonline Ltd]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[]]></expiration-date>
	<creation-date><![CDATA[2019-08-22]]></creation-date>
</job>
<job price="0.08">
	<price><![CDATA[0.08]]></price>
	<id><![CDATA[20135]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[http://joblookup.com/uk/dispatch/job/feed/area-support-technician-service-delivery-technician-1?utm_source=feed-2&utm_medium=PostJobFree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[Area Support Technician / Service Delivery Technician]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[Job Title: Area Support Technician Location: Central to Eastbourne Salary: circa £20,000 per annum plus a car allowance Job Type: Full Time, Permanent The Company is the UK's leading operator of Point of Care software and services, with over 20 years experience in the field.<br><br>Their solutions are used in more than 130 hospital sites across the NHS, offering patient media and Wi-Fi.<br><br>Role Overview: Their Area Support Technicians (ASTs) are customer facing technical contacts for a local 'cluster' of Hospitals that host their services and equipment.<br><br>The role involves interacting with customers at the bedside in Hospital and with Ward staff and other contacts on the site.<br><br>Although you will be part of a team, each AST has operational responsibility for their designated cluster, and should be self driven and committed to the maintenance and success of their services within their cluster.<br><br>Practical technical skills are key, but soft skills are also vital in this role where you will be working closely with our customers and NHS staff.<br><br>Local travel will be required to all hospital sites in your designated cluster.<br><br>Key Responsibilities and Duties: Responsible for managing your own working schedule with support from your Team Leader.<br><br>Working to targets to complete your daily work schedule Carrying out Health and Safety checks to ensure equipment is fit for purpose Carrying out checks on faulty Bedside Units to minimise customer service disruption and maximise uptime Working closely with the Maintenance and Repair team and Regional Engineers as required to resolve faults that cannot be easily fixed at the bedside Regularly monitoring Vending Machine usage and ensuring they are working Monthly decommissioning, reconciliation and banking of Vending Machines Low level fault resolution to site systems, for example server restarts or satellite receiver reboots Frequent engagement with customers (patients, their friends and family) supporting with the use of the service and to resolve any problems or escalate these if required Managing customer expectations in a professional and polite manner Regular engagement with Ward staff to build rapport and encourage them to raise awareness of the services Working as part of a team with other ASTs and other areas of the business such as the Customer Call Centre Completing end of day reporting and checks Providing cover for other nearby clusters in the Region as required Key Requirements: Essential Demonstrated logical, hands on, practical approach to electrical and mechanical problems Clear competence with a range of hand tools and electrical testing kit to identify system faults Demonstrated experience of providing high levels of customer service, including listening to feedback and complaints and delivering swift pragmatic solutions A Disciplined, discreet and professional approach to work Highly organised with the ability to prioritise effectively and work to deadlines Proficient verbal and written communication skills, including the ability to communicate technical issues to non-technical people Computer literate, including knowledge of basic packages such as MS Office Word and Excel and good keyboard skills Ability to prepare and produce professional reports Flexibility of working hours.<br><br>There is an element of out of hours cover required for regional health and safety matters, for which call out allowances will be paid Full UK driving license with your own car Desirable Previous experience of working with Vending Machines and payphones Previous experience of cash handling Experience of working within the Audio-Visual Industry Experience of working with cabling / infrastructure Relevant Telecommunications / IT experience Work Pattern: Normal hours of work are based on a shift pattern, working 40 hours per week, between the hours of 8am and 6pm.<br><br>They are operational 7 days a week therefore weekend working may be required.<br><br>Statutory Bank Holidays are normal working days at their Hospital sites.<br><br>This role will require attendance at site in the event of a code red call-out outside of normal working hours, in line with the current Out of Hours procedure.<br><br>Please click on the APPLY button to send your CV and Cover Letter for this role.<br><br>Candidates with experience of: Customer Support, Customer Service Executive, Customer Service Representative, Customer Service Administrator, Business Administration, Business Administration Support, Admin Support, Administrative, Client Service, Customer Services, Customer Assistant, Customer Service Consultant, Customer Advisor, Customer Service, Application Support Officer, Application Support, IT Application Support, may also be considered for this role.]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[South East]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[East Sussex]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[Eastbourne]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[Eastbourne East Sussex]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[BN21]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[20000.00]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[20000.00]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[annum]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[Bluetownonline Ltd]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[]]></expiration-date>
	<creation-date><![CDATA[2019-08-22]]></creation-date>
</job>
<job price="0.08">
	<price><![CDATA[0.08]]></price>
	<id><![CDATA[21804]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[http://joblookup.com/uk/dispatch/job/feed/assistant-financial-controller-1?utm_source=feed-2&utm_medium=PostJobFree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[Assistant Financial Controller]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[My client is a well established Warwickshire based manufacturing company.<br><br>Due to an internal promotion, an opportunity has arisen for an Assistant Financial Controller to join the business on a permanent basis.<br><br>You will be responsible for the following: Control of the month end and quarter end processes Taking the lead with internal and external auditors Preparing the statutory accounts Weekly cashflow forecasts Monthly KPI reporting This is a great time to join the business and you will be an individual who has experience of working within a fast paced manufacturing environment.<br><br>A qualified accountant (ACA, ACCA, CIMA) you will be looking for the next challenge in your career.<br><br>If this sounds like the role for you, please apply immediately.<br><br>Management experience is a must for this role as you will be looking after a team of three direct and two indirect reports.]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[West Midlands]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[Warwickshire]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[Alcester]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[Warwickshire]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[B49]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[50000.00]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[55000.00]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[annum]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[SF Recruitment Limited t/a SF Group]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[]]></expiration-date>
	<creation-date><![CDATA[2019-08-22]]></creation-date>
</job>
<job price="0.08">
	<price><![CDATA[0.08]]></price>
	<id><![CDATA[494505]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[http://joblookup.com/uk/dispatch/job/feed/class-1-driver?utm_source=feed-2&utm_medium=PostJobFree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[Class 1 Driver]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[HGV - Class 1 Driver - Worksop - Up to £3000 p/m - Guaranteed Shifts until 2020 - Paid Assessments - Apply Now!<br><br>Nexus People are looking for HGV Class 1 drivers in Worksop to work for one of the UK’s leading logistics and distribution companies for a leading supplier of hardware, homeware and garden supplies for weekend working. <br><br>We have guaranteed shifts working Friday, Saturday, Sunday and Monday running all the way through to 2020. <br><br>*Please note, you must have a Class 1 Licence to apply for this role*<br><br>What does being a Class 1 Driver entail?<br><br>- Driving an HGV  – Class 1<br> - Trunking and store deliveries - working with cages<br> - Routine Vehicle Maintenance Checks<br> - Route and delivery paperwork completion<br><br>Shift times &amp; working hours of a Class 1 Driver…<br><br>- 48 hour working week (must include a Saturday shift)<br> - Ongoing regular work <br> - GUARANTEED SHIFTS AVAILABLE THROUGH TO 2020<br><br>Why should you work for Nexus People as a Class 1 Driver?<br><br>- Earn up to £3,000 per month!<br> - Guaranteed Shift allocations<br> - Fully paid Assessments <br> - Free CPC Modules! Complete a free CPC module for every 12 months of ongoing service completed, up to 5 years!<br> - Pension Scheme (Auto-enrollment)<br> - Full Employment and Mortgage References<br> - Paid holidays (PAYE Drivers - earn up to 28 days a year!)<br> - Weekly Pay (Every Friday!)<br> - PAYE &amp; LTD drivers welcome<br> - Use of a microwave/vending machines/hot drinks facilities<br> - Free onsite carparking<br> - 24 hour support from the Nexus team<br> - Temp to Perm opportunities<br><br>What do we need from you to be a Class 1 Driver?<br><br>- Full HGV Class 1 driving licence<br> - Minimum 3 months experience<br> - 90 days tacho recorded driving in the last 180 days<br> - We will accept up to 6 points on your licence, but no DD, TT, DR, CD, IN endorsements<br> - Digi Tachograph Card<br> - DCPC Card<br> - Completion of a full corporate driving assessment<br><br>Click “apply” today and our recruitment team will be in touch to progress your application.<br><br>*<br>*<br>*<br>*<br><br>#HGV #Driver #Class1 #Worksop #Weekend #Transport #Working #Workintransport #Class 1<br><br>** IMPORTANT **<br>Please be aware, Nexus People do NOT charge any fees for arranging work for you – if anyone asks you for money to organise an interview or assessment, please contact our HR team immediately.<br> <br>Important Information: We endeavour to process your personal data in a fair and transparent manner. In applying for this role, Nexus People will be acting within your interest and will contact you in relation to the role, either by email, phone or text message. For more information see our Privacy Policy on our website. It is important you are aware of your individual rights and the provisions the company has put in place to protect your data. If you would like further information on the policy or the GDPR please contact us.]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[East Midlands]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[Nottinghamshire]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[Worksop]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[Worksop]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[S80]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[3000.00]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[3000.00]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[month]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[temporary]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[full-time]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[Nexus Workforce Limited]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[http://joblookup.com/img/recruiters/e8/e8a1541_471.png]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[2019-09-25]]></expiration-date>
	<creation-date><![CDATA[2019-09-11]]></creation-date>
</job>
<job price="0.08">
	<price><![CDATA[0.08]]></price>
	<id><![CDATA[21813]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[http://joblookup.com/uk/dispatch/job/feed/financial-accountant-19?utm_source=feed-2&utm_medium=PostJobFree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[Financial Accountant]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[My client is a Warwickshire based distribution business who are looking for a Financial Accountant on a permanent basis.<br><br>This is a fantastic business which has experienced really good growth over the course of the last few years.<br><br>Whilst they continue to go from strength to strength, they are looking to bolster the team with this key appointment in the team.<br><br>You will be responsible for the following: Statutory accounting Support with internal and external auditors Corporation tax Cashflow P&amp;L reporting This is a really good role for an entry into the business where you will have the opportunity to further develop in your career with the ability to progress based upon your performance.<br><br>You will be a qualified accountant (ACA, ACCA, CIMA) and you will have experience of working in a fast paced environment.<br><br>If this sounds like the role for you, please apply immediately.]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[West Midlands]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[Warwickshire]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[Alcester]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[Warwickshire]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[B49]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[40000.00]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[50000.00]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[annum]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[SF Recruitment Limited t/a SF Group]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[]]></expiration-date>
	<creation-date><![CDATA[2019-08-22]]></creation-date>
</job>
<job price="0.08">
	<price><![CDATA[0.08]]></price>
	<id><![CDATA[28066]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[http://joblookup.com/uk/dispatch/job/feed/maintenance-engineer-multi-skilled-mechanical-bias?utm_source=feed-2&utm_medium=PostJobFree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[Maintenance Engineer - Multi-Skilled - Mechanical Bias]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[Maintenance Engineer<br>- Multi-Skilled (Mechanical Bias) Chorley Manager: Engineering Supervisor Salary £27,000<br>- £32,000<br>- with 25 days holiday plus bank holidays Current working pattern is 8am<br>- 4pm Monday to Friday but the company is planning to introduce 6am -2pm and 2pm<br>- 10pm Mon<br>- Fri shift pattern in the future.<br><br>Job Purpose: To support the site by ensuring the safe, reliable and efficient operation of all mechanical, electrical and other plant on site Working with Engineering Team of 5 engineers of different work experience backgrounds.<br><br>Actively participate in the Planned Preventative Maintenance scheme and the Engineering Works Request Scheme Job Dimensions: Organisation turnover;c.£25 million Primary Interfaces: Engineering Team Production staff Laboratory and support staff External contractors KEY RESPONSIBILITIES: Adhere to, and participate in, the annual maintenance plans to ensure minimum disruption to plant by planned or breakdown downtime, including Continuous engineering maintenance and preventative maintenance plan Structural facility and building maintenance plan Work with the Engineering Supervisor and process staff to monitor, implement and improve the outputs of the engineering works request scheme.<br><br>Participate in the 24hour maintenance call out system as required and open to working on a permanent late shift pattern.<br><br>Play an active part in continuous improvement programs and projects undertaken on site, such as energy efficient projects Assist in the implementation and control of Health &amp; Safety &amp; Environmental standards to satisfy legislative and corporate requirements.<br><br>SKILLS, KNOWLEDGE &amp; EXPERIENCE: ONC or equivalent level vocational qualification in mechanical and or electrical related discipline Minimum 3<br>- 5 years' in manufacturing or production mechanical maintenance engineering experience including competency in pneumatics, hydraulics, pumps, gearboxes and industrial steam system.<br><br>Welding and fabrication skill will be an advantage.<br><br>Electrical experience that will need to include isolation of motors, AC/DC drives, inverters and the ability to fault find using P&amp;ID diagram, electrical drawing and schematics diagram.<br><br>PLC experience will be an added advantage Flexible approach to work and prepared to be involved in variety of duties Self-motivated, results-oriented with a positive, can-do attitude A strong communicator at all levels and a team player who is able to stay calm under pressure.]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[North West]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[Lancashire]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[Chorley]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[Chorley Lancashire]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[PR7]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[27000.00]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[32000.00]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[annum]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[DCA Recruitment]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[]]></expiration-date>
	<creation-date><![CDATA[2019-08-22]]></creation-date>
</job>
<job price="0.08">
	<price><![CDATA[0.08]]></price>
	<id><![CDATA[33837]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[http://joblookup.com/uk/dispatch/job/feed/intermediate-quantity-surveyor-5?utm_source=feed-2&utm_medium=PostJobFree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[Intermediate Quantity Surveyor]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[Intermediate Quantity Surveyor Freelance opportunity for an Intermediate Quantity Surveyor to be based in Middlesex for an Immediate Start for an M&amp;E Residential project.<br><br>You will be responsible for the management of all costs and value relating to a £6m new development ensuring its completion within the projected timescales and manage the bills of quantities and budgets, adjusting projections accordingly The ideal candidate would be a dynamic team player with experience in freelance work and the following skill set:<br>- 3-6+ years’ experience in quantity surveying.<br><br>- M&amp;E and Residential experience<br>- BSc Quantity Surveying / Commercial Management / RCIS Daily Rate: Up to £225 per day depending on experience Start Date: ASAP Contract Length: 62 week initial contract My client is looking to line up interviews as soon as Thursday 15th August and need someone to get started ASAP.<br><br>Does this sound like it could be of interest to you? If not do you know someone who could be well suited to the role? Please send me an updated copy of your CV to or call me on This is an exciting opportunity for any experienced Quantity Surveyor that is looking to progress their career and work for one of the largest UK developers.<br><br>If this role isn’t what you’re looking for don’t worry, at X4 Construction we cover all permanent and contract positions with specialist industry sector teams.<br><br>You can check out all of our roles on our website and sign up for job alerts so you’re the first to know about a new opportunity.<br><br>About Us X4 Construction is a specialist recruitment business for the Construction sector.<br><br>We are part of the X4 Group, a multi-award-winning group of brands specialising in Life Sciences, Engineering, Construction and Technology, with over 10 years of experience in successfully placing mid to senior level contract and permanent professionals across the globe.<br><br>Our network of world class talent sets us apart from the rest and allows us to deliver skilled professionals to our pharmaceutical, biotech and medical device partners quicker than the competition.<br><br>Our aim is to help businesses grow powerful teams that deliver against exceptionally high standards and we have partnerships with leading life science companies all over the world and have made placements in over 15 countries across Europe and the US]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[Middlesex]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[200.00]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[225.00]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[day]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[contract]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[full-time]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[X4 Group Ltd]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[]]></expiration-date>
	<creation-date><![CDATA[2019-08-22]]></creation-date>
</job>
<job price="0.08">
	<price><![CDATA[0.08]]></price>
	<id><![CDATA[41653]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[http://joblookup.com/uk/dispatch/job/feed/react-native-mobile-developer?utm_source=feed-2&utm_medium=PostJobFree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[REACT NATIVE MOBILE DEVELOPER]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[REACT NATIVE MOBILE DEVELOPER TRAVEL TECHNOLOGY GREATER MANCHESTER £40,000-£50,000 PLUS BONUS THE JOB A great opportunity exists for a driven and innovative React Native Mobile developer in Manchester.<br><br>You will be involved with the development and maintenance of the companies mobile web-based products.<br><br>Within this role, you will be helping to develop and maintain recently re-written mobile product which will grow alongside other web offerings.<br><br>You will need to have extensive React Native, Redux and JavaScript skills.<br><br>WHAT EXPERIENCE DO I NEED? <br>*Minimum of 2 years' JavaScript/Ajax, React Native and Redux.<br>*It would be a great plus if you have XCode, JSON, Objective C/Java skills and experience writing bridging components as well as previous experience of both IOS and Android.<br>*The ideal candidate will have JavaScript/Ajax experience as well as exposure to backend work in PHP, MySQL or Perl.<br><br>ABOUT THE COMPANY This company believes that technology should benefit rather than detract from the customers' needs so they are looking for an innovative, flexible and driven developer to join their team.<br><br>You will join a great development team and deliver web-based products to a wide travel customer base.<br><br>You will be joining a company that is truly revolutionising online technology capabilities.<br><br>Nicola Townsend is recruiting for this React Native Mobile Developer role in Manchester.<br><br>Click to apply.<br>*By applying for this vacancy, you consent to the safe storage and handling of any personal data you've provided us with.<br><br>We will never share your data with a third-party without your consent.<br><br>You can request the removal of your data at any time.<br><br>Please visit our website for more information on our privacy policy.<br><br>Applicants must have the legal right to live and work in the country where the vacancy exists.<br><br>We regret we are only able to contact shortlisted candidates.<br><br>Progressive Travel Recruitment (a trading name of Progressive Personnel Ltd., est.<br><br>2005) is a leading international travel and hospitality recruitment company with offices in the UK, USA, Canada, United Arab Emirates, South Africa and The Maldives.]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[North West]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[Greater Manchester]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[Manchester]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[Greater Manchester]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[M2]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[40000.00]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[50000.00]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[annum]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[Progressive Travel Recruitment]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[]]></expiration-date>
	<creation-date><![CDATA[2019-08-22]]></creation-date>
</job>
<job price="0.08">
	<price><![CDATA[0.08]]></price>
	<id><![CDATA[66724]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[http://joblookup.com/uk/dispatch/job/feed/finance-manager-135?utm_source=feed-2&utm_medium=PostJobFree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[Finance Manager]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[My client is a Warwickshire based manufacturing business who are looking for a Finance Manager on a permanent basis.<br><br>Working very closely with the FD, you will be responsible for all aspects of running the finance team being involved in the following: Production of financial reports, cashflow reporting and balance sheet analysis Management accounts preparation for use by the MD Working with external auditors Liaising with budget holders in terms of variances, budgets and commentary You will be from a manufacturing background and will be used to being very hands on, whilst being able to communicate with and be part of the senior management team.<br><br>The role itself will be a mixture of transactional work along with strategic work in terms of assisting the owners with the growth of the business.<br><br>A qualified accountant (ACA, ACCA, CIMA), you will be looking for an exciting role within a growing business where you'll be able to really make your mark.]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[West Midlands]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[Warwickshire]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[Alcester]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[Warwickshire]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[B49]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[50000.00]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[55000.00]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[annum]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[SF Recruitment Limited t/a SF Group]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[]]></expiration-date>
	<creation-date><![CDATA[2019-08-22]]></creation-date>
</job>
<job price="0.08">
	<price><![CDATA[0.08]]></price>
	<id><![CDATA[69046]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[http://joblookup.com/uk/dispatch/job/feed/finance-manager-140?utm_source=feed-2&utm_medium=PostJobFree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[Finance Manager]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[My client is a Warwickshire based manufacturing business who are looking for a Finance Manager on a permanent basis.<br><br>Working very closely with the MD, you will be responsible for all aspects of running the finance team being involved in the following: Preparation of budgets and forecasts ensuring control over costs and overall expenditure Management accounts preparation for use by the MD Working with external auditors Preparation of statutory accounts You will be from a manufacturing background and will be used to being very hands on, whilst being able to communicate with and be part of the senior management team.<br><br>A qualified accountant (ACA, ACCA, CIMA), you will be looking for an exciting role within a growing business where you'll be able to really make your mark.]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[West Midlands]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[Warwickshire]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[Alcester]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[Warwickshire]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[B49]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[45000.00]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[50000.00]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[annum]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[SF Recruitment Limited t/a SF Group]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[]]></expiration-date>
	<creation-date><![CDATA[2019-08-22]]></creation-date>
</job>
<job price="0.08">
	<price><![CDATA[0.08]]></price>
	<id><![CDATA[74269]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[http://joblookup.com/uk/dispatch/job/feed/web-developer-46?utm_source=feed-2&utm_medium=PostJobFree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[Web Developer]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[If you're a Web Developer that's looking to head up the design and development team with one of the biggest marketing agencies in South East England, look no further.<br><br>We're currently helping a successful and growing agency based in Essex, hire their next Web Developer.<br><br>They're constantly looking to make use of the latest design and development tools and innovations to bring their clients websites to life, and as such they always seek to employ forward-thinking and technologically-minded developers who are not afraid to think outside the box.<br><br>As their new Web Developer, you should have: Knowledge of PHP programming language knowledge of databases &amp; full e-commerce integration, API’s, user experience and journey front-end development skills in HTML5, CSS3, Javascript and jQuery Ability to convert PSD’s and other graphical assets to HTML/CSS with pixel perfection Ability to use Photoshop and cut up design templates Experience using and implementing Google Analytics, Webmaster Tools and other tracking tools Technical knowledge of on page SEO and SEO friendly web site structures Knowledge and experience in designing and building Wordpress sites is essential In return, you'll receive a generous package of £40k per annum and working with one of the most reputable agencies in the South East of England.<br><br>To avoid missing out on this opportunity, contact Aydin or APPLY TODAY.<br><br>JGA Recruitment Group Ltd.<br><br>("We") are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.<br><br>We are a specialist payroll, HR &amp; Marketing recruitment agency and recruitment business as defined in the Employment Agencies and Employment Businesses Regulations 2003 (our business).<br><br>This statement together with our privacy notice sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us.]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[Eastern]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[Essex]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[Chelmsford]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[Essex]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[CM1]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[38000.00]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[40000.00]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[annum]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[full-time]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[James Gray Associates Ltd]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[]]></expiration-date>
	<creation-date><![CDATA[2019-08-22]]></creation-date>
</job>
<job price="0.08">
	<price><![CDATA[0.08]]></price>
	<id><![CDATA[84995]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[http://joblookup.com/uk/dispatch/job/feed/led-and-service-technician-video-broadcast-systems?utm_source=feed-2&utm_medium=PostJobFree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[LED and Service Technician (Video & Broadcast Systems)]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[This company is one of the leading industry players in the world of technical production for live events, they have an extensive inventory across the latest audio, lighting and video equipment which provides a lot of exciting work and project opportunities for all of their technical teams.<br><br>The video department certainly lives up to this and they are now looking for a skilled and passionate LED and Service Technician to join them.<br><br>The Role Based from their warehouse in Hertfordshire the position will see you playing an intrinsic role in the delivery of LED Screens and general video equipment for an exciting array of live event projects.<br><br>This means you will be assisting with the service, repair and maintenance of the equipment along with the building and wiring of equipment packages for the company’s rental inventory.<br><br>There will be plenty of support and liaison with the Head of the Department, Project, Technical and Warehouse Teams.<br><br>The organisation actively encourages the development of its staff so as you evolve and grow into the position you will be involved with the wider elements of key projects and technical development.<br><br>About You Your experience and background will show A practical understanding of LED Screens A practical understanding of PPUs and camera systems Excellent fault finding experience A methodical and neat approach to your work Excellent wiring skills Strong communication skills A desire to continually develop your technical knowledge On Offer On offer is a competitive salary based on experience and the opportunity to be part of a successful and supportive organisation within the live events sector.<br><br>For further details and consideration apply now with your full CV ________ By applying for this job, you are choosing to accept Creative Personnel's Terms &amp; Conditions. At Creative Personnel we process certain personal information about you for our legitimate business interests in order to identify and contact you about suitable positions that may be relevant to you.<br><br>Details are set out in our Privacy Policy. ]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[Eastern]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[Hertfordshire]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[St Albans]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[Hertfordshire]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[AL3]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[22000.00]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[25000.00]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[annum]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[full-time]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[Creative Personnel]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[]]></expiration-date>
	<creation-date><![CDATA[2019-08-22]]></creation-date>
</job>
<job price="0.08">
	<price><![CDATA[0.08]]></price>
	<id><![CDATA[105052]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[http://joblookup.com/uk/dispatch/job/feed/audio-visual-installation-engineer-smart-home-marine?utm_source=feed-2&utm_medium=PostJobFree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[Audio Visual Installation Engineer- Smart Home & Marine]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[My client, an established AV/IT Integration company based in the South East, is now looking for an experienced AV Installation Engineer who has experience with programming, commissioning and/or servicing Audio Visual control systems.<br><br>The work will be in high-end residential properties and onboard Luxury Yachts.<br><br>Interacting with clientele as well as internal team members, the ideal AV Installation Engineer will need to be flexible, and independent, with top quality customer service skills.<br><br>The successful AV Installation Engineer will need experience and knowledge of: Installation of Audio Visual equipment including Sky, standard antenna and cabling Strong hands-on installation experience of Crestron and Lutron control systems Technical understanding of Audio Visual equipment Audio and Visual distribution and setting up network systems Programming knowledge of control systems such as Home Automation and CCTV would be beneficial Programming experience of Crestron and/or Lutron would be a distinct advantage.<br><br>Ideally, the AV Installation Engineer will be based in the South London/Surrey area although the work would be UK wide as well abroad on occasion.<br><br>As such, a full Driving Licence and a valid Passport are BOTH essential.<br><br>This is a fantastic opportunity for an experienced AV Engineer who is looking to take that next step in their career with the added bonus of international travel thrown in.<br><br>If you feel this is the right role for you, please APPLY NOW with your full technical CV.<br><br>NO SPONSORSHIP IS ON OFFER YOU MUST BE IN THE UK / COMING TO THE UK WITH A VISA TO BE CONSIDERED OR HAVE THE APPROPRIATE WORKING VISA, ALL INFORMATION MUST BE IN THE CV NOT IN A COVERING LETTER.<br><br>AV, Audio Visual, AudioVisual, Audio-Visual, Installation, Engineer, Installation Engineer, AV Engineer, Programmer, Lutron, Crestron, Residential, Marine, Home Automation, Home, Yacht, Superyacht ________ By applying for this job, you are choosing to accept Creative Personnel's Terms &amp; Conditions. At Creative Personnel we process certain personal information about you for our legitimate business interests in order to identify and contact you about suitable positions that may be relevant to you.<br><br>Details are set out in our Privacy Policy. ]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[South East]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[Surrey]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[Esher]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[Surrey]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[KT10]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[25000.00]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[35000.00]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[annum]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[full-time]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[Creative Personnel London]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[]]></expiration-date>
	<creation-date><![CDATA[2019-08-22]]></creation-date>
</job>
<job price="0.08">
	<price><![CDATA[0.08]]></price>
	<id><![CDATA[138014]]></id>
	<url><![CDATA[http://joblookup.com/uk/dispatch/job/feed/care-assistants-32?utm_source=feed-2&utm_medium=PostJobFree]]></url>
	<title><![CDATA[Care Assistants]]></title>
	<desc><![CDATA[Have you got a ready smile? We are looking for care assistants to help our elderly residents with all activities of daily living: washing, dressing, eating and drinking, and providing emotional support.<br><br>All our residents have dementia, and this means they need the right people to support them.<br><br>What type of people are we looking for? Do you have a ready smile? Are you patient? Can you understand that when people cry or get cross it's because they don't know what's going on? Do you mind if the conversation becomes jumbled and hard to follow? If you think that this describes you then we would like to hear from you.<br><br>We are looking to fill full and part time vacancies and would love to hear from the sort of person who wants to make a difference to people who live with dementia.<br><br>Interested? Click on "Show me the telephone number" to apply today]]></desc>
	<region><![CDATA[Wales]]></region>
	<county><![CDATA[Gwent]]></county>
	<town><![CDATA[Llanyrafon]]></town>
	<location><![CDATA[Llanyrafon]]></location>
	<postcode><![CDATA[NP44]]></postcode>
	<salary-from><![CDATA[19697.99]]></salary-from>
	<salary-to><![CDATA[19697.99]]></salary-to>
	<salary-type><![CDATA[annum]]></salary-type>
	<job-type><![CDATA[]]></job-type>
	<job-status><![CDATA[]]></job-status>
	<category><![CDATA[]]></category>
	<reference><![CDATA[]]></reference>
	<company><![CDATA[JobLookup]]></company>
	<logo><![CDATA[]]></logo>
	<expiration-date><![CDATA[]]></expiration-date>
	<creation-date><![CDATA[2019-08-22]]></creation-date>
</job>
</jobs>
