<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><source><lastBuildDate>2020-10-28 11:43:02</lastBuildDate>
<job><id>3845551907</id><company>Communicate Recruitment: Finance 1</company><title>Newly Qualified Chartered Accountants</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Skills &amp;amp; Experience: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Minimum 0 - 4 years experience&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualification:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;BCom Accounting with outstanding transcripts&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SAIPA/SAICA Articles Completed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Board 1 and 2 Exams Completed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CA(SA)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Contact&lt;strong&gt; KYLE HAGGLUND &lt;/strong&gt;on &lt;strong&gt;021 418 1750&lt;/strong&gt;, quoting the Ref: &lt;strong&gt;CTF012770.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Connect with us on &lt;/p&gt;</description><url>https://za.jobsora.com/job-3845551907</url><city>Cape Town</city><country>South Africa</country><date>2020-10-28</date></job><job><id>3845551909</id><company>Communicate Recruitment: Finance 3</company><title>Cost Accountant</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualification and Experience Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;BCom&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;CIMA complete&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 2 years experience within a similar role either in Pharmaceuticals or Manufacturing&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Expeience with ABC Costing&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Must have strong experience with BOM and variance analysis&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you meet the above requirements and would like more information, Contact us immediately.&lt;/p&gt;</description><url>https://za.jobsora.com/job-3845551909</url><city>Johannesburg</city><country>South Africa</country><date>2020-10-28</date></job><job><id>3845551911</id><company>The Recruitment People</company><title>Financial Manager</title><description>&lt;p&gt;A global services company is searching for a Financial Manager for one of their divisions in the East Rand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Job Description:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The candidate will be responsible for the Financial Management function, including but not limited to the following:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Overseeing the full accounting function for the division.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Monthly management reports.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Presenting the financial reports to top management.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Provide commentary to enable top management to make strategic business decisions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Management of staff.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;BCom degree&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Around 5 years experience.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent presentation skills.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Benefits are negotiable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Thank you for submitting your CV. We will assess your suitability for the existing vacancies and retain your CV in our database in accordance with the Protection of Personal Information Policy. We will contact you should your CV be suitable for any available positions. You have the right to &quot;Opt-Out&quot; of electronic communications from us at any time and you also have the right to request us to delete your information by sending a request to &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><url>https://za.jobsora.com/job-3845551911</url><city>Johannesburg</city><country>South Africa</country><date>2020-10-28</date></job><job><id>3845551913</id><company>First Point Group</company><title>Human Resource/Employee Relations Management Professional</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Skills and experience required (Non-negotiable):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;10 years of HRM work experience in SA&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Labour Relations: Grievance, Disciplinary, CCMA, Performance Improvement &amp;amp; reviews&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Compliance: Employment Equity, COID, UIF, IRP5 recons&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Membership: Employment Equity, MANCO, Training Committee&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;B-BBEE: Tenders, Strategy implementation, Employment Equity Targets, Empowering Supplier targets, Headcounts, HR docs for B-BBEE audit, Policies, Job Grading, Employment Equity Policy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Occupational Health, Safety and Quality: EHS and Quality (audits), Quality document control, IOD&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Policies / Templates: HR legal register, Manage policies as per Law/company, Draft new policies as per Law/company&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Local Talent Development: Local high-end talent retention, etc.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Outsourcing company management: General Management of PSL, meeting &amp;amp; reviews with HRBPs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications Required:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Degree in HR Management&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work with HRD as the senior partner for local affairs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Training &amp;amp; development of staff on labour relations&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Staff welfare&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Assist with corporate visa applications&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Present at Employees Orientation Programmes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Manage Top Employer survey&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><url>https://za.jobsora.com/job-3845551913</url><city>Johannesburg</city><country>South Africa</country><date>2020-10-28</date></job><job><id>3845551915</id><company>Rosstone Consulting</company><title>PMO Lead</title><description>The Role: &lt;p&gt;We are looking for an experienced PMO Lead for a 12-month fixed term contract for our client in Mpumalanga.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Â &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are looking for your 10 years work experience within heavy industry, mining and production environment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Â &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are looking for your Project Management experience in applying Lean methodology in a project management environment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Â &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum educational level: Â  Â  Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â  &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;BEng Engineering&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Government Certificate of Competence: Engineering&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Certificate Project Management&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lean Six Sigma Black Belt&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;Skills and Experience: &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Purpose of the role:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Establish and operationalise a Project Management Office (PMO) function, with a key focus on driving the PMO function and continuous improvement initiatives.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Manage continuous improvement reporting, develop and implement robust processes, manage the overall governance and tracking of projects.Â &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;To direct and manage project development for duration of projects phases.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;To develop project plans and estimate resources needed to achieve project goals through the implementation of Lean principles.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Engage with Stakeholders.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The PMO Lead is the functional leader of project delivery and governance across the projects. Provide advice and guidance, monitoring and assurance, advocacy and education with respect to programmes, projects, and their delivery, at all levels.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Reporting framework focussed on value added advice and early identification of risk and issues for all major programmes and projects across the organisation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Support identification of improvement areas and solution development.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Â &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Coordinate site operations readiness team interfacing with the project to ensure the delivery of key project milestones. This includes ensuring critical milestones are met, providing visual management on progress and problem solving with the work stream teams to mitigate risks or project delays.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Create and execute project work plans and revise to meet changing project needs and requirements.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Creating action plans to manage risk to the operations.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ensure document control via centralised capturing system specified.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Implement controls to ensure legal compliance.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Apply controls to ensure legal and best practice compliance in accordance with MHSA (Mine Health and Safety Act), MPRDA (Mineral and Petroleum Resources Development Act), OHSA (Occupational Health and Safety Act) where applicable&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Implement effective SHE management systems for project.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adhere to Enterprise Project Management (EPM) Standards and requirements of quality management systems.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ensure compliance to environmental Record of Decision (RoD).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Manage and ensure optimal use of budget allocated to project.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Advise on selection of project recovery team members.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Report on the optimization and improvement projects to the mega project manager to ensure targets and initiatives are met.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Provide inputs for planning and recommendations for staff to be efficiently deployed and identify areas of further development (projects and training).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;Key Accountabilities: &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We require your 10 Yearsâ?? work experience with the following D&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;uties and Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Audit projects and programmes for project progress against agreed tolerances&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Audit Project support offices to ensure adhere to Corporate Governance with regards to processes, systems, guidelines and templates&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Update knowledge of project management best practice&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Participate in evaluation of discipline-specific standards, principles and practice to enable planning, design and implementation of project outcomes that support business strategy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Contribute to development and implementation of an appropriate approach to knowledge management for discipline in line with business needs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Provide and participate in governance systems for best practice&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Keep abreast with developments in Lean principles&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Create working relationships with project managers and other Project Management Offices (PMO)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Identify resources needed and assigns individual responsibilities&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Take action to mitigate and manage risks that can impact on project&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Identify and manage project dependencies and critical path&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Supervise and ensure execution of projects in adherence to agreed SLA&apos;&apos;s and service delivery standards&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work directly with the work stream leads to develop detailed robust operational readiness plans are developed by each function to ensure they are aligned and integrated across the site and with the project and provide regular visibility on progress.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Create an environment of right first time in everything that we do through a focus on principles of lean including simplification, standard work, visual management and a learning organisation as part of the establishment of the site PMO&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Be accountable for a robust investigation process to drive to right first time&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ensure Regional Project Support Office (RPSO) conduct periodic audits on projects responsibility&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Represent the PMO office at appropriate conferences, seminars and other events&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Maintain and ensure healthy environment, safe operations and practices, ensuring compliance with all applicable SHE policies and procedures in line with set standards&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Encourage culture that focuses on safety in all operations&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><url>https://za.jobsora.com/job-3845551915</url><city>Johannesburg</city><country>South Africa</country><date>2020-10-28</date></job><job><id>3845551917</id><company>Elmich Consultants</company><title>R&amp;D Manager from Food Manufacturing/bakery focus. R1 Mill CTC Johannesburg</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Masters in Food Technology, Nutritional Sciences and perhaps some quality management. Minimum 8 years&apos;&apos;expereince in R &amp;amp;D from Food Manufacturing environment, focus bakery technology. Handling of multi-projects simultaneously. Staff management as will have 5 R&amp;amp;D staff reporting.Advanced Excel, food markets trends knowledge, competency in food safety management systems, labelling, ingredients and back of pack information and all the necessary S.A. legislations. Skills for costing and capacity calculations and evluation stats. Experience in product development from brief, lab to final product and sensory evaluation. Food Safety team member - GMP, HACCP, ISO Standards.&lt;/p&gt;</description><url>https://za.jobsora.com/job-3845551917</url><city>Johannesburg</city><country>South Africa</country><date>2020-10-28</date></job><job><id>3845551919</id><company>Toro Human Capital</company><title>SAP Functional Consultant</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Intermediate Consultant  between 5 and 10 years working experience&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Senior Consultant  10+ years working experience at a managerial / team lead level&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Willingness to Travel (4 days / week)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Relevant qualification (IT / Math / etc.), university preferred&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Office Skills (Word, Excel, PPT)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Technical Affinity &amp;amp; Experience&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Basic SQL / Database Knowledge&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;XML, UML, etc.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Basic Linux&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;     Retail Process Knowledge (Retail Experience)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;POS / Backoffice&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;ERP / Store processes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of POS / ERP products&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;    Product Skills (POS / Backoffice, OMS ...)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Processes / Functions / Features&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Configuration&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Integration / Interfaces&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;     SAP Product Skills&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;THEY OFFER:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A cooperative work environment offering the scope for individual ideas, creativity and concepts&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The latest technology in the workplace, an international feel, continued employee development and training&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Employee benefits, a safe working environment and facilities to make everyday life easier&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><url>https://za.jobsora.com/job-3845551919</url><city>Johannesburg</city><country>South Africa</country><date>2020-10-28</date></job><job><id>3718999831</id><company>Tedroox Technologies Pvt.Ltd</company><title>Fullstack Developer (MERN Stack)</title><description>A full-stack developer handles both: Front-end and Back-end.&lt;br /&gt;need to build web pages, websites, create UI, make the website simple and attractive.Ã‚Â Your primary focus will be on developing user interface components and implementing them following well-known React.js workflows (such as Flux or Redux) along with CSS3 and HTML5.&lt;br /&gt;You will ensure that these components and the overall application are robust and easy to maintain.&lt;br /&gt;You will coordinate with the rest of the team working on different layers of the infrastructure.&lt;br /&gt;Therefore, a commitment to collaborative problem solving, sophisticated design, and quality product is important.Ã‚Â Ã‚Â React Native, MongoDB, Node JS Knowledge is a plus.Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Ã‚Â ResponsibilitiesÃ‚Â Design the overall architecture of the web application.Maintain quality and ensure the responsiveness of applications.Collaborate with the rest of the engineering team to design and launch new features.Maintain code integrity and organization.Experience working with graphic designers and converting designs to visual elements.Understanding and implementation of security and data protection.Ã‚Â Ã‚Â QualificationsÃ‚Â Graduation/ masters in computer scienceGood communicationMinimum 1 years of experience in mobile application and web application development.Front end Skills: Html, CSS, JavaScript ES6, React JS, react-native.Back end skills: Node Js, Mongo DB (Added advantage) Skills:- Javascript, PHP, NodeJS (Node.js), MongoDB, HTML/CSS, React Native and React.js</description><url>https://in.jobsora.com/job-3718999831</url><city>Bengaluru</city><country>India</country><salary>700000</salary><currency>INR</currency><date>2020-10-21</date></job><job><id>3718999837</id><company>Stanza Living</company><title>Frontend Developer</title><description>Â¢ Good with Data Structures and Algorithms.Â¢ Javascript, Angular 2.0, React, React Native, Angular Ionic (optional), JQuery, MYSQL,MongoDB, Firebase.Â¢ Comfortable with REST API development using Java or python.Â¢ Exposure to Artificial Intelligence / Machine Learning concepts will be a plus.&lt;br /&gt;Skills:- Javascript, HTML/CSS, Angular (2+), React.js and React Native</description><url>https://in.jobsora.com/job-3718999837</url><city>New Delhi</city><country>India</country><salary>2600000</salary><currency>INR</currency><date>2020-10-21</date></job><job><id>3718999851</id><company>Capgemini</company><title>Windows with Active Directory</title><description>&lt;b&gt; Job Description&lt;/b&gt;   Experience in designing, solutioning &amp;amp; Migrating Active Directory, Windows &amp;amp; End points  Strong familiarity with DNS &amp;amp; DHCP systems and Migration of services from AD to any platform  Good Knowledge of and experience with Active Directory &amp;amp; windows in a large corporate environment  Good knowledge and experience in AD assessment in terms of OU delegation, GPOs, permission etc.,  Expertise in Active Directory versions 2003, 2008R2, 2012R2 &amp;amp; 2016  Good knowledde and hands on experience in setting up lab based on the solution requirements  Good knowledge on Virtualization platforms  Good knowledge and hands on experience in AD disaster recovery  Good Knowledge on Active Directory &amp;amp; windows audit logs  Good knowledge on Networking, DNS, DHCP, DFS &amp;amp; Network load balancer  Good knowledge on Cryptography, certificates, PKI, symmetric, asymmetric keys, Encryption &amp;amp; hash algorithms  Good knowledge on AD authentication protocols Kerberos, NTLM, LDAP, LDAPS &amp;amp; LDAP-Start TLS  Good knowledge on Network log capturing &amp;amp; analyzing the logs through the tools Wireshark, Tshark, Microsoft NM etc.,  Good knowledge on application integration with LDAP &amp;amp; Kerberos i.e. Keytab, krb5 etc.,  Good knowledge on AD migration tools like ADMT, Quest etc.,&lt;br /&gt; Â   &lt;b&gt; Primary Skills&lt;/b&gt;   Active directory  &lt;b&gt; Secondary Skills&lt;/b&gt;   Windows</description><url>https://in.jobsora.com/job-3718999851</url><city>Chennai</city><country>India</country><date>2020-10-21</date></job><job><id>1657970183</id><company>Sea Horse View</company><title>Packaging Millwright Vacancy Available</title><description>Take your career forward with an FMCG who offers you challenging and interesting work. Provide specialised artisan skill and knowledge to the packaging department, supporting operations, maintenance and problem solving activities of the shift teams. Carry out condition monitoring activities, carry out running repairs on plant and equipment, assess problems and determine a cause of action.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
 A minimum of 5 - 8 years post-apprenticeship experience with knowledge of high-speed packaging equipment is desirable.&lt;br /&gt;
 An N6 / N5 Engineering plus a Millwright Trade Test is essential.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Backed and supported by a company with over 30 years in the recruitment industry, Extraordinary Futures International was established to fill a specific need within niche recruitment markets that require dedicated focus and intensive research, so we concentrate exclusively on placing high calibre and qualified candidates with reputable companies&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Call a Talent Acquisition Consultant at Extraordinary Futures International today for a confidential discussion about your next career move.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Please forward your cv to -Please upload your CV here-&amp;gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Visit our website extraordinaryfutures.co.za to see more hot jobs, and upload your CV. Look forward to hearing from you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
If you have not had any response in two weeks, please consider the vacancy application unsuccessful. Your profile will be kept on our database for any other suitable roles / positions.</description><url>https://za.jobsora.com/job-1657970183</url><city>Johannesburg</city><country>South Africa</country><date>2020-10-31</date></job>

<job><id>1657970623</id><company>FNB Bank Limited</company><title>FirstJob Graduate Programme Opportunity 2020</title><description>about us&lt;br /&gt;
WesBank believes that its people are its single most important resource and will not operate in a sector unless it has people who are right for that market and who share their business values. We recruit self-starters who have a passion for what they do. We empower them, hold them accountable and reward them appropriately. We value diversity in our people, particularly for the way that this contributes to innovative thinking. If you think you will flourish in our environment, and you believe you have the necessary skills and competencies for the position advertised, then we are looking for you! All suitably qualified candidates will be considered. Appointments will be made in line with the Bankâ€™s EE Strategy.&lt;br /&gt;
purpose&lt;br /&gt;
This is a 12-months contract for unemployed graduates to join our FirstJob work experience programm e. The focus of this programme is to improve employability of successful candidates. Throughout the programme, the incumbent will have an opportunity to build workplace confidence and competence by contributing to business objectives and deliverables. The incumbent will be required to successfully complete prescribed development programme.&lt;br /&gt;
experience and qualifications&lt;br /&gt;
Â· Minimum Qualification - Bachelorâ€™s degree Â· Preferred Qualification - Post graduate degree Qualifications will be matched against the requirements of Business Units across WesBank Skills required include; Â· Building relationships Â· Teamwork Â· Problem solving Â· Learning agility Â· Resilience and Stress Management Â· Drive and Results orientation&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
additional requirements&lt;br /&gt;
The FirstJob Programme seeks to provide an opportunity for unemployed youth that meet the following criteria: Â· Must be between the ages of 18 â€“ 34 Â· Must have been unemployed for at least the last 6 months Â· Must have no or limited work experience â€“ i.e. a total of less than twelve monthsâ€™ work experience and/or of a part-time, casual nature. This must be the youthâ€™s FIRST job experience The youth must also not have previously participated in the FirstJob programme at any of the FirstRand franchises.&lt;br /&gt;
responsibilities&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Â· Demonstrate excellence and quality orientation in all assigned tasks, deliverables and projects; Â· Execute role responsibilities efficiently through careful and timeous planning, reporting and updating; Â· Contribute to projects through proactive, innovative and appropriate input; Â· Participate in knowledge sharing with peers and stakeholders; Â· Manage own development plan to increase competencies and skills through various channels; Â· Adheres to and advocates WesBankâ€™s shared values and business philosophy</description><url>https://za.jobsora.com/job-1657970623</url><city>Johannesburg</city><country>South Africa</country><date>2020-10-30</date></job><job><id>1657970873</id><company>Clicks Group Limited</company><title>Clicks: Wellness Assistant</title><description>To offer exceptional service to all customers by providing knowledgeable service and basic advice on healthcare, nutrition and supplementation in order to maximise sales and build customer loyalty.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Purpose and Objectives&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
 To deliver exceptional customer service through in-store visibility and proactivity to customer needs through knowledge and understanding of health and supplements.&lt;br /&gt;
 To consult with customers and provide suitable advice on healthcare, nutritional and supplement products.&lt;br /&gt;
 To drive healthcare sales in line with targets through promotion of a broad range of brands by cross selling and upselling to increase profitability.&lt;br /&gt;
 To drive stock availability in the healthcare aisles through compliance with stock management principles and procedures in order to drive sales.&lt;br /&gt;
 To prevent wastage in own area by adhering to stock rotation principles.&lt;br /&gt;
 To prevent stock losses by following all risk management policies and principles.&lt;br /&gt;
 To ensure high standards of hygiene and cleanliness within the store in order to create an appealing shopping environment for customers.&lt;br /&gt;
 To assist in product merchandising by following the merchandising guidelines and procedures.&lt;br /&gt;
 To adhere to all store standard operating procedures.&lt;br /&gt;
 To ensure continuity of service by focusing on own development and product knowledge and sharing product information with relief staff.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Requirements&lt;br /&gt;
Job Knowledge:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
 Essential: Basic health, fitness and supplements product knowledge&lt;br /&gt;
 Essential: Basic knowledge of retail store operations principles (stock management, merchandising, risk management,)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Job Related Skills:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
 Essential: Good communication and interaction skills&lt;br /&gt;
 Essential: Customer and service orientation&lt;br /&gt;
 Essential: Selling skills&lt;br /&gt;
 Essential: Merchandising skills&lt;br /&gt;
 Desirable: Basic computer literacy&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Job Experience:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
 Essential: At least 1 year related experience&lt;br /&gt;
 Essential: Experience working with sports nutrition and vitamin related products&lt;br /&gt;
 Essential: Selling skills; customer related training&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Education:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
 Essential: Matric&lt;br /&gt;
 Essential: Matric 50% Maths or 60% Maths Literacy, 50% English and a pass in Life or Physical Science&lt;br /&gt;
 Desirable: Sports / fitness / nutrition qualification&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Competencies&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Essential&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
 Relating and Networking&lt;br /&gt;
 Persuading and Influencing&lt;br /&gt;
 Following Instructions and Procedures&lt;br /&gt;
 Delivering Results and Meeting Customer Expectations&lt;br /&gt;
 Presenting and Communicating Information&lt;br /&gt;
 Achieving Personal Work Goals and Objectives&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Desirable&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
 Coping with Pressures and Setbacks&lt;br /&gt;
 Adapting and Responding to Change&lt;br /&gt;
 Adhering to Principles and Values&lt;br /&gt;
 Planning and Organising&lt;br /&gt;
 Working with People</description><url>https://za.jobsora.com/job-1657970873</url><city>Pretoria</city><country>South Africa</country><date>2020-10-30</date></job>
</source>