<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><source><lastBuildDate>2020-10-28 11:43:02</lastBuildDate>
<job><id>3845551907</id><company>Communicate Recruitment: Finance 1</company><title>Newly Qualified Chartered Accountants</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Skills &amp;amp; Experience: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Minimum 0 - 4 years experience&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualification:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;BCom Accounting with outstanding transcripts&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SAIPA/SAICA Articles Completed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Board 1 and 2 Exams Completed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CA(SA)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Contact&lt;strong&gt; KYLE HAGGLUND &lt;/strong&gt;on &lt;strong&gt;021 418 1750&lt;/strong&gt;, quoting the Ref: &lt;strong&gt;CTF012770.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Connect with us on &lt;/p&gt;</description><url>https://za.jobsora.com/job-3845551907</url><city>Cape Town</city><country>South Africa</country><date>2020-10-28</date></job><job><id>3845551909</id><company>Communicate Recruitment: Finance 3</company><title>Cost Accountant</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualification and Experience Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;BCom&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;CIMA complete&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 2 years experience within a similar role either in Pharmaceuticals or Manufacturing&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Expeience with ABC Costing&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Must have strong experience with BOM and variance analysis&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you meet the above requirements and would like more information, Contact us immediately.&lt;/p&gt;</description><url>https://za.jobsora.com/job-3845551909</url><city>Johannesburg</city><country>South Africa</country><date>2020-10-28</date></job><job><id>3845551911</id><company>The Recruitment People</company><title>Financial Manager</title><description>&lt;p&gt;A global services company is searching for a Financial Manager for one of their divisions in the East Rand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Job Description:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The candidate will be responsible for the Financial Management function, including but not limited to the following:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Overseeing the full accounting function for the division.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Monthly management reports.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Presenting the financial reports to top management.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Provide commentary to enable top management to make strategic business decisions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Management of staff.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;BCom degree&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Around 5 years experience.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent presentation skills.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Benefits are negotiable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Thank you for submitting your CV. We will assess your suitability for the existing vacancies and retain your CV in our database in accordance with the Protection of Personal Information Policy. We will contact you should your CV be suitable for any available positions. You have the right to &quot;Opt-Out&quot; of electronic communications from us at any time and you also have the right to request us to delete your information by sending a request to &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><url>https://za.jobsora.com/job-3845551911</url><city>Johannesburg</city><country>South Africa</country><date>2020-10-28</date></job><job><id>3845551913</id><company>First Point Group</company><title>Human Resource/Employee Relations Management Professional</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Skills and experience required (Non-negotiable):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;10 years of HRM work experience in SA&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Labour Relations: Grievance, Disciplinary, CCMA, Performance Improvement &amp;amp; reviews&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Compliance: Employment Equity, COID, UIF, IRP5 recons&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Membership: Employment Equity, MANCO, Training Committee&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;B-BBEE: Tenders, Strategy implementation, Employment Equity Targets, Empowering Supplier targets, Headcounts, HR docs for B-BBEE audit, Policies, Job Grading, Employment Equity Policy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Occupational Health, Safety and Quality: EHS and Quality (audits), Quality document control, IOD&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Policies / Templates: HR legal register, Manage policies as per Law/company, Draft new policies as per Law/company&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Local Talent Development: Local high-end talent retention, etc.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Outsourcing company management: General Management of PSL, meeting &amp;amp; reviews with HRBPs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications Required:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Degree in HR Management&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work with HRD as the senior partner for local affairs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Training &amp;amp; development of staff on labour relations&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Staff welfare&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Assist with corporate visa applications&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Present at Employees Orientation Programmes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Manage Top Employer survey&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><url>https://za.jobsora.com/job-3845551913</url><city>Johannesburg</city><country>South Africa</country><date>2020-10-28</date></job><job><id>3845551915</id><company>Rosstone Consulting</company><title>PMO Lead</title><description>The Role: &lt;p&gt;We are looking for an experienced PMO Lead for a 12-month fixed term contract for our client in Mpumalanga.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Â &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are looking for your 10 years work experience within heavy industry, mining and production environment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Â &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are looking for your Project Management experience in applying Lean methodology in a project management environment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Â &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum educational level: Â  Â  Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â  &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;BEng Engineering&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Government Certificate of Competence: Engineering&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Certificate Project Management&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lean Six Sigma Black Belt&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;Skills and Experience: &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Purpose of the role:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Establish and operationalise a Project Management Office (PMO) function, with a key focus on driving the PMO function and continuous improvement initiatives.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Manage continuous improvement reporting, develop and implement robust processes, manage the overall governance and tracking of projects.Â &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;To direct and manage project development for duration of projects phases.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;To develop project plans and estimate resources needed to achieve project goals through the implementation of Lean principles.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Engage with Stakeholders.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The PMO Lead is the functional leader of project delivery and governance across the projects. Provide advice and guidance, monitoring and assurance, advocacy and education with respect to programmes, projects, and their delivery, at all levels.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Reporting framework focussed on value added advice and early identification of risk and issues for all major programmes and projects across the organisation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Support identification of improvement areas and solution development.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Â &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Coordinate site operations readiness team interfacing with the project to ensure the delivery of key project milestones. This includes ensuring critical milestones are met, providing visual management on progress and problem solving with the work stream teams to mitigate risks or project delays.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Create and execute project work plans and revise to meet changing project needs and requirements.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Creating action plans to manage risk to the operations.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ensure document control via centralised capturing system specified.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Implement controls to ensure legal compliance.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Apply controls to ensure legal and best practice compliance in accordance with MHSA (Mine Health and Safety Act), MPRDA (Mineral and Petroleum Resources Development Act), OHSA (Occupational Health and Safety Act) where applicable&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Implement effective SHE management systems for project.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adhere to Enterprise Project Management (EPM) Standards and requirements of quality management systems.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ensure compliance to environmental Record of Decision (RoD).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Manage and ensure optimal use of budget allocated to project.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Advise on selection of project recovery team members.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Report on the optimization and improvement projects to the mega project manager to ensure targets and initiatives are met.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Provide inputs for planning and recommendations for staff to be efficiently deployed and identify areas of further development (projects and training).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;Key Accountabilities: &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We require your 10 Yearsâ?? work experience with the following D&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;uties and Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Audit projects and programmes for project progress against agreed tolerances&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Audit Project support offices to ensure adhere to Corporate Governance with regards to processes, systems, guidelines and templates&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Update knowledge of project management best practice&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Participate in evaluation of discipline-specific standards, principles and practice to enable planning, design and implementation of project outcomes that support business strategy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Contribute to development and implementation of an appropriate approach to knowledge management for discipline in line with business needs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Provide and participate in governance systems for best practice&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Keep abreast with developments in Lean principles&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Create working relationships with project managers and other Project Management Offices (PMO)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Identify resources needed and assigns individual responsibilities&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Take action to mitigate and manage risks that can impact on project&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Identify and manage project dependencies and critical path&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Supervise and ensure execution of projects in adherence to agreed SLA&apos;&apos;s and service delivery standards&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work directly with the work stream leads to develop detailed robust operational readiness plans are developed by each function to ensure they are aligned and integrated across the site and with the project and provide regular visibility on progress.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Create an environment of right first time in everything that we do through a focus on principles of lean including simplification, standard work, visual management and a learning organisation as part of the establishment of the site PMO&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Be accountable for a robust investigation process to drive to right first time&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ensure Regional Project Support Office (RPSO) conduct periodic audits on projects responsibility&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Represent the PMO office at appropriate conferences, seminars and other events&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Maintain and ensure healthy environment, safe operations and practices, ensuring compliance with all applicable SHE policies and procedures in line with set standards&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Encourage culture that focuses on safety in all operations&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><url>https://za.jobsora.com/job-3845551915</url><city>Johannesburg</city><country>South Africa</country><date>2020-10-28</date></job><job><id>3845551917</id><company>Elmich Consultants</company><title>R&amp;D Manager from Food Manufacturing/bakery focus. R1 Mill CTC Johannesburg</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Masters in Food Technology, Nutritional Sciences and perhaps some quality management. Minimum 8 years&apos;&apos;expereince in R &amp;amp;D from Food Manufacturing environment, focus bakery technology. Handling of multi-projects simultaneously. Staff management as will have 5 R&amp;amp;D staff reporting.Advanced Excel, food markets trends knowledge, competency in food safety management systems, labelling, ingredients and back of pack information and all the necessary S.A. legislations. Skills for costing and capacity calculations and evluation stats. Experience in product development from brief, lab to final product and sensory evaluation. Food Safety team member - GMP, HACCP, ISO Standards.&lt;/p&gt;</description><url>https://za.jobsora.com/job-3845551917</url><city>Johannesburg</city><country>South Africa</country><date>2020-10-28</date></job><job><id>3845551919</id><company>Toro Human Capital</company><title>SAP Functional Consultant</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Intermediate Consultant  between 5 and 10 years working experience&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Senior Consultant  10+ years working experience at a managerial / team lead level&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Willingness to Travel (4 days / week)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Relevant qualification (IT / Math / etc.), university preferred&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Office Skills (Word, Excel, PPT)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Technical Affinity &amp;amp; Experience&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Basic SQL / Database Knowledge&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;XML, UML, etc.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Basic Linux&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;     Retail Process Knowledge (Retail Experience)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;POS / Backoffice&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;ERP / Store processes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of POS / ERP products&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;    Product Skills (POS / Backoffice, OMS ...)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Processes / Functions / Features&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Configuration&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Integration / Interfaces&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;     SAP Product Skills&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;THEY OFFER:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A cooperative work environment offering the scope for individual ideas, creativity and concepts&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The latest technology in the workplace, an international feel, continued employee development and training&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Employee benefits, a safe working environment and facilities to make everyday life easier&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><url>https://za.jobsora.com/job-3845551919</url><city>Johannesburg</city><country>South Africa</country><date>2020-10-28</date></job><job><id>3718999831</id><company>Tedroox Technologies Pvt.Ltd</company><title>Fullstack Developer (MERN Stack)</title><description>A full-stack developer handles both: Front-end and Back-end.&lt;br /&gt;need to build web pages, websites, create UI, make the website simple and attractive.Ã‚Â Your primary focus will be on developing user interface components and implementing them following well-known React.js workflows (such as Flux or Redux) along with CSS3 and HTML5.&lt;br /&gt;You will ensure that these components and the overall application are robust and easy to maintain.&lt;br /&gt;You will coordinate with the rest of the team working on different layers of the infrastructure.&lt;br /&gt;Therefore, a commitment to collaborative problem solving, sophisticated design, and quality product is important.Ã‚Â Ã‚Â React Native, MongoDB, Node JS Knowledge is a plus.Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Ã‚Â ResponsibilitiesÃ‚Â Design the overall architecture of the web application.Maintain quality and ensure the responsiveness of applications.Collaborate with the rest of the engineering team to design and launch new features.Maintain code integrity and organization.Experience working with graphic designers and converting designs to visual elements.Understanding and implementation of security and data protection.Ã‚Â Ã‚Â QualificationsÃ‚Â Graduation/ masters in computer scienceGood communicationMinimum 1 years of experience in mobile application and web application development.Front end Skills: Html, CSS, JavaScript ES6, React JS, react-native.Back end skills: Node Js, Mongo DB (Added advantage) Skills:- Javascript, PHP, NodeJS (Node.js), MongoDB, HTML/CSS, React Native and React.js</description><url>https://in.jobsora.com/job-3718999831</url><city>Bengaluru</city><country>India</country><salary>700000</salary><currency>INR</currency><date>2020-10-21</date></job><job><id>3718999837</id><company>Stanza Living</company><title>Frontend Developer</title><description>Â¢ Good with Data Structures and Algorithms.Â¢ Javascript, Angular 2.0, React, React Native, Angular Ionic (optional), JQuery, MYSQL,MongoDB, Firebase.Â¢ Comfortable with REST API development using Java or python.Â¢ Exposure to Artificial Intelligence / Machine Learning concepts will be a plus.&lt;br /&gt;Skills:- Javascript, HTML/CSS, Angular (2+), React.js and React Native</description><url>https://in.jobsora.com/job-3718999837</url><city>New Delhi</city><country>India</country><salary>2600000</salary><currency>INR</currency><date>2020-10-21</date></job><job><id>3718999851</id><company>Capgemini</company><title>Windows with Active Directory</title><description>&lt;b&gt; Job Description&lt;/b&gt;   Experience in designing, solutioning &amp;amp; Migrating Active Directory, Windows &amp;amp; End points  Strong familiarity with DNS &amp;amp; DHCP systems and Migration of services from AD to any platform  Good Knowledge of and experience with Active Directory &amp;amp; windows in a large corporate environment  Good knowledge and experience in AD assessment in terms of OU delegation, GPOs, permission etc.,  Expertise in Active Directory versions 2003, 2008R2, 2012R2 &amp;amp; 2016  Good knowledde and hands on experience in setting up lab based on the solution requirements  Good knowledge on Virtualization platforms  Good knowledge and hands on experience in AD disaster recovery  Good Knowledge on Active Directory &amp;amp; windows audit logs  Good knowledge on Networking, DNS, DHCP, DFS &amp;amp; Network load balancer  Good knowledge on Cryptography, certificates, PKI, symmetric, asymmetric keys, Encryption &amp;amp; hash algorithms  Good knowledge on AD authentication protocols Kerberos, NTLM, LDAP, LDAPS &amp;amp; LDAP-Start TLS  Good knowledge on Network log capturing &amp;amp; analyzing the logs through the tools Wireshark, Tshark, Microsoft NM etc.,  Good knowledge on application integration with LDAP &amp;amp; Kerberos i.e. Keytab, krb5 etc.,  Good knowledge on AD migration tools like ADMT, Quest etc.,&lt;br /&gt; Â   &lt;b&gt; Primary Skills&lt;/b&gt;   Active directory  &lt;b&gt; Secondary Skills&lt;/b&gt;   Windows</description><url>https://in.jobsora.com/job-3718999851</url><city>Chennai</city><country>India</country><date>2020-10-21</date></job><job><id>3718999855</id><company>Intel</company><title>Graphics Software Engineer</title><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;b&gt; Job Description&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt; Responsible for developing multiple aspects of graphics software, display driver development and simulation environment development. Works with various partners to enhance and improve graphics performance on upcoming processor graphics devices by analyzing performance issues in software drivers and applications, implementing software performance improvements, and recommending future hardware &amp;amp; software improvements. Also responsible for providing internal and external feedback to implement upcoming graphics features in yet-to-be-released OSes to ensure our hardware and software will function and perform as expected on next generation platforms as well as designing/developing/implementing graphics system-level software for future platforms.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt; Qualifications&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; Master or Bachelor of Engineering degree in Electronics or Computer Engineering with 2 to 6 years of experience. Should have good understanding of Computer architecture(IA), micro controller/microprocessor, device driver (preferably graphic driver), windows components. Ability to understand and interpret graphics &amp;amp; display driver requirements. Should be self-motivated and should have open mindset to change &amp;amp; should be able to multitask effectively. A self-starter with the ability to work effectively both independently and in a team across multiple Geos. Excellent analytical ability, problem solving and communication skills (verbal and written). Should have right attitude to work with Intelâ€™s customers/OEMs (Japan, China, Taiwan etc.). Hands on experience using windbg and windows debugging tools would be added advantage. Experience in customer support and system level understanding would be added advantage. Good understanding of Display graphics driver / Media / 3D /Audio would be added advantage. Familiarity with agile methodologies like Scrum or Kanban will be added advantage.&lt;/p&gt;</description><url>https://in.jobsora.com/job-3718999855</url><city>Bengaluru</city><country>India</country><date>2020-10-21</date></job><job><id>3718999859</id><company>CouponDunia</company><title>Senior Software Engineer (PHP)</title><description>2 - 6 yrs of relevant experience in any coding language, PHP would be preferred.&lt;br /&gt;Proficient with full development stack (MySQL, Redis, Memcached, MVC frameworks, jQuery, Server Administration, CSS, HTML, etc) and understanding of OOP design, AJAX, jQuery, and MySQLUnderstands how to build an optimized web app and has experience with caching and other scaling techniquesThe desire and energy to work long hours so that we can continuously improve our website at the quickest pace possiblePassionate about working in a startup and creating a great productMust love to program, must be willing to learn, and must be creative.&lt;br /&gt;If you are the type of person who finds learning a new technology or language an exhilarating experience, you will love it here.Must be able to show us projects and or websites that you have created.&lt;br /&gt;Bonus points if youve created these projects/websites outside of your work (we love seeing proof of how much you love technology and coding).Education - relevant degree in Engineering preferable Skills:- MySQL, PHP, Algorithms, Data Structures, Redis, Python and Java</description><url>https://in.jobsora.com/job-3718999859</url><city>Mumbai</city><country>India</country><salary>2500000</salary><currency>INR</currency><date>2020-10-21</date></job><job><id>3718999861</id><company>ISURAKSHA SOLUTIONS PVT LTD</company><title>UX Designer</title><description>We&apos;re iSuraksha Solutions Pvt.&lt;br /&gt;Ltd., a leading company in geo &amp;amp; GPS tracking  technology.&lt;br /&gt;We are obsessed with technology with a vision of future.&lt;br /&gt;Working to make better products with our better research programs in order to simplify some of the most important tasks in your everyday life.&lt;br /&gt;Skills:- User Experience (UX) Design, HTML/CSS and Adobe Photoshop</description><url>https://in.jobsora.com/job-3718999861</url><city>Pune</city><country>India</country><salary>300000</salary><currency>INR</currency><date>2020-10-21</date></job><job><id>3718999863</id><company>Hucon Solutions</company><title>Backend Developer</title><description>Looking for a candidate who holds a rich experience in the following programming languages: If you are interested please forward me your updated resume.- MY SQL- JavaScript- Core PHP- Linux- LaravelAdditional Skills (Anyone is required):- Elastic search- MongoDB- RedisRoles &amp;amp; Responsibilities :- Experience in working with REST APIs, OAuth, etc.- Well versed with cross-browser development fundamentals- Experience in building dashboards is a plus- Experience in working on scalable systems is a plus- Experience in building dashboards is a plus (based on jQuery Datatables)- Compile and analyse data, processes, and codes to troubleshoot problems and identify areas for improvement.- Developing ideas for new programs, products, or features by monitoring industry developments and trends.- Flexible working hours, a friendly work environment and lots moreImmediate Joiners Preferred Skills:- PHP, MongoDB, Redis, Elastic Search, Laravel, MySQL, Linux/Unix, Javascript and core php</description><url>https://in.jobsora.com/job-3718999863</url><city>Haryana</city><country>India</country><salary>500000</salary><currency>INR</currency><date>2020-10-21</date></job><job><id>3718999867</id><company>Accenture in India</company><title>Java Enterprise Edition Application Developer</title><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;b&gt; Job Description&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;b&gt; About Accenture: &lt;/b&gt; Accenture is a leading global professional services company, providing a broad range of services in strategy and consulting, interactive, technology and operations, with digital capabilities across all of these services. We combine unmatched experience and specialized capabilities across more than 40 industries â€” powered by the worldâ€™s largest network of Advanced Technology and Intelligent Operations centers. With 513,000 people serving clients in more than 120 countries, Accenture brings continuous innovation to help clients improve their performance and create lasting value across their enterprises.</description><url>https://in.jobsora.com/job-3718999867</url><city>Bengaluru</city><country>India</country><date>2020-10-21</date></job><job><id>3718999873</id><company>Ethx.co</company><title>Community Manager</title><description>ResponsibilitiesManage, Moderate and Grow Telegram Group and Forum.&lt;br /&gt;Hire and manage a team of interns for community and content.&lt;br /&gt;Organise events in various cities.&lt;br /&gt;Speak at events.&lt;br /&gt;Source influencers and moderate weekly AMA sessions.&lt;br /&gt;Manage Social Media Pages and Postings.&lt;br /&gt;Design and Send a weekly newsletter to users.&lt;br /&gt;Source and implement various Growth Hacks.&lt;br /&gt;Develop and nurture blogger community.&lt;br /&gt;Mobilize community.&lt;br /&gt;Content creation.&lt;br /&gt;Skills:- Content Management System (CMS), Content Writing and Blogging</description><url>https://in.jobsora.com/job-3718999873</url><city>New Delhi</city><country>India</country><salary>500000</salary><currency>INR</currency><date>2020-10-21</date></job><job><id>3718999875</id><company>Careator Technologies Pvt Ltd</company><title>Javascript Developer/leads</title><description>Permanent positions with a product customerEssential Skills:10+ years experience in JavaScript and web technology such as CSSProject experience in building solutions out with the React JavaScript Framework3+ years at Lead Developer LevelInterest in, or experience of, mobile solution development (i.e.&lt;br /&gt;worked as part of a team to deliver a mobile application)Desire to develop applications on NoSQL technologyUnderstanding of software engineering design patternsInterest in or experience of Enterprise level solution development (i.e.&lt;br /&gt;understanding of web security protocols and understanding of typical enterprise security solutions)Experience of the full software development lifecycleProven experience in designing and building solutions from scratchTeam leadingSystems software design, assurance and best practiceRelease planningTest strategy definitionSoftware deployment architecture designAdvantageous:Experience of NoSQL technology (i.e.&lt;br /&gt;CouchBase)Experience of JS frameworks such as React Native/React WebExperience of Xamarin app developmentExperience of Umbraco, Sitecore or other CMS solutionsExperience of Azure solution deployment and developmentAppreciation of business needs in e-commerce Skills:- Javascript, HTML/CSS, jQuery, AJAX, AngularJS (1.x), React.js, Backbone.js and .NET</description><url>https://in.jobsora.com/job-3718999875</url><city>New Delhi</city><country>India</country><salary>2000000</salary><currency>INR</currency><date>2020-10-21</date></job><job><id>3718999883</id><company>Media Magic Technologies Pvt Ltd</company><title>Codec Developer</title><description>Great exposure to their technical skills.&lt;br /&gt;Skills:- Codec, gstreamer, gdb, C++, Linux/Unix, TCP/IP and C</description><url>https://in.jobsora.com/job-3718999883</url><city>Pune</city><country>India</country><salary>1000000</salary><currency>INR</currency><date>2020-10-21</date></job><job><id>3718999891</id><company>Serigor Inc.</company><title>Azure/ETL Integration Consultant</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Location - Anywhere in India&lt;/b&gt;Â &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Our approach is to hire someone in India who has experience in working for top notch consulting firms and is looking to change. We will be providing assistance with Canadian PR.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are seeking an Azure consultant who had cloud ETL integration experience (any cloud ETL is fine)&lt;br /&gt;Candidate should have 5 years experience working with Accenture, Deloitte, Cognizant in India.Â &lt;br /&gt;Hands-on experience in Azure SQL, Azure EDW and Azure data factory&lt;br /&gt;Familiarity with BI technologies (e.g. Microsoft Power BI, Tableau)&lt;br /&gt;In-depth understanding of database management systems, online analytical processing (OLAP) and ETL (Extract, transform, load) framework.&lt;br /&gt;Ability to work in Agile and Waterfall environment, requirements gathering and documentation including flow diagrams&lt;br /&gt;Strong technical and analytical skills&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Powered by JazzHR&lt;/p&gt;</description><url>https://in.jobsora.com/job-3718999891</url><country>India</country><date>2020-10-21</date></job><job><id>3718999893</id><company>Accenture in India</company><title>Informatica Cloud Application Developer</title><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;b&gt; Job Description&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;b&gt; About Accenture: &lt;/b&gt; Accenture is a leading global professional services company, providing a broad range of services in strategy and consulting, interactive, technology and operations, with digital capabilities across all of these services. We combine unmatched experience and specialized capabilities across more than 40 industries â€” powered by the worldâ€™s largest network of Advanced Technology and Intelligent Operations centers. With 513,000 people serving clients in more than 120 countries, Accenture brings continuous innovation to help clients improve their performance and create lasting value across their enterprises.</description><url>https://in.jobsora.com/job-3718999893</url><city>Pune</city><country>India</country><date>2020-10-21</date></job><job><id>3718999899</id><company>Western Union</company><title>Senior Associate, Solution Engineering (DevOps)</title><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;b&gt; Senior Associate, Solution Engineering (DevOps)&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/p&gt;    IND - Pune   &lt;p&gt; &lt;b&gt; Senior Associate, Solution Engineering â€“ Pune, India&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Want to do work on a massively global scale with a fintech company that is poised to revolutionize the industry?Â Come join our growing team and help shape our companyâ€™s digital capabilities and revolutionize an industry! Join Western Union as Senior Associate, Solution Engineering.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;b&gt; Motivated by our values: purpose driven, globally minded, and trustworthy &amp;amp; respectful&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Weâ€™re a FinTech thatâ€™s using insight from customers and colleagues worldwide to improve financial services for families, small businesses, multinational corporations, and non-profit organizations. Weâ€™re a team of over 10,000 people spanning 200 countries and territories. We believe when money moves, better things happen.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;b&gt; Better requires process discipline and simplification&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; You will create, manage, and own automation tools and scripts, configuration management of platform technologies. Your focus will be to monitor continuous integration build systems and proactively debug issues working closely with the development and support teams. You will be involved in planning the deployment in conjunction with change management, configuration management, and knowledge management processes in the organization.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; For this role, you will come with a Bachelorâ€™s degree and 7+ years of experience in software engineering with extensive experience in Build &amp;amp; Release management for applications hosted in On-prem and Cloud environments. You should know Core Java and have hands-on experience working with DevOps tools - Git/Gitlab, Jenkins, Gradle, Rundeck, Ansible, Redhat Linux configuration, and management. You will also have experience with Repository Management (Archiva, JFrog), Containers (Docker, Kubernetes, AWS Fargate), RDBMS (DB2, MySQL) which is mandatory, NoSQL (Couchbase) will be preferred. AWS certification will be a plus for this role.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;b&gt; Join us, and let us move money for better&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; Western Union is transforming its business and shaping the financial services sector by driving quality, convenience, and customer service to new levels of excellence. Itâ€™s an exciting time for our organization, as the largest cross-border money transfer operator, trusted by millions of consumers around the world. If youâ€™re ready to unleash your potential to help drive change through bottom-up innovation, apply now.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; Weâ€™re a company on the move, and we want our people to grow and develop. Youâ€™ll have plenty of opportunities to learn new skills and build a career, as well as a great salary and benefits package.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; We are passionate about our diversity. Our commitment is to provide an inclusive culture that celebrates the unique backgrounds and perspectives of our global teams, while reflecting the communities we serve. We do not discriminate on the basis of race, color, national origin, religion, political affiliation, sex (including pregnancy), sexual orientation, gender identity, age, disability, marital status, or veteran status.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; #LI-TK1&lt;/p&gt;</description><url>https://in.jobsora.com/job-3718999899</url><city>Pune</city><country>India</country><date>2020-10-21</date></job><job><id>3718999903</id><company>Rejolut Technology Solutions Pvt Ltd.</company><title>React Native Developer</title><description>Rejolut is one of the award winning fastest growing emerging tech company which is working on leading technology like Blockchian, ML &amp;amp; AI, Complex mobile &amp;amp; web apps, IoT etc.The ideal candidate will be responsible for developing highly scalable and secure code.Responsibilities:--Able to take the Extreme Ownership of modules/product/projects-Able to learn &amp;amp; implement new technology/framework/library at God Speed-Able to come with optimal solution for the business problem-Can handle calls with the client &amp;amp; customer to know their feedback-Writing clean code &amp;amp; able to dig into other&apos;s code or open source code.-Build pixel-perfect, buttery smooth UIs across both mobile platforms.-Leverage native APIs for deep integrations with both platforms.-Diagnose and fix bugs and performance bottlenecks for performance that feels native.-Reach out to the open source community to encourage and help implement mission-critical software fixesReact Native moves fast and often breaks things.-Maintain code and write automated tests to ensure the product is of the highest quality.-Transition existing React web apps to React NativeDesired Candidate Profile:-Firm grasp of the JavaScriptÃ‚Â (and TypeScript or ClojureScript)Ã‚Â language and its nuances, including ES6+ syntaxKnowledge ofÃ‚Â (functional or object-oriented)Ã‚Â programmingAbility to write well-documented, clean Javascript codeRock solid at working with third-party dependencies and debugging dependency conflictsFamiliarity with native build tools, like XCode, GradleÃ‚Â (Android Studio, IntelliJ)Understanding of REST APIs, the document request model, and offline storageTransition existing apps to React Native and work with native modules when required.Experience in releasing Android and iOS App storeExperience working with Swift, Objective C, and Java a plus but not requiredHow we are differentÃ‚Â Ã‚Â -We are young and dynamic team who are obsessed with solving business problem at scale -We are a technology agnostic company who focus more on finding the optimal solution to business problem rather than technologyÃ‚Â Why to join usÃ‚Â -We provide huge learning curve.&lt;br /&gt;Spending 1.5-2 years with us will put you 3 years ahead in the career-We work only on cutting edge technology like React, React Native, Flutter, NodeJS, Python, Go, Svelte, ELM-There are two technology Co-founder in the company ho are pretty much hands-on and have earlier bult the Consumer application which is downloaded millions of time and are in leadership position in copanies like Samsung, Purplle, Loylty Rewardz-Get mentored by the best in the industry-Flexible working hours-Perks best in the industry-Flat structure, no hierarchy Skills:- React Native, Android Development and iOS App Development</description><url>https://in.jobsora.com/job-3718999903</url><city>Navi Mumbai</city><country>India</country><salary>1500000</salary><currency>INR</currency><date>2020-10-21</date></job><job><id>3718999905</id><company>M U HR</company><title>Team Lead</title><description>Team Lead  OperationsÃ‚Â·Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Must have work experience in a BPO of 1 year as a Team LeadÃ‚Â·Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Should be fluent in English and Hindi (able to clear Versant 4)Ã‚Â·Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Open to rotational shifts and week off Ã‚Â (24/7 process)Ã‚Â·Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Ã‚Â 6 day workingÃ‚Â·Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Experience in Inbound callingÃ‚Â·Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Managing a team of at least 15 callersÃ‚Â·Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Ã‚Â Must have qualities of a good leader Skills:- Team Management, Team leadership and Team building</description><url>https://in.jobsora.com/job-3718999905</url><city>Chennai</city><country>India</country><salary>3500000</salary><currency>INR</currency><date>2020-10-21</date></job>
</source>