<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<channel><ad><id><![CDATA[11995]]></id><url><![CDATA[https://us.jobs4it.pt/jobs/11995/hr-risk-planning-analytics-manager-qbe-sun-prairie-wi]]></url><title><![CDATA[HR Risk, Planning & Analytics Manager - QBE - Sun Prairie, WI]]></title><content><![CDATA[Provide reporting and analysis expertise, execute contract management activities and partner with HR leaders and Finance to enhance business decision-making. Mitigate risk across all aspects of HR and ensure compliance with regulatory requirements and compliance programs.
Primary Responsibilities
Manage the HR Risk Control Assessment, Controls Assurance and Business Impact Assessment processes and collaborate with Global HR as appropriate
Serve as first point of contact with Compliance, Risk and Legal on regulatory compliance matters across all aspects of HR
Accountable for cyclical HR budget and forecasting efforts by partnering with Finance and key stakeholders within Group HR to meet and understand reporting guidelines and deadlines
Perform data analysis and identify trends by developing knowledge of data available and applying those findings into presentations and reports; partner with HR team to understand business requests and anticipate future needs
Communicate and provide technical advice and guidance to senior leadership by utilizing expertise to share information related to HR, financial systems and other management data in order to support understanding, communication, and management of HR budgets and expenses
Optimize efficiency by identifying opportunities to improve, recommending solutions and providing relevant information to key decision makers to streamline and standardize processes
Manage all HR contracts by partnering with Procurement on negotiations, obtaining all necessary approvals and ensuring expenses are aligned with the HR budget
Oversee the production of required reports with HR analyst; provide insight on complex matters and ensure adherence to industry best practice
Required Qualifications
Education: Bachelor's Degree or equivalent combination of education and work experience
Experience: 6 years relevant experience
Preferred Qualifications
Licenses/Certifications: Certified Management Accountant (CMA); Project Management Professional (PMP); Senior Professional in Human Resources (SPHR)
Preferred Knowledge
Relevant trends, standards, best practices and information within the industry
Strong quantitative analysis
Advanced working knowledge of Microsoft Excel
Strong business acumen
Familiarity with HR processes and procedures
Preferred Competencies/Skills
Identify complex problems and review related information to develop and evaluate options and implement solutions
Foresee potential obstacles and challenges, identify root cause and strategize plans to address
Evaluate the outcome of a project and interpret the results and their implications
Quickly change direction when working on multiple projects or issues
Multi-task and handle competing priorities
Provide personalized and quality service to meet the expectations of internal and external customers
Clearly and confidently convey information to various audiences through speech and writing
Understand customer needs and goals actively look for ways to meet them
Create, maintain and ensure current, accurate and readily accessible data in various formats
Motivational, inspirational and enthusiastic approach to team involvement and engagement
Apply project management methodology and techniques to manage projects
Guide oneself with little or no supervision, and depend on oneself to get things done
Adapt and be flexible in a complex, changing environment
QBE Cultural DNA
Everything we do at QBE is underpinned by our DNA (which interlinks seven cultural elements) – because we know it's not just what we do that matters, it's how we do it that makes the difference. We expect all employees to role model and inspire the right behaviors that link to our cultural elements:
We are customer-centered
We are technical experts
We are diverse
We are fast-paced
We are courageous
We are accountable
We are a team
All employees are expected to adhere to QBE’s Code of Ethics and Conduct and apply sound risk management practices
Work environment
Travel frequency: Infrequent (approximately 1-4 trips annually)
Physical demands: General office jobs: Work is generally performed in an office environment in which there is not substantial exposure to adverse environmental conditions. Must have the ability to remain in a stationary position for extended periods of time. Must be able to operate basic office equipment including telephone, headset and computer. Incumbent must be able to lift basic office equipment up to 20 lbs.
To successfully perform this job, the individual must be able to perform each essential job
responsibility satisfactorily. Reasonable accommodations may be made to enable an individual with disabilities to perform the essential job responsibilities.
Number of Openings:
1
How to Apply:
To submit your application, click "Apply" and follow the step by step process.
Equal Employment Opportunity:
QBE is an equal opportunity employer and is required to comply with equal employment opportunity legislation in each jurisdiction it operates.]]></content><city><![CDATA[Sun Prairie]]></city><category><![CDATA[Analyst]]></category><company><![CDATA[QBE]]></company><date><![CDATA[07/05/2019]]></date></ad><ad><id><![CDATA[11994]]></id><url><![CDATA[https://us.jobs4it.pt/jobs/11994/quality-assurance-analyst-envolve-fresno-ca]]></url><title><![CDATA[Quality Assurance Analyst - Envolve - Fresno, CA]]></title><content><![CDATA[Develop and document test requirements, test design, and test plan reviews to match software features to user requirements.Work as part of agile teams to verify programming changes in various applications. Attend daily stand-up meetings and use JIRA to identify issues requiring quality assurance verification.
Consult with developers and stakeholders to develop test plans. Execute tests and communicate findings. Insure that implementation has met quality standards. Test execution would involve manual testing. Automated/programmatic testing would also be performed, depending on skill set of tester. Working on projects involving testing of web applications, verification of changes to custom letters used to communicate with providers and members and testing of stored procedures in Oracle database.
Develop test cases and scripts according to the specifications of the development team.Develop and implement functional test cases and test scripts of the application software, database upgrades, installation modifications, and infrastructure modifications and upgrades.Collaborate with business and technology leads to identify and prepare appropriate data for testingAssist in establishing and maintaining testing standards, processes, and systems that follow industry standards and common practice, including development of test plan templates and instructions, test environments, test software, test data, etc.Eliminate, document, and report defects in the test process as early in the systems development life cycle as possibleExecute Performance Tests and Stress and Load TestsCoordinate with appropriate stakeholders to resolve issues identified during testing and validate product corrections and fixes
Qualifications:Education/Experience:
Bachelor’s degree in IT, related field, or equivalent experience.
3+ years of software development life-cycle experience.
Experience with generally accepted QA methodologies and best practices.
General understanding of programming languages such as Oracle, Unix and JAVA preferred.
Preferred Skills and Experience:
2+ years of Database or programming experience
2+ years of experience creating test plans
Effective communication to gather information.
Background in either database work or programming.
Ability to work independently to formulate test strategy.
Attention to detail.
License/Certification: ITIL Certificate or obtain within 18 months of hire.]]></content><city><![CDATA[Fresno]]></city><category><![CDATA[Database]]></category><company><![CDATA[Envolve]]></company><date><![CDATA[07/05/2019]]></date></ad><ad><id><![CDATA[11993]]></id><url><![CDATA[https://us.jobs4it.pt/jobs/11993/data-ml-engineer-amazon-web-services-inc-united-states]]></url><title><![CDATA[Data & ML Engineer - Amazon Web Services, Inc. - United States]]></title><content><![CDATA[Bachelor’s degree, or equivalent experience, in Computer Science, Engineering, Mathematics or a related field8+ years’ experience of Data platform implementation, including 3+ years of hands-on experience in implementation and performance tuning Kinesis/Kafka/Spark/Storm implementations.Experience with analytic solutions applied to the Marketing or Risk needs of enterprisesBasic understanding of machine learning fundamentals.Ability to take Machine Learning models and implement them as part of data pipeline5+ years of IT platform implementation experience.Experience with one or more relevant tools ( Flink, Spark, Sqoop, Flume, Kafka, Amazon Kinesis ).Experience developing software code in one or more programming languages (Java, JavaScript, Python, etc).Current hands-on implementation experience requiredAbility to travel to client locations to deliver professional services when needed.
At Amazon Web Services (AWS), we’re hiring highly technical cloud computing architects and engineers to collaborate with our customers and partners on key engagements. Our consultants will develop and deliver proof-of-concept projects, technical workshops, and support implementation projects. These professional services engagements will focus on customer solutions such as Machine Learning, Data and Analytics, HPC and more.In this role, you will work with our partners, customers and focus on our AWS Analytics and ML service offerings such Amazon Kinesis, AWS Glue, Amazon Redshift, Amazon EMR, Amazon Athena, Amazon SageMaker and more. You will help our customers and partners to remove the constraints that prevent them from leveraging their data to develop business insights.AWS Professional Services engage in a wide variety of projects for customers and partners, providing collective experience from across the AWS customer base and are obsessed about customer success. Our team collaborates across the entire AWS organization to bring access to product and service teams, to get the right solution delivered and drive feature innovation based upon customer needs.In our Global Specialist Practice, you will also have the opportunity to create white papers, writing blogs, build demos and other reusable collateral that can be used by our customers, and, most importantly, you will work closely with our Solution Architects, Data Scientists and Service Engineering teams.The ideal candidate will have extensive experience with design, development and operations that leverages deep knowledge in the use of services like Amazon Kinesis, Apache Kafka, Apache Spark, Amazon Sagemaker, Amazon EMR, NoSQL technologies and other 3rd parties.Excellent business and communication skills are a must to develop and define key business questions and to build data sets that answer those questions. You should be able to work with business customers in understanding the business requirements and implementing solutions.
Masters or PhD in Computer Science, Physics, Engineering or Math.Hands on experience working on large-scale data science/data analytics projects.Ability to lead effectively across organizations.Ability to think strategically about business, product, and technical challenges in an enterprise environment.Hands-on experience with Data Analytics technologies such as AWS, Hadoop, Spark, Spark SQL, MLib or Storm/Samza.Implementing AWS services in a variety of distributed computing, enterprise environments.Proficiency with at least one the languages such as C++, Java, Scala or Python.Experience with at least one of the modern distributed Machine Learning and Deep Learning frameworks such as TensorFlow, PyTorch, MxNet Caffe, and Keras.Experience building large-scale machine-learning infrastructure that have been successfully delivered to customers.Experience defining system architectures and exploring technical feasibility trade-offs.3+ years experiences developing cloud software services and an understanding of design for scalability, performance and reliability.Experience working on a code base with many contributors.Ability to prototype and evaluate applications and interaction methodologies.Experience with AWS technology stack.Written and verbal technical communication skills with an ability to present complex technical information in a clear and concise manner to a variety of audiences.Amazon is an Equal Opportunity Employer – Minority / Women / Disability / Veteran / Gender Identity / Sexual Orientation / Age.Pursuant to the San Francisco Fair Chance Ordinance, we will consider for employment qualified applicants with arrest and conviction records.Pursuant to the Los Angeles Fair Chance Ordinance, we will considerfor employment qualified applicants with arrest and conviction records.]]></content><city><![CDATA[United States]]></city><category><![CDATA[Machine Learning]]></category><company><![CDATA[Amazon Web Services, Inc.]]></company><date><![CDATA[07/05/2019]]></date></ad><ad><id><![CDATA[11992]]></id><url><![CDATA[https://us.jobs4it.pt/jobs/11992/manager-third-party-risk-management-gateway-center-of-excellence-deloitte-detroit-mi]]></url><title><![CDATA[Manager - Third Party Risk Management Gateway - Center of Excellence - Deloitte - Detroit, MI]]></title><content><![CDATA[Manager - Third Party Risk Management Gateway – Center of Excellence
The Third Party Risk Management (TPRM) Gateway Center of Excellence (COE) is seeking a professional to oversee and manage various tasks related to the Deloitte U.S. Firms’ Risk and Regulatory Affairs (R&RA) risk management process and technology. The TPRM Gateway is a technology solution that facilitates performing risk-based due diligence on the Deloitte U.S. Firm’s third parties to address independence and business conflicts, corruption and trade risk, cyber security and data privacy risk, among other topics.
The Team
The TPRM Gateway COE’s mission is to manage the firm’s risk exposure related to third parties through enhanced risk management practices and automated capabilities and to provide the firm leadership with transparency into Deloitte’s third party ecosystem, risk exposure and risk decisions.Work you’ll do
TPRM Gateway COE Manager is expected to:
Gain comprehensive knowledge and understanding of Deloitte U.S. third party due diligence policies and guidelines
Centrally manage the TPRM framework and coordinate portfolio-wide TPRM activities
Coordinate with external providers and internal technology teams regarding platform development, enhancements, integration and issue resolution
Support reporting activity and analyzing metrics for performance
Manage presentations, communications and leadership updates
Identify issues for escalation to leadership
Independently manage workload and priorities with limited oversight and direction
Manage US and India resources in a remote environment
Represent COE with business teams, partners, others within the organization, and with external third parties
Liaison with the TPRM Gateway risk and compliance groups related to due diligence matters and system requests
Collaborate across Risk and Regulatory Affairs and other Enabling Areas teams to escalate issues and resolve issues
Work with global partners (e.g., DTTL member firms and venture partners) to advance TPRM Gateway goals
Drive select tasks supporting Third Party Relationship Management Strategic Initiative, including but not limited to:
Assist in developing and maintain TPRM program roadmap including: continuous improvements/process enhancements
Assist in developing and maintain TPRM program strategy (e.g., risk oversight and governance strategy, risk sensing) aligned with firm's strategy and risk appetite
Execute project management tasks and support Senior Manager and Partner
Facilitate TPRM Working Group with stakeholders (Procurement, OGC, risk & compliance groups) and management of significant events/incidents (e.g., coordinate with crisis management group, facilitate root-cause analysis of incidents)
Manage activities related to the TPRM Gateway, including but not limited to:
Manage US and USI team resources
Manage data analysis within the TPRM Gateway for reporting and other various diligence activities on third parties of Deloitte U.S.
Perform reviews of third party relationships escalated from various risk & compliance groups
Triage TPRM Gateway process, access or other related issues
Contact and respond to partner and third party inquiries as issues are escalated for your attention
Coordinate across Risk and Regulatory Affairs or other Enabling Areas
Represent COE directly with client service teams, partners, others within the organization, and with external third parties
Execute project management tasks and support COE leadership
Gather statistics and develop reports to monitor progress for presentations to senior leaders of the U.S. Firms
Design and manage other third party review activity as needed
Assist in driving enhancements to the TPRM Gateway, including but not limited to:
Assist in periodically assessing and evaluating the process, data analysis and reporting
Liaison with the TPRM Gateway risk & compliance groups on third party due diligence system requests
Recommend modifications to technology solution to meet COE, risk & compliance group and firm needs
Working with the Risk & Regulatory Affairs Technology team on enhancements (e.g., risk assessment changes, system email notifications)
Work with global partners (e.g., DTTL member firms and venture partners) to advance TPRM Gateway goals
Manage TPRM Gateway communications and training efforts, including but not limited to:
Continued development and maintenance of COE documents (policy, procedures, training and FAQs)
Continued improvements of necessary requirements and templates in coordination with other groups
Other tasks specifically supporting the development and implementation of guidance and processes to facilitate compliance, implementation, and operational efficiency of the TPRM Gateway.
Requirements includeMinimum of 6 years of experience working for a professional services organization providing one or more of the following: regulatory and compliance, audit, consulting, financial advisory, enterprise risk management and other related services.
Substantive direct experience in one or more of the following: third party due diligence, ethics and compliance programs, risk and controls, process management or change management
Substantive direct experience managing a team, with managing remote teams a plus
Bachelor’s degree in accounting, finance, business or related field
Experience with a global professional services firm a plus
Aptitude to learn and utilize technology (e.g. TPRM Gateway, Dun and Bradstreet (DnB) Supplier Evaluation Risk tool, and Arachnys) to perform and document responsibilities
Ability to work with technical tools including Microsoft Office applications, specifically Word, Excel, and PowerPoint
Excellent organizational aptitude
Ability to analyze problems and facilitate solutions
Excellent written and verbal communication skills
Detail-oriented with strong organization, prioritization and time management skills
Flexibility in working on several processes or projects simultaneously to meet team goals and responsibilities
High integrity to handle sensitive and confidential data
Ability to work accurately and efficiently under pressure
Proven ability to work independently and drive projects to completion with minimal oversight
Ability to work collaboratively with subject matter resources in often a virtual and cross border environment
Confidence and poise to work directly with partners, business teams and other firm leaders
Interest in effectively developing other colleagues and creating a culture of compliance, inclusion and professional growth
How you’ll grow
At Deloitte, our professional development plan focuses on helping people at every level of their career to identify and use their strengths to do their best work every day. From entry-level employees to senior leaders, we believe there’s always room to learn. We offer opportunities to help sharpen skills in addition to hands-on experience in the global, fast-changing business world. From on-the-job learning experiences to formal development programs, our professionals have a variety of opportunities to continue to grow throughout their career
Benefits
At Deloitte, we know that great people make a great organization. We value our people and offer employees a broad range of benefits. Learn more about what working at Deloitte can mean for you.
Deloitte’s culture
Our positive and supportive culture encourages our people to do their best work every day. We celebrate individuals by recognizing their uniqueness and offering them the flexibility to make daily choices that can help them to be healthy, centered, confident, and aware. We offer well-being programs and are continuously looking for new ways to maintain a culture where our people excel and lead healthy, happy lives. Learn more about Life at Deloitte.
Corporate citizenship
Deloitte is led by a purpose: to make an impact that matters. This purpose defines who we are and extends to relationships with our clients, our people and our communities. We believe that business has the power to inspire and transform. We focus on education, giving, skill-based volunteerism, and leadership to help drive positive social impact in our communities. Learn more about Deloitte’s impact on the world.
Recruiter tips
We want job seekers exploring opportunities at Deloitte to feel prepared and confident. To help you with your interview, we suggest that you do your research: know some background about the organization and the business area you’re applying to. Check out recruiting tips from Deloitte professionals.]]></content><city><![CDATA[Detroit]]></city><category><![CDATA[Cyber Security]]></category><company><![CDATA[Deloitte]]></company><date><![CDATA[07/05/2019]]></date></ad><ad><id><![CDATA[11991]]></id><url><![CDATA[https://us.jobs4it.pt/jobs/11991/software-development-manager-amazoncom-services-inc-bellevue-wa]]></url><title><![CDATA[Software Development Manager - Amazon.com Services, Inc. - Bellevue, WA]]></title><content><![CDATA[BS in Computer Science, Electrical Engineering, or related field8+ years of industry experience.8+ years of programming experience in Java or C++; in Linux, Windows, and/or Mac environment.Design/development skills including experience driving projects from concept to prototype to production
You will be working with a unique and gifted team developing new, exciting and cutting-edge products for consumers. The team is a multidisciplinary group of engineers, scientists, and business people engaged in a fast-paced mission to deliver these new products. The team faces a challenging task of balancing cost, schedule, technical invention, and performance requirements. You should be comfortable collaborating in a fast-paced and often uncertain environment, and contributing to innovative solutions, while demonstrating leadership and meticulousness. You should also be comfortable collaborating regularly with colleagues across many of Amazon’s current businesses, including devices, retail, and AWS.This is an early stage initiative with a fast paced, highly collaborative start up like environment inside Amazon. To be successful you need to be flexible and entrepreneurial, comfortable operating with ambiguity and willing to develop quick proof of concepts. You are a true owner - you are passionate about the potential customer and societal impact and will operate at all levels, diving deep into the details while providing strategic inputs for the product.We are building backend services, frontend UIs, apps, skills, scalable algorithms, and prototypes. You don’t need to be an expert in all of these, but the right candidate is excited and willing to learn to take on these challenges.Software Engineers at Amazon do so much more than just software development:Will work in an Agile/Scrum environment to deliver on-time, high-quality softwareResponsible for the development and maintenance of key system featuresDesigns scalable software systems that solve key business problems and contribute to scaling the businessKnowledge of professional software engineering practices & best practices for the full software development life cycle, including agile development, coding standards, code reviews, source control management, build processes, testing, and operationsTechnical leadership of large-sized technical projects with minimal supervisionTrack record of designing, building and delivering complex software systems
MS in Computer Science, Electrical Engineering, or related fieldExperience developing cloud software services and an understanding of design for scalability, performance and reliability, or experience building scalable, reliable applications on mobile platformsExperience creating advanced architectures and sustainable solutionsExperience defining system architectures and exploring technical feasibility trade-offsDemonstrated ability to mentor other software developers to maintain architectural vision and software qualityExcellence in technical communications with both technical and non-technical peersHighly innovative, self-directed and able to deal well with ambiguous problems]]></content><city><![CDATA[Bellevue]]></city><category><![CDATA[Agile Methodologies]]></category><company><![CDATA[Amazon.com Services, Inc.]]></company><date><![CDATA[07/05/2019]]></date></ad><ad><id><![CDATA[11990]]></id><url><![CDATA[https://us.jobs4it.pt/jobs/11990/product-manager-fulfillment-technology-amazoncom-services-inc-nashville-tn]]></url><title><![CDATA[Product Manager - Fulfillment Technology - Amazon.com Services, Inc. - Nashville, TN]]></title><content><![CDATA[Bachelor’s degree or higher with a technical discipline3-5+ years of product management experienceKnowledge of Product Management principlesExperience in working with Agile / Scrum / Kanban methodologiesExperience working on technical, developer-facing productsExperience working with cross-functional teams to deliver products and projects on tight deadlinesExperience coordinating product development cycles and software development schedulesStrong analytical and quantitative skills with the ability to use data and metrics to back up assumptions and recommendations
Do you want a unique, exciting opportunity to help build something from the ground up? We are looking for builders who thrive in ambiguity to join the leadership team of a new tech organization under Global Specialty Fulfillment.As a Product Manager for GSF Fulfillment Technology, you will be helping to define the future of this critical operational business lane at Amazon. You will craft a business strategy, feature set, and roadmap that will drive your creative vision forward and enable some of Amazon’s biggest brands to delight millions of customers. Your focus will be on the services that offer a full suite of digital capabilities that power some of Amazon’s most important initiatives.As a Product Manager, you will be responsible for the following:Innovating on behalf of our customersManaging the product life cycle from strategic planning to tactical executionDefine the feature sets, business requirements, measures of success, and roadmap for your productsPrioritizing engineering work while balancing the requirements of customers and stakeholdersEvangelizing the product both internally and externallyWorking with key stakeholders in the company to identify and drive product solutions to support sales, account management, operations, and customer supportDefining product requirements based on an intimate knowledge of the customer and technologyEstablishing product goals and reviewing success metrics to achieve commercial successHere are some qualities we are looking for:Be great fun to work with. At Amazon, we have a credo of “Work hard. Have fun. Make history”. In this role, you will love what you do, and instinctively know how to make work fun. You will be dynamic and creative, and willing to take on any challenge and make a big impact.Be data-driven, with high judgment. GSF is building out a new team and this means there is a lot of room for experimentation and adaptation, but in these early days we lack some of the structure that a more established group would have. We’re looking for someone who is data-driven and analytical in their approach, and yet also able to use sound judgement to make smart decisions in the absence of data.Be scrappy: The GSF team operates like a start-up – we’re moving fast and learning and adapting along the way. We’re looking for people who are willing to dive in and solve a variety of problems and own the solution end-to-end.
Excellent organizational and interpersonal skillsExperience in customers insights and various testing methodsStrong attention to detail including precise and effective customer communications and proven ability to manage multiple, competing priorities simultaneouslyAnalytical and quantitative skills; ability to use hard data and metrics (SQL, Excel, etc.) to back up assumptions and develop business casesSuperior verbal and written communications skills, and ability to navigate a complex and unstructured cross-functional environmentHistory of teamwork and willingness to do whatever is necessary; general manager / owner mentality
Amazon is an Equal Opportunity-Affirmative Action Employer – Minority / Female / Disability / Veteran / Gender Identity / Sexual Orientation]]></content><city><![CDATA[Nashville]]></city><category><![CDATA[Agile Methodologies]]></category><company><![CDATA[Amazon.com Services, Inc.]]></company><date><![CDATA[07/05/2019]]></date></ad><ad><id><![CDATA[11989]]></id><url><![CDATA[https://us.jobs4it.pt/jobs/11989/sr-product-manager-fulfillment-technology-amazoncom-services-inc-nashville-tn]]></url><title><![CDATA[Sr. Product Manager - Fulfillment Technology - Amazon.com Services, Inc. - Nashville, TN]]></title><content><![CDATA[Bachelor’s degree or higher with a technical discipline5+ years of product management experienceKnowledge of Product Management principlesDemonstrated experience in working with Agile / Scrum / Kanban methodologies.Experience working on technical, developer-facing productsExperience leading cross-functional teams to deliver products and projects on tight deadlinesExperience coordinating complex product development cycles and software development schedulesStrong analytical and quantitative skills with the ability to use data and metrics to back up assumptions and recommendations
Do you want a unique, exciting opportunity to help build something from the ground up? We are looking for builders who thrive in ambiguity to join the leadership team of a new tech organization under Global Specialty Fulfillment.As a Sr. Product Manager for GSF Fulfillment Technology, you will be helping to define the future of this critical operational business lane at Amazon. You will craft a business strategy, feature set, and roadmap that will drive your creative vision forward and enable some of Amazon’s biggest brands to delight millions of customers.. Your focus will be on the services that offer a full suite of digital capabilities that power some of Amazon’s most important initiatives.As a Sr. Product Manager, you will be responsible for the following:Innovating on behalf of our customersManaging the product life cycle from strategic planning to tactical executionDefine the feature sets, business requirements, measures of success, and roadmap for your productsPrioritizing engineering work while balancing the requirements of customers and stakeholdersEvangelizing the product both internally and externallyWorking with key stakeholders in the company to identify and drive product solutions to support sales, account management, operations, and customer supportDefining product requirements based on an intimate knowledge of the customer and technologyEstablishing product goals and reviewing success metrics to achieve commercial successHere are some qualities we are looking for:Be great fun to work with. At Amazon, we have a credo of “Work hard. Have fun. Make history”. In this role, you will love what you do, and instinctively know how to make work fun. You will be dynamic and creative, and willing to take on any challenge and make a big impact.Be data-driven, with high judgment. GSF is building out a new team and this means there is a lot of room for experimentation and adaptation, but in these early days we lack some of the structure that a more established group would have. We’re looking for someone who is data-driven and analytical in their approach, and yet also able to use sound judgement to make smart decisions in the absence of data.Be scrappy: The GSF team operates like a start-up – we’re moving fast and learning and adapting along the way. We’re looking for people who are willing to dive in and solve a variety of problems and own the solution end-to-end.
MBA preferredExcellent organizational and interpersonal skillsExperience in customers insights and various testing methodsStrong attention to detail including precise and effective customer communications and proven ability to manage multiple, competing priorities simultaneouslyAnalytical and quantitative skills; ability to use hard data and metrics (SQL, Excel, etc.) to back up assumptions and develop business casesSuperior verbal and written communications skills, and ability to navigate a complex and unstructured cross-functional environmentHistory of teamwork and willingness to do whatever is necessary; general manager / owner mentality
Amazon is an Equal Opportunity-Affirmative Action Employer – Minority / Female / Disability / Veteran / Gender Identity / Sexual Orientation]]></content><city><![CDATA[Nashville]]></city><category><![CDATA[Agile Methodologies]]></category><company><![CDATA[Amazon.com Services, Inc.]]></company><date><![CDATA[07/05/2019]]></date></ad><ad><id><![CDATA[11988]]></id><url><![CDATA[https://us.jobs4it.pt/jobs/11988/software-development-engineer-alexa-connect-kit-amazoncom-services-inc-bellevue-wa]]></url><title><![CDATA[Software Development Engineer, Alexa Connect Kit - Amazon.com Services, Inc. - Bellevue, WA]]></title><content><![CDATA[Bachelor's degree in Computer Science or equivalent5+ years building production software systemsExperience defining system architectures and exploring trade-offsFamiliarity with Alexa
The Alexa Connect Kit Team is focused on making Alexa the user interface for the home.Customers love using Alexa to interact with their homes through natural commands and intuitive interfaces. We are evolving Alexa into an intelligent, indispensable companion that helps customers get the most out of the technology in their homes.The Alexa Connect Kit Team is seeking a software development engineer to help develop new solutions focused on improving the quality, diversity, and customer of smart home devices.The ideal teammate is passionate about Alexa and has a track record of success in delivering new features and products. A commitment to teamwork, knowledge of IoT systems, strong CS fundamentals, developing new systems, and strong communication skills (to both business and technical partners) are absolute requirements.As a leader on the team, you will be responsible for leading the development and launch of core product features. You will have significant influence on our overall strategy by helping define these product features, system design, and best practices.Other responsibilities include:Leading development and maintenance of key system featuresWorking with other team members to investigate design approachesPrototyping designs and testing them with teammatesWorking in an Agile/Scrum environment to deliver high quality software against aggressive schedules.
Master's degree in Computer ScienceFamiliarity with IoT or embedded software developmentExcellence in technical communication with peers and non-technical cohortsAmazon is an Equal Opportunity Employer – Minority / Women / Disability / Veteran / Gender Identity / Sexual Orientation / Age.]]></content><city><![CDATA[Bellevue]]></city><category><![CDATA[Agile Methodologies]]></category><company><![CDATA[Amazon.com Services, Inc.]]></company><date><![CDATA[07/05/2019]]></date></ad><ad><id><![CDATA[11987]]></id><url><![CDATA[https://us.jobs4it.pt/jobs/11987/software-development-engineer-amazoncom-services-inc-seattle-wa]]></url><title><![CDATA[Software Development Engineer - Amazon.com Services, Inc. - Seattle, WA]]></title><content><![CDATA[Bachelor's degree in Computer Science or related field1+ years of experience building production software systemsExperience with OO design/developmentExperience with the tools of the trade, including a variety of modern programming languages (Java, C/C++, Objective C, Python) and open-source technologies (Linux, SQLite, OpenGL, Spring, Hibernate)Experience in technical communication across technical and non-technical teamsDevelopment experience defining, developing and maintaining REST based interfaces
Interested in Alexa? Come work on it. We’re building the speech and language solutions behind Alexa and other Amazon products and services. We’re working hard, having fun, making history; come join us!ResponsibilitiesResponsible for the development and maintenance of key system featuresWill work with other team members to investigate design approaches, prototype new technology and evaluate technical feasibility.Will work in an Agile/Scrum environment to deliver high quality software against aggressive schedules.Will establish architectural principles, select design patterns and then mentor team members on their appropriate applicationFull stack developer that are able to work in all parts of an application – the backend services, middle tier, and front-end
Experience developing cloud software services and an understanding of design for scalability, performance and reliabilityDevelopment experience defining, developing and maintaining web service API'sDevelopment experience with Linux and embedded operating systems.Development experience with communications products (e.g. IP messaging, voice , and video)Demonstrated ability to mentor other software developers to maintain architectural vision and software qualityAmazon is an Equal Opportunity Employer – Minority / Women / Disability / Veteran / Gender Identity / Sexual Orientation]]></content><city><![CDATA[Seattle]]></city><category><![CDATA[Agile Methodologies]]></category><company><![CDATA[Amazon.com Services, Inc.]]></company><date><![CDATA[07/05/2019]]></date></ad><ad><id><![CDATA[11986]]></id><url><![CDATA[https://us.jobs4it.pt/jobs/11986/senior-delivery-manager-healthstream-nashville-tn]]></url><title><![CDATA[Senior Delivery Manager - HealthStream - Nashville, TN]]></title><content><![CDATA[Position Summary
As a Senior Delivery Manager, you will be the operational leader of the CloudOps administrative, operations and development activity. You will work closely with Product/Solution Leadership and other stakeholders across departments to ensure their requirements are being properly captured, translated and implemented. You will also ensure the operational effectiveness of the teams within your lane, including removing any impediments they may be experiencing internally or from external forces. Ultimately, you will be responsible for the delivery of cloud services and software by your lane.
ESSENTIAL DUTIES OR RESPONSIBILITIES –
Work closely with Product/Solution Leadership to understand their strategic direction for both development lanes and individual products
Understand work objectives from multiple perspectives and levels, including the executive level, proactively suggesting alternatives and challenging assumptions
Collaborate with Product/Solution Leadership and the development teams to understand commitments, priorities, and delivery expectations
Define and generate key performance indicators (KPIs) to help better forecast product timelines, proactively identify potential issues with a product/service delivery and support optimization and refinement of DevSecOps processes
Continuously monitor budget utilization, polcy adherence and process adoption, collaborating across teams and departments to clearly communicate and resolve issues as they arise
Identify, track and help remove impediments adversely affecting teams’ ability to meet delivery expectations
Deliver consistent, clear, and timely communication (both written and verbal) to Product/Solution leadership
Translate technical concepts into language easily understood by both technical and non-technical stakeholders
Inspiring a mindset of continuous quality by motivating the team to consider quality standards throughout the development lifecycle
Manage team resource needs, risks, issues, project scope and contingency plans, while escalating to leadership when appropriate.
Actively monitor, track and manage project tasks, timelines, attainment of established milestones deliverables (Discovery to Delivery)
Additional PMO Department Expectations Include:
Support current PMO standards, while directly and continuously revising/creating protocols to help move the department forward
Participate in critical issue ‘on-call’ rotation (requiring 24-hour availability for specified time-period)
Help to define and lead quarterly PMO department initiatives
Complete annual required training/learning as directed by HealthStream and PMO leadership
Job Specifications
KNOWLEDGE/EDUCATION AND EXPERIENCE REQUIRED:
Minimum 5 years of professional experience managing enterprise-level software projects using Agile methodologies
Experience overseeing and synchronizing multiple agile development teams towards a common goal, as well as coordinating dependencies external to that team
Bachelor’s degree in Business, Project Management or related field, or equivalent experience is required.
PMP preferred
CSM, PMI-ACP, or equivalent preferred
SKILLS REQUIRED:
Proven in-depth, hands-on experience with Agile software development methodologies
Excellent oral and written communications skills and experience interacting with both business and technical individuals at all levels
Solid leadership and planning skills to enable successful coordination of many resources and task simultaneously
Exceptional conflict management skills in solving problems, compromising, settling personality differences, and resolving conflicts within a team environment
Well versed in iterative project management methodologies to include Scrum and Kanban
Working knowledge of Public Cloud infrastructure and services such as those offered by Amazon Web Services or Microsoft Azure
Familiarity with DevSecOps processes including distributed development, continuous integration, delivery, compliance and operations.
Solid understanding of and demonstrated experience in using:
MS Office Suite (Word, Excel, PowerPoint, OneNote)
Agile Project Management tools such as Azure DevOps Services (formerly VSTS), used by HealthStream, or an equivalent.
Continuous integration and delivery tools such as those provided in Azure Devops or equivalentHealthStream is an equal opportunity employer. HealthStream prohibits employment practices that discriminate against individual employees or groups of employees on the basis of age, color, disability, national origin, race, religion, sex, sexual orientation, pregnancy, veteran or military status, genetic information or any other category deemed protected by state and/or federal law.]]></content><city><![CDATA[Nashville]]></city><category><![CDATA[Agile Methodologies]]></category><company><![CDATA[HealthStream]]></company><date><![CDATA[07/05/2019]]></date></ad><ad><id><![CDATA[11985]]></id><url><![CDATA[https://us.jobs4it.pt/jobs/11985/sr-product-manager-resuscitation-healthstream-nashville-tn]]></url><title><![CDATA[Sr. Product Manager, Resuscitation - HealthStream - Nashville, TN]]></title><content><![CDATA[Position Summary
The Senior Product Manager is responsible for leading the vision, go-to-market strategy and execution of the resuscitation product portfolio. This individual acts as the spokesperson for their respective portfolio and assumes responsibility for designing differentiating products, expanding market share, and assuring attainment of revenue and customer satisfaction goals. This individual works in a matrix environment across internal departments such as sales, marketing & development, interfaces directly with customers, and develops relationships with business partners. Strong interpersonal skills and emotional intelligence are as critical to the success in this position as education and experience.
The Senior Product Manager will develop a high degree of credibility, both internally and externally. This individual will have the ability to plan and execute own activities with generally defined goals and minimal supervision, as well as manage multiple concurrent activities and complex projects with the appropriate prioritization and focus.
Approximately 20-30% travel is required to support partner and customer relationships; attend workshops, conferences, or trade shows; and work with offsite colleagues.
ESSENTIAL DUTIES OR RESPONSIBILITIES –
 A. Product Development and Management
Develops a vision and executes strategy for a portfolio of products, considering organizational goals and strategy and in collaboration with supervisor
Conducts market and customer research, communicating trends, competitive landscape, size of opportunity and unique value proposition for a portfolio of products
Tracks and understands market share, financial performance, renewal metrics, and product usage patterns/trends and report internally on this analysis
Produces well-researched and well-founded product pricing and appropriate incentive/discounts to promote sales
Guides multiple cross-functional and self-led scrum (technology) teams as the portfolio/product visionary to ensure customer-focused product development
Guides the resolution of customer and product issues in collaboration with development and support personnel
Communicates effectively with internal personnel to assure accurate and complete understanding of a portfolio of products
Communicates effectively with leaders and executives on all aspects of vision and execution for a portfolio of products
B. Sales and Marketing Support
Co-develops sales and marketing strategies for the portfolio of products with a goal of optimizing growth
Supports the execution of sales and marketing activities
Coordinates and communicates new product releases, including sales enablement tools, marketing collateral and training
Acts as the thought leader for the Company for the assigned portfolio of products
Supports internal team members on an ongoing basis with regards to product-related questions
Assists in identifying and supporting marketing opportunities, such as professional conferences and other events that provide access to potential customers
C. Partner Management
Recommends potential partners based on market research and portfolio needs
Effectively presents opportunities through a business case
Conducts negotiations with partners in collaboration with leadership and legal counsel
Manages ongoing relationships with partners, communicating relevant KPIs, leading annual growth strategies, and ensuring satisfaction
Job Specifications
 A. KNOWLEDGE/EDUCATION AND EXPERIENCE REQUIRED:
Bachelor’s degree in business, healthcare, or marketing (advanced degree strongly preferred)
At least 5 years in a business, product, sales, marketing, or relevant role
Experience in the healthcare industry strongly preferred
Experience in the software development lifecycle or technology management strongly preferred
Experience in resuscitation and simulation strongly preferred
B. SKILLS REQUIRED:
Excellent written, verbal, and presentation skills
Excellent organizational, multi-tasking, and time-management skills with a keen eye for detail
Proficiency in the use of technical applications for business purposes; specifically, the Microsoft Office suite and CRMs
Proficiency in the interpretation of business-related data and KPIs
C. ABILITIES REQUIRED:
Works independently, exhibiting a high degree of personal ownership and accountability
Communicates effectively with various levels of management and customers to express vision, goals, objectives and strategies
Establishes high degree of trust and credibility internally, with business partners, and with customers
Respectfully works within a multi-disciplinary, matrixed team with a focus on meeting organizational and team goals
Negotiates internally for appropriate resources and investments, as well as externally with regards to business partnerships
Displays critical thinking ability while managing multiple projects with the appropriate prioritization and focus
Responds to setbacks and roadblocks with a positive attitude and appropriate redirection
HealthStream is an equal opportunity employer. HealthStream prohibits employment practices that discriminate against individual employees or groups of employees on the basis of age, color, disability, national origin, race, religion, sex, sexual orientation, pregnancy, veteran or military status, genetic information or any other category deemed protected by state and/or federal law.]]></content><city><![CDATA[Nashville]]></city><category><![CDATA[Agile Methodologies]]></category><company><![CDATA[HealthStream]]></company><date><![CDATA[07/05/2019]]></date></ad><ad><id><![CDATA[11984]]></id><url><![CDATA[https://us.jobs4it.pt/jobs/11984/sr-product-manager-workforce-development-healthstream-nashville-tn]]></url><title><![CDATA[Sr. Product Manager, Workforce Development - HealthStream - Nashville, TN]]></title><content><![CDATA[Position Summary
The Sr. Product Manager has direct responsibility for HealthStream’s workforce development product suite. This position supports and grows HealthStream’s products throughout their life cycle, working in a matrix environment across internal departments, interfacing with customers as necessary, developing and growing relationships with business partners, researching and identifying options to improve the product(s), and negotiating new business partner agreements. This role works closely with leaders from all internal departments, to 1) define and implement the product family’s vision and roadmap, 2) assure attainment of projected sales, revenue and customer satisfaction goals, and 3) align activities across all departments with HealthStream’s organizational strategy and goals.
The Sr. Product Manager is responsible for the vision, strategy, and implementation of technology, service, and content products that support a customer’s workforce development initiatives. Customers include acute, post-acute, and ambulatory care providers such as hospitals, outpatient clinics, long-term care facilities, and free-standing surgery centers.
The Sr. Product Manager is a complex, well-respected, and highly visible role at HealthStream. A candidate for this position should immediately generate a very high level of credibility with both internal and external customers. This credibility should come from a long history of relevant experience, prior success with similar/related products, and ability to quickly create value to the organization and its customers. Strong interpersonal skills and emotional intelligence is as critical to the success in this position as education and experience.
Approximately 10-15% travel is required to support partner and customer relationships; attend workshops, conferences, or trade shows; and work with offsite colleagues.
ESSENTIAL DUTIES OR RESPONSIBILITIES:
Product Management
Create and manage vision and strategy for all assigned products within the context of the total product family and aligned with organizational priorities and focus
Launch new products and enhancements in collaboration with marketing, sales, technology, and other areas of the organization
Collaborate with organizational leaders to assure full understanding of market, sub-markets, customers, and product opportunities
Conduct market and customer research to better understand market trends and other considerations and the competitive environment for related products
Track and understand market share, financial performance, renewal metrics, and product usage patterns/trends and report internally on this analysis
Produce well-researched and well-founded product pricing and appropriate incentive/discounts to promote product sales
Grow sales and revenues for assigned HealthStream-owned and partner products
Informally manage, support, and direct an organization-wide and cross-functional team of employees who work within a matrix environment in support of the product family
Guide multiple cross-functional and self-led scrum (technology) teams developing and supporting product technology components
Assure accurate and complete understanding of products through routine internal training, development of customer training, and other forms of internal and external communication
Identify, resolve, and monitor customer and product issues with the assistance of client services support
Business Development
Research and evaluate potential new partnerships/mergers/acquisitions and other external opportunities, including managing the RFP/RFI process
Make recommendations for future new partnerships and manage product enhancements with existing partners
Conduct negotiations with partners to finalize business relationships and contracting, with the support of internal legal counsel
Manage the ongoing relationships with existing partners, including gaining a deep understanding of their business and enhancing the business and technical relationships with existing partners
Sales and Marketing Support
Assist in the development and support the execution of sales plans
Support new product releases with a full product launch including the development of sales tools, collaterals, and training
Assist in the development of marketing strategy and prioritize the production of marketing materials and sales-supporting activities
Identify and support marketing opportunities such as trade shows and other events that provide access to potential customers
Identify and support public relations opportunities such as speaking engagements, published articles, and other events that promote HealthStream as a thought leader
Job Specifications
A. KNOWLEDGE/EDUCATION AND EXPERIENCE REQUIRED:
Bachelor’s degree in business, human resources, product marketing, or clinical discipline (advanced degree strongly preferred)
At least 5 years in a product management, sales, product marketing, or relevant role (i.e. clinical or HR)
Clinical or healthcare-related experience strongly preferred
Software development lifecycle or technology management experience strongly preferred
B. SKILLS REQUIRED:
Exceptional written, verbal, and presentation skills
Successful use of technical applications for business purposes (Salesforce, HPQC, etc)
C. ABILITIES REQUIRED:
Establishes high level of trust and credibility internally, with business partners, and with customers
Works within a multi-disciplinary, matrixed team with respect towards others and laser focus on successfully meeting organizational and team goals
Motivates and leads both direct reports and non-direct reports using a “rally team” methodology
Appropriately influences and directs cross-functional team members without formal authority or management control
Resolves conflict to meet needs of organization and/or customer, while retaining or improving relationships with those involved
Negotiates for appropriate resources and investments in product family, irrespective of direct management responsibility for functional area in need
Displays critical thinking ability examining and considering multiple perspectives and decision-making founded outside of functional silos
Possesses strong interpersonal skills, including listening skills and a striving to understand before being understood
Responds to setbacks and roadblocks with positive attitude and appropriate redirection of activity
Plans and executes own activities with generally-defined goals and minimal supervision
Manages activities for multiple concurrent and complex projects across multiple functional areas with the appropriate prioritization and focus
HealthStream is an equal opportunity employer. HealthStream prohibits employment practices that discriminate against individual employees or groups of employees on the basis of age, color, disability, national origin, race, religion, sex, sexual orientation, pregnancy, veteran or military status, genetic information or any other category deemed protected by state and/or federal law.]]></content><city><![CDATA[Nashville]]></city><category><![CDATA[Agile Methodologies]]></category><company><![CDATA[HealthStream]]></company><date><![CDATA[07/05/2019]]></date></ad><ad><id><![CDATA[11983]]></id><url><![CDATA[https://us.jobs4it.pt/jobs/11983/dir-reimbursement-access-value-takeda-pharmaceuticals-lexington-ma]]></url><title><![CDATA[Dir Reimbursement, Access & Value - Takeda Pharmaceuticals - Lexington, MA]]></title><content><![CDATA[By clicking the “Apply” button, I understand that my employment application process with Takeda will commence and that I agree with Takeda’s Privacy Notice, Privacy Policy and Terms of Use.
Job Description
Director Reimbursement, Access & Value (RAV)
Are you looking for a patient-focused company that will inspire you and support your career? If so, be empowered to take charge of your future at Takeda.
Join us as the Director Reimbursement, Access & Value (RAV) in our Greater Boston area, MA office.
Here, everyone matters and you will be a vital contributor to our inspiring, bold mission. As a Director Reimbursement, Access & Value (RAV) working on the Gastroenterology Business Unit team, you will be empowered to help develop the Entyvio Marketing on in the GI therapeutic area and a typical day will include:
Here, you will be a vital contributor to our inspiring, bold mission.
A typical day will include:
OBJECTIVES:
Understand patient/provider unmet needs relating to Entyvio reimbursement, access and value proposition vs competitor perceptions/programs
Develop strategies and tactics with the following objectives:
Create awareness and understanding of Entyvio’s access landscape
Develop solutions/programs that facilitate access to Entyvio for appropriate patients
Support HCPs and key accounts in understanding the Entyvio value proposition and relevant strategic business/market dynamics
Assess current IBD market access trends and related brand performance to make necessary adjustments to related strategies or tactics and support organizational alignment of activities to brand strategy
Develop and maintain plans to segment, target and engage with specific provider customer segments, through thought leader partnership, peer to peer activation and key association connection
Work across Managed Markets, Medical, Marketing, Key Account Management, and Regional Account Management to develop strategic access/value related KAM/FRM resources
Partner with HUB/Patient Services to develop long-term roadmap for access programming and operationalize near-term programs
Develop and execute long-range goals for both the brand and the team that correspond with marketing and people growth and development
ACCOUNTABILITIES:
Support Snr Dir RAV by playing a substantial role in the development of the annual brand strategy and expense plan related to reimbursement, access and value. This includes providing input on forecast assumptions, brand plan and manage multi-million dollar budgets to achieve net sales and operating margin goals.
Manages relationship with key creative agencies and provides guidance for the development of briefs and execution for relevant areas of focus
Interface and collaborate with many internal partners within the organization to ensure alignment to the strategy and continue progress within the commercial approach to key customers
Partner with Market Access colleague to provide input on value proposition execution and develop a key understanding of the account strategy at both a payer and provider level.
Oversee and help support the expert engagement plans, including integration and collaboration with the Global team as well as Medical Affairs and R&D
Lead regular analyses of ongoing programs and tactics to identify needs for adjustment or change and to anticipate market changes relevant to focus areas
Engage and develop relationships with key external access/reimbursement experts within the market to continually gain insights first hand to inform the brand as well as ensure infusion of innovation and new thinking.
Serve as back-up for RAV Leadership when needed.
Support brand team counterparts, contribute to a positive team culture and uphold the Takeda values and principles
EDUCATION , SKILLS
Bachelor Degree
10 years of marketing, sales or related function experience in the pharmaceutical industry with 3 years of leadership experience.
Experience with provider and/or payer accounts
Demonstrated ability to lead / manage a team, positively influence coworkers toward common goals, foster collaboration, and enable teamwork
Industry knowledge
Experience in value proposition development, expert engagement strategies and/or peer to peer engagement is desired
Ability to understand and leverage analytics to drive decision making
Significant experience in highly competitive specialty markets with complex science and reimbursement. In-depth knowledge of service company business models.
Proven experience partnering with cross functional stakeholders to develop innovative strategies and programs.
Ability and experience to perform all functions in adherence with legal, compliance and regulatory guidelines.
Innovative and creative thinking demonstrating implementation of real and measurable positive change.
Ability to inspire and lead innovation across cross functional teams to maximize team productivity and outcomes in support of overall RAV strategy.
Ability to influence cross functional teams and stakeholders and assist in prioritizing ideas that have the maximum positive impact on the GI leadership strategy.
Demonstrated ability to motivate large teams to rally behind a common vision.
Ability to anticipate future market trends across the industry and proactively refine and adapt leadership strategy to stay at the forefront of leadership trends.
A demonstrated ability to process complex information and summarize it concisely in writing and/or verbally in a professional manner and in a time sensitive environment is required.
Experience in managing projects, including overseeing work plans, budgets.
TRAVEL REQUIREMENTS:
Relevant travel
WHAT TAKEDA CAN OFFER YOU:
401(k) with company match and Annual Retirement Contribution Plan
Tuition reimbursement Company match of charitable contributions
Health & Wellness programs including onsite flu shots and health screenings
Generous time off for vacation and the option to purchase additional vacation days
Community Outreach Programs
Empowering Our People to Shine
Discover more at takedajobs.com
No Phone Calls or Recruiters Please.
#LI- AS2
Locations
Lexington, MA
Worker Type
Employee
Worker Sub-Type
Regular
Time Type
Full time
Job ID R0008765]]></content><city><![CDATA[Lexington]]></city><category><![CDATA[Microsoft]]></category><company><![CDATA[Takeda Pharmaceuticals]]></company><date><![CDATA[07/05/2019]]></date></ad><ad><id><![CDATA[11982]]></id><url><![CDATA[https://us.jobs4it.pt/jobs/11982/director-software-development-fiserv-san-antonio-tx]]></url><title><![CDATA[Director Software Development - Fiserv - San Antonio, TX]]></title><content><![CDATA[What does an excellent Director Software Development do?
You are part of the Fiserv mortgage lending product development, and technical delivery of product applications team. You will partner with other leaders to grow the company by effectively and efficiently delivering product initiatives using an active and practical approach. As a leader, you will guide your team to attain the mortgage lending objectives outlined in our strategic plan. You will manage, guide and lead teams that are highly productive and deliver the highest levels of production quality.
You can expect:
Strategy and Planning
Partner with the leadership team, you will help find opportunities and risks for delivering our services, including identification of opportunities for innovation, and assessment of marketplace obstacles and technical hurdles to the business success.
You will participate in establishing governance processes, direction and controls to ensure success, risks are managed appropriately and the organization’s resources are used responsibly for software development.
Collaborate with the appropriate departments to assess and recommend technologies that support company organizational needs and product objectives.
Product Development
Establish effective processes for organizing, prioritizing and reporting on software development cases/stories/epics to ensure objectives are achieved.
Supervise the effective implementation, management and support practices for software development version controls and company ticketing/ project management systems.
Recruit, manage and supervise company employees or outsourced vendors who will implement application enhancements and refinements conforming to industry best practices.
Define and document methodologies for efficient product development in alignment to Fiserv standards.
Supervise specification conformance and testing regimen based on user stories and Fiserv / product design standards.
Craft and review coding conventions and documentation standards.
Review current best practices for the selected framework and support an architecture roadmap for the application that aligns with business objectives and Fiserv resources.
Establish and supervise the software development process, setting objectives and assessing progress as defined by the selected software development methodology.
Conduct code reviews and specification conformance testing as defined by the selected software development methodology and Fiserv Style Guide conformance.
Contribute to the application deployment process requirements and ensure timely deployment to QA, UAT, Sales and production servers to ensure applications are accurately deployed.
As a member of the senior management team, establish effective support processes for software / application issue remediation.
Operational Management
Maintain up-to-date knowledge of software development standards, industry trends, emerging technologies and best practices.
Ensure that software development standards and best practices are documented and maintained across the organization.
Share knowledge, guide, and educate the management, staff, partners, clients and stakeholders with regard to the company’s technological vision, opportunities, and challenges.
Develop, track, and supervise annual budgets for third party software required for software development objectives.
Supervise recruitment, training, retention, and organization of all software development staff in accordance with Fiserv hiring process, personnel policies, and budget requirements.
Establish standards of performance and monitor conformance for staff through performance reviews.
Collaborate with other Fiserv teams in a manner that ensure BU conformance with Fiserv Bank Solutions product development best practices.
Ensure the company’s internal technological processes and customer-facing services comply with Fiserv expectations and applicable laws and regulations for privacy, security, and social responsibility.
Coordinate development and team resources to establish detailed written plans for the long-term infrastructure requirements of Fiserv applications.
Provide supervisory management, reviews and discipline of technology department employees.
Coach, mentor and train Fiserv software development resources to support their skill set development.
Document and enforce processes that ensure the progress of all development cases are accurately documented within Fiserv’s software tracking system(s).
Supervise and establish effective time tracking for LOS, Web and API development resources as necessary for product development and professional services objectives:
Coding requirements
Business requirements
Troubleshooting
Provide support to BA resources as necessary to ensure product designs and release planning objectives are met.
Provide support to QA/QC resources as necessary to support product releases.
Supervise the work with third party vendors, customers and Fiserv SME’s to ensure the most efficient and effective use/interaction of vendor services for development requirements.
Validate initial unit and system testing is completed by developers in a manner that ensures appropriate software testing is completed prior to review by Case Owners, Business Leads or Fiserv QA resources.
Maintain acceptable levels of competency with Fiserv’s product suite and services to ensure product designs are effective and customer implementations maximize the effectiveness of Fiserv resources available to them.
Provide reports to the senior management team that summarize progress on department objectives, software development releases, software development quality and SLA objectives.
Supervise the identification and documentation of critical path support requirements from other departments that are necessary to meet software development quality and release deadlines objectives.
Supervise and manage the escalation of any issues that will impact the quality or release deadlines of software development objectives.
Supervise the preparation and coordination of Mortgage Steering Committee agendas, collateral and support processes. Document and report customer feedback/findings to Fiserv Business Unit senior management.
Basic Qualifications for consideration:
10+ years of relevant work experience
Ability to establish and create effective resource planning initiatives that are comprehensively approached and completed
Proficiency with Agile software development methodology.
Proficiency with PHP, Delphi, .Net and C Sharp requirements and utilization.
Proficiency with software project management methods and effective development staff supervision.
Proficiency with reporting languages/methods and ability to understand how to structure reports to ensure projects and team members are accurately monitored and project delivery deadlines are achieved.
Knowledgeable in Quality Assurance methods and performance and security testing
Proficiency with one or more of the following: MS Suite, Visio, Crystal Reports, PowerBI, GoToMeeting, Jira, Confluence, SVN, and Fisheye
Preferred Qualifications for consideration:
2+ years working in the mortgage business and/or LOS software business
Solid grasp of the mortgage loan origination process
Ability to effectively communicate with developers and business resources.
Familiarity with information security vulnerabilities and risk management.
Familiarity with consumer privacy and payments industry compliance requirements.
Exposure to business theory, business process development, governance processes, management, budgeting, and administrative operations.
Effective listening and communication skills; gather customer requirements and explain requirements to developers and employees at various levels.
Strong organization and time management skills.
Proven leadership ability.
Ability to set and manage priorities judiciously
Ability to clearly communicate ideas to both technical and non-technical audiences.
Exceptionally self-motivated and directed.
Keen attention to detail and ability/interest to learn in depth product knowledge.
Superior analytical, evaluative, and problem-solving abilities.
Exceptional service orientation.
Ability to motivate in a team-oriented, collaborative environment.
Ability to lead globally dispersed, multi-cultural teams
Learn more about Fiserv:
In a world moving faster than ever before, Fiserv helps clients deliver solutions in step with the way people live and work today – financial services at the speed of life. With 24,000 associates, we help more than 12,000 clients worldwide create and deliver solutions to enable today's consumer to move and manage money with ease, speed and convenience. Our Aspiration is to move money and information in a way that moves the world. As a FORTUNE™ 500 company and one of FORTUNE Magazine World’s Most Admired Companies for the sixth consecutive year, we are committed to excellence and purposeful innovation.
We welcome and encourage diversity in our workforce. Fiserv is an equal opportunity employer/disability/vet
Explore the possibilities of a career with Fiserv and Find Your Forward with us.]]></content><city><![CDATA[San Antonio]]></city><category><![CDATA[Microsoft]]></category><company><![CDATA[Fiserv]]></company><date><![CDATA[07/05/2019]]></date></ad><ad><id><![CDATA[11981]]></id><url><![CDATA[https://us.jobs4it.pt/jobs/11981/regional-sales-manager-transit-bus-rail-safe-fleet-california-city-ca]]></url><title><![CDATA[Regional Sales Manager - Transit Bus & Rail - Safe Fleet - California City, CA]]></title><content><![CDATA[CommissionWho are we?

Safe Fleet owns a portfolio of brands committed to saving life and property, reducing accidents and improving employee efficiency and job satisfaction.

Our VISION is to be the leading global provider of safety solutions for fleet vehicles.

We develop, manufacture and sell best in class high performance safety related products. Our products provide increased functionality and integrated solutions for fleet vehicle manufacturers and operators.

Founded in 1999, Seon is a fast-growing fleet technology company that is the market leader in video surveillance for passenger transportation. As part of the Safe Fleet portfolio of brands, we are reimagining fleet safety; creating disruptive technologies. Our products encourage safe driving habits, protect passengers, and prevent pedestrian accidents.

Our mission is to improve the lives of fleet operators and protect the passengers they are trusted to transport. We’ve got the perfect blend of entrepreneurial spirit and long-term stability, boasting a 20-year history of profitable growth. We’re a passionate, committed group of people that love what we do and who we work with.

Our vision is to make the world a safer place which is why we started our United Against Bullying campaign (unitedagainstbullying.net) in 2013 to offer school communities tools, resources, and funding to stop bullying and empower young people to stand up against abusive behavior.

What are we looking for?

We are looking for an energetic, hands-on, detail-oriented individual for this opportunity.

This is a permanent full-time position, 40 hours per week.

Compensation is base salary plus commission. We also offer paid vacation time, sick/personal days and fully paid benefits after 3 months’ probation (Life, Accidental Death & Disability, Short and Long-Term Disability, Extended Health, Dental, Employee Assistance Program and RRSP Program with company matching your contributions, up to 3% of your salary).

JOB SUMMARY

The Regional Sales Manager will be responsible for providing customers with exceptional knowledge and demonstration of complex solutions through a consultative sales approach and own the Business Plan for the defined territory. The Regional Sales Manager will be a self-starter, extremely motivated and somewhat technical due to the products we sell, service and maintain and must have a prior track record of selling “like” systems from a technical perspective either in a fixed or mobile environment. The Reg Sales Manager must continually attain and develop new business as well as maintain existing accounts within the defined territory and will strive to initiate, develop and maintain relationships with key decision makers, industry insiders and integration partners.

RESPONSIBILITIES:

Create, own and execute the business plan for the assigned territory
Have direct contact and relationships with all customers in the assigned territory including Tier 1 – 4 transit authorities and light rail
Protect existing accounts, increase revenue and profitability by upselling additional products and services and cross selling applicable Safe Fleet products
Complete all weekly and activity reporting in accordance with Safe Fleet forecasting cadence
Be able to comfortably communicate the Safe Fleet story and value proposition to customers
Maintain knowledge of other Safe Fleet product lines that are applicable to transit bus and light rail
Ongoing market and competitor analysis to stay in tune with competitor activity and effectively communicate findings cross-functionally to sales peers and product management
Represent the company at networking functions, speaking engagements and other industry-related events
Research and deliver executive-level strategic marketing presentations
Able to conceive of and execute effective marketing and prospecting programs to increase awareness of Critical Mass among qualified prospects
Develop and continue to refine a list of target third party supplier companies, and contacts deemed influential to developing business with those targets.
Identify possible OEM's / ODM’s and raise these to Senior Management
 REQUIRED SKILLS, KNOWLEDGE AND EXPERIENCE

Disciplined self-starter with 5+ years of consultative sales selling integrated video / security systems in a fixed or transit environment
Bachelor’s degree from a recognized College or University
An understanding of internet and wireless communication systems and topologies
Ability & skills to explain technical solutions to non-technical buyers across various influencers at the end user level
Demonstrated proficiency with CRM tools and Microsoft Suite is a must
Proven track record of developing effective strategies and customized proposals that win new business
Excellent oral and written communication, persuasion, diplomatic and interpersonal skills; experience in researching, writing and delivering marketing proposals and presentations
A demonstrated ability to work in a highly entrepreneurial setting where 'many hats' must be worn and decisions need to be made quickly sometimes with minimal management direction
Hard driving, "Close the Deal" attitude will be important but must be balanced with flexibility, patience and adaptability
Familiarity with Tier 1 Government purchasing cycles and processes (RFP)
Strong written, project management and technical aptitude skills are essential
Ability to simultaneously manage multiple projects
Valid driver’s license and passport is required – travel between the US and Canada (up to 60%)]]></content><city><![CDATA[California City]]></city><category><![CDATA[Microsoft]]></category><company><![CDATA[Safe Fleet]]></company><date><![CDATA[07/05/2019]]></date></ad><ad><id><![CDATA[11980]]></id><url><![CDATA[https://us.jobs4it.pt/jobs/11980/advanced-software-solutions-developer-healthstream-san-diego-ca]]></url><title><![CDATA[Advanced Software Solutions Developer - HealthStream - test]]></title><content><![CDATA[Position Summary
Design, develop, and maintain the software products offered by Verity. Lead project development efforts while training development staff in technology best practices and product offerings. Work with systems group to understand internal and external customer needs, understand requirements, and effectively communicate product and technology decisions. Design and estimate effort of new features or sub-systems from business concept to detailed technical design. Develop quality, defect free software that adheres to company coding and documentation standards.
ESSENTIAL DUTIES OR RESPONSIBILITIES – (The below listed duties are not all inclusive. This position must also perform other duties as assigned.):
This position is a non-management development position. Developers in this position will participate as members of a software development team and will have individual project leadership responsibilities across the spectrum of software development for a particular Verity product or serve as Development lead for a Verity Software Development team under guidance of a more senior Developer.
Job Specifications
1. KNOWLEDGE/EDUCATION AND EXPERIENCE REQUIRED:
A Bachelor's degree in Computer Science, Engineering (any discipline), or closely related field of study is preferred
3 years of experience in the job offered or 3 years of experience as a Senior Application Developer, Consultant, Software Engineer, or closely related occupation
Position also requires demonstrated experience with: ASP.NET and C#; and Database development experience with Microsoft SQL Server, MySQL or similar.
Agile project management experience required, ideally focused on SCRUM or Kanban
2. SKILLS REQUIRED (manual, verbal or mental manipulation of data or things):
.NET (latest), including C# and ASP.net
ASP.NET
Web technologies including HTML 5, CSS and JavaScript
SQL querying and performance tuning
Familiarity with development practices including:
Cloud Providers such as AWS
DevOps practices and automation
Continuous Integration practices
SOLID Development Principles
Inversion of Control
Code refactoring
Object-oriented Design Patterns (GOF)
Architecture Patterns (N-Tier)
Data Access Layer Technologies (ORMs, Micro ORMs, etc.)
Strong communication skills including technical writing ability
3. ABILITIES REQUIRED (work characteristics, behaviors, leadership abilities, etc.):
HealthStream is an equal opportunity employer. HealthStream prohibits employment practices that discriminate against individual employees or groups of employees on the basis of age, color, disability, national origin, race, religion, sex, sexual orientation, pregnancy, veteran or military status, genetic information or any other category deemed protected by state and/or federal law]]></content><city><![CDATA[San Diego]]></city><category><![CDATA[Microsoft]]></category><company><![CDATA[HealthStream]]></company><date><![CDATA[07/05/2019]]></date></ad><ad><id><![CDATA[11979]]></id><url><![CDATA[https://us.jobs4it.pt/jobs/11979/associate-implementation-manager-healthstream-nashville-tn]]></url><title><![CDATA[Associate Implementation Manager - HealthStream - Nashville, TN]]></title><content><![CDATA[Position Summary
The Associate Implementation Manager will be responsible for onboarding new and existing customers to the HealthStream Learning Management System (LMS) and Clinical Solution products. This individual will be responsible for all phases of the implementation process through application of basic project management methodology as well as utilizing a consultative approach to providing the best solutions for HealthStream customer needs. The Associate Implementation Manager will be responsible for the actual deployment of the LMS or product, assisting customers with defining key personnel, testing, and developing best practices that will ensure a successful role out of the HealthStream LMS or clinical products at customer facilities.
Implement new learning management sites, activate new content/products, and work with project managers regarding large scale projects as required. Application of basic Project Management methodology as well as a consultative approach toward the HLC design will be utilized.
Assist customers with defining key personnel, best practices, training and deployment via thorough consultation of key system needs.
Maintain project artifacts throughout customer implementation process.
Manage project scope and customer expectations throughout implementation process.
Maintain weekly status report of all on-going implementations to Manager of Implementation Services.
Maintain department documentation, participate in quarterly team workshops, and assist with on-boarding new products into department.
Work with database administrators to clearly define and document defects incurred during implementation process
Job Specifications
A. KNOWLEDGE/EDUCATION AND EXPERIENCE REQUIRED:
Experience with manage projects and/or Project Management methodology
Experience with web based software running on .Net platform
Experience troubleshooting web based software on multiple platforms
Experience with Microsoft Word, Excel and Salesforce
Experience problem solving web based software related issues, data file issues
Basic understanding of software delivery lifecycle
A.S in computer related field required
B. SKILLS REQUIRED:
Project Management (certification not required)
Excellent verbal and written communication skills
Excellent customer service skills
Excellent critical thinking skills
Time management skills
Ability to read analyze and interpret basic excel and tab delimited data files
C. ABILITIES REQUIRED:
Ability to work independently or within a team dynamic
Ability to follow outlined policies and procedures
Ability to translate technical requirements into non-technical terminology
Working Environment: Desk/Work Station
HealthStream is an equal opportunity employer. HealthStream prohibits employment practices that discriminate against individual employees or groups of employees on the basis of age, color, disability, national origin, race, religion, sex, sexual orientation, pregnancy, veteran or military status, genetic information or any other category deemed protected by state and/or federal law.]]></content><city><![CDATA[Nashville]]></city><category><![CDATA[Microsoft]]></category><company><![CDATA[HealthStream]]></company><date><![CDATA[07/05/2019]]></date></ad><ad><id><![CDATA[11978]]></id><url><![CDATA[https://us.jobs4it.pt/jobs/11978/product-solutions-developer-healthstream-nashville-tn]]></url><title><![CDATA[Product Solutions Developer - HealthStream - Nashville, TN]]></title><content><![CDATA[Position Summary
This is a non-management software development position. Developers in this position have software development responsibilities for one or more HealthStream products. Serves as a self-sufficient member of a software development team.
ESSENTIAL DUTIES OR RESPONSIBILITIES – (The below listed duties are not all inclusive. This position must also perform other duties as assigned.):
Inform complexity estimates for proposed software application features and enhancements
Program new applications, features, and enhancements, including application code and database queries
Execute integrations with third-party software systems
Author and maintain automated tests for software applications to safeguard quality
Investigate, diagnose, and mitigate software applications failures and defects
Measure, record, and maintain a standardized set of metrics for software code quality
Monitor and support as necessary the deployment of software applications to production
Provide consultations for other software developers working in his areas of subject matter expertise
Advise Quality Assurance regarding how to test software application features, enhancements, and defect fixes
Job Specifications
1. KNOWLEDGE/EDUCATION AND EXPERIENCE REQUIRED:
Bachelor degree in Computer Science preferred. Commensurate experience or advanced industry technical certification (e.g., Microsoft Certified Professional, etc.) may substitute.
2+ years’ experience in Software Development
2. SKILLS REQUIRED (manual, verbal or mental manipulation of data or things):
.NET (latest)
C#
ASP.NET
Web technologies
HTML 5
HTTP
CSS 3
JavaScript
SQL querying and performance tuning
Development practices
SOLID Development Principles
Inversion of Control
Code refactoring
3. ABILITIES REQUIRED (work characteristics, behaviors, leadership abilities, etc.):
Process compliance
Tolerance for change
HealthStream is an equal opportunity employer. HealthStream prohibits employment practices that discriminate against individual employees or groups of employees on the basis of age, color, disability, national origin, race, religion, sex, sexual orientation, pregnancy, veteran or military status, genetic information or any other category deemed protected by state and/or federal law]]></content><city><![CDATA[Nashville]]></city><category><![CDATA[Microsoft]]></category><company><![CDATA[HealthStream]]></company><date><![CDATA[07/05/2019]]></date></ad><ad><id><![CDATA[11977]]></id><url><![CDATA[https://us.jobs4it.pt/jobs/11977/advanced-product-solutions-developer-healthstream-nashville-tn]]></url><title><![CDATA[Advanced Product Solutions Developer - HealthStream - Nashville, TN]]></title><content><![CDATA[Position Summary
Design, develop, and maintain the software products offered by HealthStream. Lead project development efforts while training development staff in technology best practices and product offerings. Work with systems group to understand internal and external customer needs, understand requirements, and effectively communicate product and technology decisions. Design and estimate effort of new features or sub-systems from business concept to detailed technical design. Develop quality, defect free software that adheres to company coding and documentation standards.
ESSENTIAL DUTIES OR RESPONSIBILITIES – (The below listed duties are not all inclusive. This position must also perform other duties as assigned.):
This position is a non-management development position. Developers in this position will participate as members of a software development team and will have individual project leadership responsibilities across the spectrum of software development for a particular HealthStream product or serve as Development lead for a HealthStream Software Development team under guidance of a more senior Developer.
Job Specifications
1. KNOWLEDGE/EDUCATION AND EXPERIENCE REQUIRED:
A Bachelor's degree in Computer Science, Engineering (any discipline), or closely related field of study is preferred
3 years of experience in the job offered or 3 years of experience as a Senior Application Developer, Consultant, Software Engineer, or closely related occupation
Position also requires demonstrated experience with: ASP.NET and C#; and Database development experience with Microsoft SQL Server, MySQL or similar.
2. SKILLS REQUIRED (manual, verbal or mental manipulation of data or things):
.NET (latest), including C# and ASP.net
ASP.NET
Web technologies including HTML 5, CSS and JavaScript
SQL querying and performance tuning
Familiarity with development practices including:
Cloud Providers such as AWS
DevOps practices and automation
Continuous Integration practices
SOLID Development Principles
Inversion of Control
Code refactoring
Object-oriented Design Patterns (GOF)
Architecture Patterns (N-Tier)
Data Access Layer Technologies (ORMs, Micro ORMs, etc.)
3. ABILITIES REQUIRED (work characteristics, behaviors, leadership abilities, etc.):
Candidates should demonstrate abilities including:
Agile project management experience required, ideally focused on SCRUM or Kanban
Strong communication skills including technical writing ability

HealthStream is an equal opportunity employer. HealthStream prohibits employment practices that discriminate against individual employees or groups of employees on the basis of age, color, disability, national origin, race, religion, sex, sexual orientation, pregnancy, veteran or military status, genetic information or any other category deemed protected by state and/or federal law]]></content><city><![CDATA[Nashville]]></city><category><![CDATA[Microsoft]]></category><company><![CDATA[HealthStream]]></company><date><![CDATA[07/05/2019]]></date></ad><ad><id><![CDATA[11976]]></id><url><![CDATA[https://us.jobs4it.pt/jobs/11976/systems-engineer-healthstream-nashville-tn]]></url><title><![CDATA[Systems Engineer - HealthStream - Nashville, TN]]></title><content><![CDATA[Position Summary
Under direction of the Director of Site Operations designs, develops, and maintains the infrastructure and hosting environment at Healthstream.
ESSENTIAL DUTIES OR RESPONSIBILITIES
Design, Build and migrate solutions to the cloud across the organization working with various teams. Responsible for Automation, Virtual networking/security and access in AWS Cloud Services. Provide DevOps and Systems engineering work with all AWS Services (EC2, RDS, Redshift etc..)And frameworks such as Chef or Puppet.
Lead efforts to support and integrate our on premise Virtualization, Cloud infrastructure and systems with external cloud as needed. Ensure on premise and off premise workloads work well together. Develop reproducible migration plans for workloads and applications
Create, modify, and update written procedures, processes, and technical support knowledge effectively and use this knowledge to provide consultation to other units and to streamline future application moves.
Lead problem and incident resolution facilitating calls with vendors to file bug reports and resolve technical issues.
Will support administration of servers, server clusters, backups, and storage, VMware and networking environments.
Design, plan and implement systems architectures that support client and organizational objectives and requirements
Support environment that includes Windows OS, VMware, EMC VNX, IIS Web Servers, Clustering Technologies and various applications.
Identify, plan and lead projects and tasks necessary to assess, optimize, proactively manage and maintain systems and infrastructure.
Ensure all support requests, projects and other tasks are reviewed, prioritized, addressed and completed in a timely and proficient manner
Identify, document, publish and uphold systems policies, standards, procedures, checklists, agreements, diagrams, inventory, etc.
Efficiently troubleshoot all issues and problems to ensure a timely and appropriate resolution
Coordinate with members of the Site Operations team, rest of the organization and any others needed to ensure proper implementation, support and maintenance of systems
Train and mentor team member
Perform on-call duty for non-business hours support
Complete any other tasks necessary to accomplish the organizations objectives
Job Specifications
1. KNOWLEDGE/EDUCATION AND EXPERIENCE REQUIRED:
Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science or similar field preferred.
Minimum 7-10 years’ experience in a Systems Engineer Role
Knowledge and experience with large-scale systems integration involving private, hybrid, and public cloud platforms
Experience with public and private cloud, including OpenStack and AWS
Experience with virtualization, including: VMWare and HyperV
Experience administering CentOS or Ubuntu
Experience in a 24X7 hosting environment
2. SKILLS REQUIRED:
Hands-on technical prototyping in a virtualized and/or cloud services environment with a hands-on understanding of Cloud Computing solutions (e.g., Google App Engine, Microsoft Azure, Amazon EC2, S3, VMware, Eucalyptus or other cloud vendor offerings.).
Understanding of cloud orchestration frameworks, enterprise IT service provisioning tools, and their role in IT transformation including Chef, SALT, Puppet, etc.
Able to write software in Python or some other administrative language
Design, Build and migrate solutions to the cloud across the organization working with various teams. Responsible for Automation, Virtual networking/security and access in AWS Cloud Services. Provide DevOps and Systems engineering work with all AWS Services (EC2, RDS, Redshift etc..)And frameworks such as Chef or Puppet.
Lead efforts to support and integrate our on premise Virtualization, Cloud infrastructure and systems with external cloud as needed. Ensure on premise and off premise workloads work well together. Develop reproducible migration plans for workloads and applications
Create, modify, and update written procedures, processes, and technical support knowledge effectively and use this knowledge to provide consultation to other units and to streamline future application moves.
Lead problem and incident resolution facilitating calls with vendors to file bug reports and resolve technical issues.
Will support administration of servers, server clusters, backups, and storage, VMware and networking environments.
Design, plan and implement systems architectures that support client and organizational objectives and requirements
Support environment that includes Windows OS, VMware, EMC VNX, IIS Web Servers, Clustering Technologies and various applications.
Identify, plan and lead projects and tasks necessary to assess, optimize, proactively manage and maintain systems and infrastructure.
Ensure all support requests, projects and other tasks are reviewed, prioritized, addressed and completed in a timely and proficient manner
Identify, document, publish and uphold systems policies, standards, procedures, checklists, agreements, diagrams, inventory, etc.
Efficiently troubleshoot all issues and problems to ensure a timely and appropriate resolution
Coordinate with members of the Site Operations team, rest of the organization and any others needed to ensure proper implementation, support and maintenance of systems
Train and mentor team member
Perform on-call duty for non-business hours support
Complete any other tasks necessary to accomplish the organizations objectives
3. ABILITIES REQUIRED:
Strong understanding of ASP.Net fundamentals
Ability and experience to design and deploy highly available and mission critical web applications
Strong and Deep understanding of systems performance tuning
HealthStream is an equal opportunity employer. HealthStream prohibits employment practices that discriminate against individual employees or groups of employees on the basis of age, color, disability, national origin, race, religion, sex, sexual orientation, pregnancy, veteran or military status, genetic information or any other category deemed protected by state and/or federal law]]></content><city><![CDATA[Nashville]]></city><category><![CDATA[Microsoft]]></category><company><![CDATA[HealthStream]]></company><date><![CDATA[07/05/2019]]></date></ad></channel>