<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><source><jobs><job><location>Tobyhanna, PA, United States</location><title>Delivery Driver</title><city>Tobyhanna</city><state>PA</state><zip>18466</zip><country>United States</country><job_type></job_type><posted_at>2019-09-03</posted_at><job_reference>787_966686741</job_reference><company>Aaron&apos;s Inc</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category>Transportation/Logistics</category><html_jobs>Yes</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/26qks04?cs=8k</url><body>We are Aaron&apos;s - an industry leader in the sales&lt;br/&gt;and lease-to-own retailer known for quality brand names and superior customer&lt;br/&gt;service. We provide our team members the opportunity to reach their full&lt;br/&gt;potential in a team-oriented, high-energy, recognition-based environment with&lt;br/&gt;competitive pay and benefits. This is much more than a job - It is a career&lt;br/&gt;with purpose.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Aaron&apos;s Delivery Drivers are recognized as the front line to our customers. As&lt;br/&gt;brand ambassadors, their goal is to provide a top-notch, red carpet customer&lt;br/&gt;experience. As a Delivery Driver, you will be responsible for delivering,&lt;br/&gt;installing, and demonstrating merchandise in our customer&apos;s home, while&lt;br/&gt;providing outstanding customer service along the way!&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Skills for Success**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Delivery Drivers are professional, courteous and genuinely enjoy working with&lt;br/&gt;people. Solid communication skills, a working knowledge of electronics, and&lt;br/&gt;dependability are necessary. Like all Aaron&apos;s team members, they share our&lt;br/&gt;purpose and passion for making a real difference in the lives of others and the&lt;br/&gt;rewards that come from creating strong personal connections for life.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**The Work**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;?       Load, secure and protect product in delivery&lt;br/&gt;vehicle and safely transport merchandise without damage&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;?       Verify product information and accessories to&lt;br/&gt;ensure it matches for deliveries and returns&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;?       Ensure all merchandise is clean and in operating&lt;br/&gt;condition prior to delivery&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;?       Offload, install and demonstrate merchandise for&lt;br/&gt;our customers safely&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;?       Perform routine service calls, product exchanges&lt;br/&gt;and assist with merchandise returns&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;?       Confirm customer identification, collect money&lt;br/&gt;and obtain customers signature on lease agreements&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;?       Assist sales team with field marketing programs&lt;br/&gt;requested by store management&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;?       Support in maintaining the showroom floor and&lt;br/&gt;store&apos;s warehouse by moving and organizing merchandise&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;?       Maintain the store&apos;s warehouse in a neat and&lt;br/&gt;orderly manner&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;?       Safely operate delivery vehicle and follow&lt;br/&gt;delivery schedule set by management&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;?       Accurately document all vehicle movement on&lt;br/&gt;daily route sheets&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;?       Team partnership with both the Sales Manager and&lt;br/&gt;Customer Service Representative(s) to drive revenue and to meet and exceed&lt;br/&gt;daily, weekly and monthly sales goals&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;?       Conduct daily inspection of assigned delivery&lt;br/&gt;vehicle to ensure safety and maintenance guidelines are met&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;?       Any other reasonable duties requested by&lt;br/&gt;management&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Requirements**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;?       At least 21 years old with a valid state&lt;br/&gt;Driver&apos;s License and compliance with the Company&apos;s Driver Qualification Policy;&lt;br/&gt;including satisfactory MVR (driving record)&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;?       Must meet DOT requirements to obtain&lt;br/&gt;certification in required states&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;?       Ability to work schedule of hours varying from 8&lt;br/&gt;am to 9 pm&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;?       Ability to lift up to 50 lbs. without help and&lt;br/&gt;up to 300 lbs. with the assistance of a dolly&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;?       Excellent interpersonal and communication skills&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;?       High energy with the ability to effectively&lt;br/&gt;perform all functions of the store and multitasking effectively&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;?       High School diploma or equivalent preferred&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;?       Proper customer service etiquette&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;?       Uphold the Aaron&apos;s Brand and protect company&lt;br/&gt;assets&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;?       Maintain a professional appearance&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;?       Strong technical skills and/or working knowledge&lt;br/&gt;of electronic products&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Rewards**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Team members enjoy access to career training and advancement opportunities, and&lt;br/&gt;rewarded with competitive compensation and a comprehensive benefits package,&lt;br/&gt;which includes:&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;?       Paid time off including vacation days, sick days and holidays&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;?       Medical, dental &amp; vision insurance&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;?       401(k) plan with company match&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;?       Flexible spending accounts&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;?       Life insurance&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;?       Disability benefits&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;?       Stock Purchase Plan&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;?       Team Member purchase discounts&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; **About Aaron&apos;s**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;At Aaron&apos;s we provide sales and lease-to-ownership specialty items relating to&lt;br/&gt;furniture, consumer electronics, home appliances, and accessories through its more&lt;br/&gt;than 1,800 Company-operated and franchised stores. Our customers shop at&lt;br/&gt;Aaron&apos;s for the same reason you should choose us for the next step in your&lt;br/&gt;career - our ability to influence people&apos;s lives. We help people &quot;OWN IT&quot;, and&lt;br/&gt;if you are looking for a company with the passion and dedication to make a&lt;br/&gt;difference in the lives of customers and team members alike, join us today.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Aaron&apos;s is committed to creating a diverse work environment, celebrates our&lt;br/&gt;team members&apos; differences, and is proud to be an equal opportunity employer.&lt;br/&gt;All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without&lt;br/&gt;regard to race, color, pregnancy, religion, sex, sexual orientation, gender&lt;br/&gt;identity, national origin, age, disability, Veteran status, military duty, gender&lt;br/&gt;expression, genetic information, or any other protected class.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Aaron&apos;s is an Equal Opportunity Employer.**  &lt;script id=&quot;detrack&quot; defer src=&quot;https://d2e48ltfsb5exy.cloudfront.net/p/t.js?i=0,1&quot; data-g=&quot;b64f44b4c276487db2825a7fcbc410111624&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;</body><cpc>0.13</cpc></job>
<job><location>Santa Clara, CA, United States</location><title>Systems Engineering Manager - Bay Area South</title><city>Santa Clara</city><state>CA</state><zip>95054</zip><country>United States</country><job_type></job_type><posted_at>2019-09-03</posted_at><job_reference>787_935197038</job_reference><company>Palo Alto Networks</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category>Engineering &amp; Architecture</category><html_jobs>Yes</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/21v355m?cs=8k</url><body>**Our Mission**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;At Palo Alto Networks? everything starts and ends with our mission:&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Being the cybersecurity partner of choice, protecting our digital way of life.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;We have the vision of a world where each day is safer and more secure than the one before. These aren&apos;t easy goals to accomplish - but we&apos;re not here for easy. We&apos;re here for better. We are a company built on the foundation of challenging and disrupting the way things are done, and we&apos;re looking for innovators who are as committed to shaping the future of cybersecurity as we are.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Your Career**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;As our Systems Engineer Manager, you are the technical leader for your District Systems Engineering team. You will work closely with the District Sales Manager and, along with your team, build relationships with your customers with the goal of helping them detect and prevent advanced cyberattacks and breaches. Our customers need guidance on what applications to deploy from our platform. Your guidance, expertise, and mentorship of your team of SEs will keep them ahead of the latest cyberthreats and staying on the leading edge of prevention.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;We are looking for a leader to develop our sales teams, providing training and technical support as a product expert. Additionally, you will provide feedback to the product management team on new feature requests and product improvements based on what you learn from your customer base. Your team, in partnership with the sales account managers, will displace competitor technologies and build market share within your targeted list of accounts, and most importantly, help your client sleep at night as they use our products to build secure digital transactions.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Your Impact**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Recruit and hire new systems engineers into the territory, hiring the best talent in the industry&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Responsible to train, mentor, and review employees on your team, keeping them engaged and successful in their careers&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Support field systems engineer team in complex evaluations, problem-solving and challenging customer environments&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Define and create an updated system engineering training curriculum&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Develop relationships with channel partners and their technical teams to ensure colleagues are appropriately trained and can support our installations&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Provide effective technical leadership in customer interactions to include sharing security trends and standard methodologies employed by other customers to actively be part of the selling process&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Act as a floating systems engineer and fill in for existing team members if there is a resource conflict or vacation coverage challenge&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Act as an escalation point for pre-sales and post-sales technical issues that arise&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Build and maintain relationships with key customers to solidify reference accounts and to assist the account teams with defining plans to drive more business&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Present to customers as our expert in your area at all levels in the customer hierarchy from technician to CIO&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Lead conversations about industry trends and emerging changes to the security landscape that every customer needs to plan for&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Discuss competitor products in the marketplace and positions ours as the best alternative&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Working with Product Management, Technical Marketing, and R&amp;D to build requirements and product features for our large customers and provide feedback from customers&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Provide design consultation and standard methodology mentorship for rollout, implementation, and policy conversion during the &apos;pre-sales&apos; process for strategic opportunities&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Ownership of advanced &apos;proof of concept&apos; testing in strategic accounts either at the customer site or our lab facilities&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Provide advanced &apos;Partner SE&apos; training for updates in our product suite&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Maintain a general understanding of competitor selling strategies&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ 50-75% travel within the region&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Your Experience**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Experience as a pre-sales System Engineer Manager&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Experience as a Senior System Engineer or Consulting Engineering&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Industry knowledge of security product market trends and directional awareness of our roadmap and technology development efforts, knowledge of competitor offerings and products&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Knowledge of how to deliver comprehensive security solutions to Palo Alto Networks customer base&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Strong communication (written and verbal) and presentation skills&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Quota driven attitude focused on client&apos;s best solution by being a trusted advisor&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**The Team**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;As part of our Systems Engineering team, you&apos;ll support the sales team with technical expertise and guidance when establishing trust with key clients. You won&apos;t find someone at Palo Alto Networks that isn&apos;t committed to your success - with everyone pitching in to assist when it comes to solutions selling, learning, and development. As a member of our systems engineering team, you are motivated by a solutions-focused sales environment and find fulfillment in working with clients to resolve incredible complex cyberthreats.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Our Commitment**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;We&apos;re trailblazers that dream big, take risks, and challenge cybersecurity&apos;s status quo. It&apos;s simple: we can&apos;t accomplish our mission without diverse teams innovating, together.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;We are committed to providing reasonable accommodations for all qualified individuals with a disability. If you require assistance or accommodation due to a disability or special need, please contact us at accommodations@paloaltonetworks.com.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Palo Alto Networks is an equal opportunity employer. We celebrate diversity in our workplace, and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to age, ancestry, color, family or medical care leave, gender identity or expression, genetic information, marital status, medical condition, national origin, physical or mental disability, political affiliation, protected veteran status, race, religion, sex (including pregnancy), sexual orientation, or other legally protected characteristics.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;EOE Protected Veterans/Disability.  &lt;script id=&quot;detrack&quot; defer src=&quot;https://d2e48ltfsb5exy.cloudfront.net/p/t.js?i=0,1&quot; data-g=&quot;878cef2ab37441ecb947c4ba4e9d1c391624&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;</body><cpc>0.13</cpc></job>
<job><location>San Jose, CA, United States</location><title>Senior Sourcing Specialist/Commodity Manager</title><city>San Jose</city><state>CA</state><zip>95115</zip><country>United States</country><job_type></job_type><posted_at>2019-09-05</posted_at><job_reference>787_970711915</job_reference><company>Danaher Corporation</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category>Management</category><html_jobs>Yes</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/27sn7pn?cs=8k</url><body>**Danaher Company Description**  &lt;br/&gt;Molecular Devices is one of the world&apos;s leading providers of high-performance bioanalytical measurement systems, software, and consumables for life science research, pharmaceutical, and biotherapeutic development. Included within a broad product portfolio are platforms for high-throughput screening, genomic and cellular analysis, colony selection, and microplate detection. These leading-edge products enable scientists to improve productivity and effectiveness, ultimately accelerating research and the discovery of new therapeutics. Molecular Devices is committed to the continual development of innovative solutions for life science applications. The company is headquartered in Silicon Valley, California with offices around the globe.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Be sure to follow us on LinkedIn!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Description**  &lt;br/&gt;     The sourcing Manager is responsible for balancing the company&apos;s end to end sourcing operations, and for meeting Global Sourcing savings targets as well as serving as an escalation path for delivery, quality, and supplier management issues. The ability to manage multiple complex projects and to develop the supply base to meet corporate and business unit objectives is critical. You must have the ability to evaluate and select new suppliers along with Engineering, Quality and Regulatory to select strategic partners worldwide. Must have strong understanding of global trade, the need for constant change and identification of new technologies. &lt;br/&gt;  * This position is based in the MolDev San Jose facility, supporting San Jose facility Operations, R&amp;D and commercial teams and provides support to Shanghai facility as needed. Ability to travel domestically 10-20% of the time required, may travel internationally.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  * Manage the company&apos;s supply portfolio ensuring transparency of spending; Generate and implement efficient sourcing and category management strategies&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  * Manage multiple supplier relationships: New parts; supplier changes; yearly negotiations; pricing and payment terms&lt;br/&gt;  * Ownership of positive relationships between Molecular Devices and suppliers leading to the best cost, quality, delivery and service&lt;br/&gt;  * Optimize sourcing procedures to attain maximum efficiency &lt;br/&gt;  * Understanding &amp; ownership of Supplier Selection Processes&lt;br/&gt;  * Owns the overall Commodity spend and is responsible to secure savings in line with annual objectives&lt;br/&gt;  * Works closely with Product Development on new projects to deliver new supplier relationships, technologies, or co-development solutions&lt;br/&gt;  * Supports operations procurement teams to deploy global sourcing strategy and help resolve parts supply or quality issues&lt;br/&gt;  * Work closely with other relative departments such as Finance, service, sales etc. to improve expense efficiency by optimizing process and supplier base&lt;br/&gt;#LI-BC1&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Qualification**  &lt;br/&gt;  * Bachelor&apos;s degree or advanced degree in Supply Chain, Engineering or related field.&lt;br/&gt;  * Proven work experience as a sourcing manager or procurement manager&lt;br/&gt;  * Experience in lean manufacturing environment&lt;br/&gt;  * Awareness of lean tools desirable, examples: 5S, Standard Work, KANBAN, Policy Deployment, Value Stream Management, Visual Management.&lt;br/&gt;  * Experience in ERP systems, Oracle is preferred.&lt;br/&gt;  * Commercial skills and contracts composition experience.&lt;br/&gt;  * Good negotiator and decision maker; strong analytical skills, use of data to drive decisions.&lt;br/&gt;  * Strong project management and leadership skills&lt;br/&gt;  * International business and multi-cultural experience&lt;br/&gt;  * Understanding of market dynamics and sound business judgement&lt;br/&gt;  * Ability to travel domestically and possibly internationally, 10-20% of the time.&lt;br/&gt;  * Driven individual with passion for quality and manufacturing great products&lt;br/&gt;  * Strong competency in driving for results, and ability to gain followership and enlist help from others&lt;br/&gt;  * Openness to coaching, with strong collaboration, communication and team work skills&lt;br/&gt;  * Ability to compile reports, analyze data, and present in meaningful manner&lt;br/&gt;  * Comfortable presenting/training in front of groups as well as via phone&lt;br/&gt;  * Strong attention to detail/accuracy, meeting deadlines, and organizational skills to manage multiple priorities&lt;br/&gt;  * The right candidate for this role will embody both the Molecular Devices and Danaher culture.  Below are key attributes this candidate will possess. &lt;br/&gt;  * Analytical. This leader seeks out facts and evaluates relationships and dependencies.&lt;br/&gt;  * Results-driven. Demonstrating initiative and personal accountability to meet work demands according to highest standards, while being able to prioritize and balance competing needs, will be key to success.&lt;br/&gt;  * Both a competitive and team player. This individual speaks to results yet gives credit to the team.Humble and self-aware. Helping drive a culture of respect across all associates, functions and levels while championing D&amp;I and focusing on results is a must. This candidate understands their personal areas of development and actively works on weaknesses.&lt;br/&gt;  * Clear communicator. Strong experience in developing effective internal communications and a clear, succinct style is desired.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;*Diversity &amp; Inclusion*&lt;br/&gt;At Danaher, we are dedicated to building and sustaining a truly diverse and inclusive culture. These are not just words on a page-Diversity and Inclusion is a top priority for the company, and it ties deeply to each of our core values. Danaher Corporation and all Danaher Companies are equal opportunity employers that evaluate applicants without regard to race, color, national origin, religion, sex, age, marital status, disability, veteran status, sexual orientation, gender identity, or other characteristics protected by law.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Danaher Corporation Overview**  &lt;br/&gt;Danaher is a global science &amp; technology innovator committed to helping our customers solve complex challenges and improve quality of life worldwide. Our world class brands are leaders in some of the most demanding and attractive industries, including life sciences, medical diagnostics, dental, environmental and applied solutions. Our globally diverse team of 71,000 associates is united by a common culture and operating system, the Danaher Business System, which serves as our competitive advantage. We generated $19.9B in revenue last year. We are ranked #162 on the Fortune 500 and our stock has outperformed the S&amp;P 500 by more than 5,200% over 25 years.&lt;br/&gt;At Danaher, you can build a career in a way no other company can duplicate. Our brands allow us to offer dynamic careers across multiple industries. We&apos;re innovative, fast-paced, results-oriented, and we win. We need talented people to keep winning. Here you&apos;ll learn how DBS is used to shape strategy, focus execution, align our people, and create value for customers and shareholders. Come join our winning team.&lt;br/&gt;Danaher is committed to competitive compensation that typically has key components including base salary, variable annual incentive compensation based on personal and company performance, and long-term incentive.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Organization:** Molecular Devices  &lt;br/&gt;**Job Function:** Supply Chain &amp; Logistics  &lt;br/&gt;**Primary Location:** North America-North America-United States-CA-San Jose  &lt;br/&gt;**Schedule:** Full-time  &lt;br/&gt;**Req ID:** MOL002480  &lt;script id=&quot;detrack&quot; defer src=&quot;https://d2e48ltfsb5exy.cloudfront.net/p/t.js?i=0,1&quot; data-g=&quot;e1059764e0de4a16bf3e9d2e477b43f51624&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;</body><cpc>0.13</cpc></job>
<job><location>San Diego, CA, United States</location><title>Line Of Business Manager</title><city>San Diego</city><state>CA</state><zip>92108</zip><country>United States</country><job_type></job_type><posted_at>2019-09-05</posted_at><job_reference>787_970711926</job_reference><company>General Atomics and Affiliated Companies</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category>Management</category><html_jobs>Yes</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/27sn731?cs=8k</url><body>**Job ID#:**  24988BR&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Company:**  General Atomics&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Title:**  Line Of Business Manager&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Job Category:**  Facilities&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**City:**  San Diego&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**State:**  California&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Travel Percentage Required:**  0% - 25%&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Clearance Required?:**  No&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Job Summary:**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;General Atomics (GA), and its affiliated companies, is one of the world&apos;s leading resources for high-technology systems development ranging from the nuclear fuel cycle to remotely piloted aircraft, airborne sensors, and advanced electric, electronic, wireless and laser technologies.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;We recognize and appreciate the value and contributions of individuals with diverse backgrounds and experiences and welcome all qualified individuals to apply.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;We currently have an exciting opportunity for a Line of Business Manager to join our Facilities department located San Diego, CA. This position directly supports a given customer/client group, and acts as a liaison for the Facilities group.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES:**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Supports the assigned Business Unit, their objectives, product lines and overall business requirements providing a pro-active approach and partnership between the Business Unit and Facilities Operations &amp; Services organization (FO&amp;S).&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Acts as the primary liaison between their selected  Business Unit and the  Facilities organization.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Schedules and attends regular meetings with the Business Unit to review business initiatives, contract requirements, long term strategies, and Facilities related issues.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Establishes regular communications with the customer via phone, email, and regularly scheduled meetings.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Performs regular  building walkthroughs to ensure compliance with standards.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Reviews data concerning facility modifications including requested modifications, company policies, regulatory requirements, and required completion dates.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Partners with and involves internal Facilities departments and other support organizations to create plans, develop ROMs, establish time tables/project schedules, develop and deliver comprehensive proposals for presentation to customer and project initiatives or Business Unit requirements.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Ensures that schedules meet the customer&apos;s needs and that the work is communicated and is in-line with business objectives.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Ensures that work performed on behalf of the customer is done so in conjunction with the business or contractual requirements and in accordance with the customer requests.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Develops and presents formal executive level presentations  to internal customers and senior executives.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Exercises independent judgment and discretion about matters of significance.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ May function in an advisory or leadership role and provide direction and guidance to less experienced staff.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ May  operate company vehicles which requires a valid driver&apos;s license with clean driving record.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Performs other duties as assigned or required.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Full-Time/Part-Time:**  Full-Time Salary&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Job Qualifications:**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Typically requires a bachelors degree in Business Administration or a related discipline and six or more years of progressive professional project administration experience.   Equivalent professional experience may be substituted in lieu of education.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Must demonstrate a complete understanding of project administration principles, theories, concepts and techniques.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Must have experience organizing, planning, scheduling, conducting, and coordinating work assignments to meet project milestones or established completion dates.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Must possess the ability to understand new concepts quickly and apply them in an evolving environment while contributing to the development of new processes.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Must be customer focused and possess: (1) the ability to identify issues, analyze data and develop solutions to a variety of complex problems; (2) strong analytical, verbal and written communication skills to accurately document, report, and present findings; (3) strong interpersonal skills enabling an effective interface with other professionals; and (4) good computer skills.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Requires a valid driver&apos;s license with clean driving record&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Ability to work independently or in a team environment is essential as is the ability to work extended hours as required.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**US Citizenship Required?:**  No&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;General Atomics and affiliated companies is committed to hiring and retaining a diverse workforce. We are an Equal Opportunity/Affirmative Action Employer and will consider all qualified applicants for employment without regard to race, color, religion, gender, pregnancy, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, gender expression, national origin, age, genetic information, protected veteran status, disability, or any other basis protected by local, state, or federal law.  &lt;script id=&quot;detrack&quot; defer src=&quot;https://d2e48ltfsb5exy.cloudfront.net/p/t.js?i=0,1&quot; data-g=&quot;4ff47725492641ed8b6646569080acee1624&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;</body><cpc>0.13</cpc></job>
<job><location>Atlanta, GA, United States</location><title>ServiceNow Implementation Technical Senior Manager</title><city>Atlanta</city><state>GA</state><zip>30309</zip><country>United States</country><job_type></job_type><posted_at>2019-09-05</posted_at><job_reference>787_948366489</job_reference><company>Deloitte</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category>Information Technology</category><html_jobs>Yes</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/23qle9a?cs=8k</url><body>**ServiceNow Implementation Technical Senior Manager**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Customer &amp; Marketing is creating a new model for a new age-we re an agency and a consultancy. Understanding the digital space and preparing for what s next is at our core. We help clients reimagine how profits are made, how relationships are created and managed; we reshape how work gets done, and rewire the competitive fabric of entire industries. That s the power of driving disruption. That s Customer &amp; Marketing.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Work you ll do**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;A Senior Manager at Deloitte works within an engagement team and is responsible for identifying business requirements, requirements management, functional design, prototyping, process design (including scenario design, flow mapping), testing, training, defining support procedures and supporting implementations.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**The team**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Digital Customer&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Our Digital Customer team focuses on designing and implementing sales and service experiences, capabilities, and architectures to bring customer strategies to life. Our ambition is to be the best in the world at driving customer transformation through the development of clever commercial strategies, distinctive experiences, and the application of digital technologies. We help make the creative digital consultancy  real and in doing so, make new markets.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Professionals will serve our clients through the following types of work:&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Sales Excellence &amp; Service Excellence - delivers sales and service strategies and plans, operating model definition, incentive design and implementation, and operations support for digitally-enabled sales, channel, and customer service capabilities&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Digital Experience - creates engaging omni-channel digital experiences across web, mobile, AR/VR, voice, gesture, IoT, and video&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Flexible Consumption - the commercial strategy, operating model definition, and capability delivery of subscription/flexible consumption business models&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Digital Foundry - a flexible, end-to-end delivery model emphasizing innovation and disruption&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;DigitalMix - an integrated set of platforms to enable business re-platforming&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Qualifications**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Required:**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;10  years of experience leading technology delivery components of major business transformation efforts (definition, design, development, implementation) within a business in the high technology, telecommunications, medical technology and/or government services sectors, enabling clients to drive enterprise-wide change across their technology and business operations.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Demonstrated experience delivering a technology solution involving the ServiceNow platform&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Demonstrated experience planning and leading key activities across the solution delivery lifecycle (e.g., requirements / user story definition, functional and technical design, technology development, testing and implementation) for global clients&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Understanding of system development lifecycle, major development methodologies (e.g., Agile development)&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Proven ability to drive business results and readiness across multiple solutions in major transformation efforts&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Must be legally authorized to work in the United States without the need for employer sponsorship, now or at any time in the future&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Preferred:**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Providing input to developing tools and go-to-market assets to enable major business transformations&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Understanding of the lead-to-revenue  business processes within the communications and high-tech sectors&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Understanding of design good practices and relevant enabling tools&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Proven ability to build assets, lead and manage teams in major transformations&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**How you ll grow**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;At Deloitte, our professional development plan focuses on helping people at every level of their career to identify and use their strengths to do their best work every day. From entry-level employees to senior leaders, we believe there s always room to learn. We offer opportunities to help sharpen skills in addition to hands-on experience in the global, fast-changing business world.  From on-the-job learning experiences to formal development programs at Deloitte University, our professionals have a variety of opportunities to continue to grow throughout their career.   Explore Deloitte University, The Leadership Center.  at https://zoomforth.com/s/deloitte/du#home&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Benefits**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;At Deloitte, we know that great people make a great organization. We value our people and offer employees a broad range of benefits.  Learn more about what working at Deloitte can mean for you.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Deloitte s culture**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Our positive and supportive culture encourages our people to do their best work every day. We celebrate individuals by recognizing their uniqueness and offering them the flexibility to make daily choices that can help them to be healthy, centered, confident, and aware. We offer well-being programs and are continuously looking for new ways to maintain a culture where our people excel and lead healthy, happy lives.   Learn more about Life at Deloitte.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Corporate citizenship**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Deloitte is led by a purpose: to make an impact that matters. This purpose defines who we are and extends to relationships with our clients, our people and our communities.  We believe that business has the power to inspire and transform. We focus on education, giving, skill-based volunteerism, and leadership to help drive positive social impact in our communities.   Learn more about Deloitte s impact on the world.  at http://www2.deloitte.com/us/en/pages/about-deloitte/articles/deloitte-corporate-citizenship.html&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Recruiter tips**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;We want job seekers exploring opportunities at Deloitte to feel prepared and confident. To help you with your interview, we suggest that you do your research: know some background about the organization and the business area you re applying to.  Check out recruiting tips from Deloitte professionals.  at http://www2.deloitte.com/us/en/pages/careers/topics/recruiting-tips.html&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;kwdeldigallddusa&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;kwdeldigsfdcusa&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Category: Customer Relationship Management&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About Deloitte &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; As used in this document, Deloitte means Deloitte LLP and its subsidiaries. Please see www.deloitte.com/us/about for a detailed description of the legal structure of Deloitte LLP and its subsidiaries. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, national origin, age, disability or protected veteran status, or any other legally protected basis, in accordance with applicable law.  &lt;script id=&quot;detrack&quot; defer src=&quot;https://d2e48ltfsb5exy.cloudfront.net/p/t.js?i=0,1&quot; data-g=&quot;5241a32a88854d9e9c701ceaf71b78f41624&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;</body><cpc>0.13</cpc></job>
<job><location>Atlanta, GA, United States</location><title>Marketing Technology Specialist</title><city>Atlanta</city><state>GA</state><zip>30309</zip><country>United States</country><job_type></job_type><posted_at>2019-09-05</posted_at><job_reference>787_948366493</job_reference><company>Deloitte</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category>Information Technology</category><html_jobs>Yes</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/23qleai?cs=8k</url><body>**Marketing Technology Specialist**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Are you a technology management professional who has demonstrated experience in administrating, configuring, and implementing client-focused marketing platforms? Are you looking to take your skills to the next level? We are looking for talent to join us in expanding our technology platforms to support our internal stakeholders and help them achieve their goals.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Work you ll do**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;As a Marketing Technology Specialist, you ll use your technical program and project management skills to:&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Administrate Deloitte s internal marketing technology stack&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Assess legacy and existing systems to understand what s working/what s not and chart the evolution of our programs&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Support multiple cross-functional technical teams to support their business objectives&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Work closely with other platform administrators, marketing technology managers and our Internal Technology Services team to support, configure and expand our platforms&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Project manage enhancements to our platforms and expansions to new internal client groups&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Stay up-to-date on the latest process and IT advancements to automate and modernize systems&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Actively participate in our platforms  user forums and attend local user group meetings&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**The team**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;The power of our marketing organization is in our people and assets. Deloitte s Client &amp; Market Growth organization has over 2,000 people and significant firm assets that strengthen our brand and grow our firm. Our role is to deliver unique insights, create powerful experiences, build strong relationships and win work for all businesses.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Qualifications**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Required&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Bachelor s Degree and 1-2  years of project management experience&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ 1  years  experience in core project management disciplines including scope, schedule, budget, quality, along with risk and critical path management&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Experience with MS Office, and/or MS SharePoint&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Interest in managing marketing technology and automation platforms (e.g. Workfront, Salesforce, Eloqua, Adobe Experience Manager)&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ 1  years  experience in analytical, quantitative, communication, and presentation skills needed&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Preferred&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Previous experience with technology infrastructure projects&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**How you ll grow**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;At Deloitte, our professional development plan focuses on helping people at every level of their career to identify and use their strengths to do their best work every day. We offer opportunities to help sharpen skills in addition to hands-on experience in the global, fast-changing business world. From on-the-job learning experiences to formal development programs, our professionals have a variety of opportunities to continue to grow throughout their career.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Benefits**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;At Deloitte, we know that great people make a great organization. We value our people and offer employees a broad range of benefits.  Learn more about what working at Deloitte can mean for you.  at http://www2.deloitte.com/us/en/pages/careers/articles/life-at-deloitte-benefits-and-rewards.html&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Deloitte s culture**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Our positive and supportive culture encourages our people to do their best work every day. We celebrate individuals by recognizing their uniqueness and offering them the flexibility to make daily choices that can help them to be healthy, centered, confident, and aware. We offer well-being programs and are continuously looking for new ways to maintain a culture where our people excel and lead healthy, happy lives.   Learn more about Life at Deloitte.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Corporate citizenship**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Deloitte is led by a purpose: to make an impact that matters. This purpose defines who we are and extends to relationships with our clients, our people and our communities.  We believe that business has the power to inspire and transform. We focus on education, giving, skill-based volunteerism, and leadership to help drive positive social impact in our communities.   Learn more about Deloitte s impact on the world.  at http://www2.deloitte.com/us/en/pages/about-deloitte/articles/deloitte-corporate-citizenship.html&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Recruiter tips**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;We want job seekers exploring opportunities at Deloitte to feel prepared and confident. To help you with your interview, we suggest that you do your research: know some background about the organization and the business area you re applying to.  Check out recruiting tips from Deloitte professionals.  at http://www2.deloitte.com/us/en/pages/careers/topics/recruiting-tips.html&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Category: Business Development / Sales / Marketing&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About Deloitte &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; As used in this document, Deloitte means Deloitte LLP and its subsidiaries. Please see www.deloitte.com/us/about for a detailed description of the legal structure of Deloitte LLP and its subsidiaries. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, national origin, age, disability or protected veteran status, or any other legally protected basis, in accordance with applicable law.  &lt;script id=&quot;detrack&quot; defer src=&quot;https://d2e48ltfsb5exy.cloudfront.net/p/t.js?i=0,1&quot; data-g=&quot;529f8eae5f3243b9b26bbaa65ac8da541624&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;</body><cpc>0.13</cpc></job>
<job><location>Plano, TX, United States</location><title>Certified Professional Services Program (CPSP) Partner Services Manager</title><city>Plano</city><state>TX</state><zip>75026</zip><country>United States</country><job_type></job_type><posted_at>2019-09-04</posted_at><job_reference>787_950799152</job_reference><company>Palo Alto Networks</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category>Management</category><html_jobs>Yes</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/2474r6r?cs=8k</url><body>**Our Mission**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;At Palo Alto Networks? everything starts and ends with our mission:&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Being the cybersecurity partner of choice, protecting our digital way of life.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;We have the vision of a world where each day is safer and more secure than the one before. These aren&apos;t easy goals to accomplish - but we&apos;re not here for easy. We&apos;re here for better. We are a company built on the foundation of challenging and disrupting the way things are done, and we&apos;re looking for innovators who are as committed to shaping the future of cybersecurity as we are.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Your Career**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;The  **Certified Professional Services Program (CPSP) Partner Services Manager**  in The Americas is responsible for managing post-sales Professional Services delivery relationship with over 25 partners&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;located throughout the Americas region.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;This person will manage the onboarding and enablement&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;process for new partners and the ongoing monitoring and &quot;care and feeding&quot; of the existing partners to ensure their success in delivering high quality post-sales Professional Services to our mutual customers.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;This role is both tactical and strategic in nature. The strategic aspect of the role is to work in concert with the Channel Business Manager and Channel Systems Engineer to understand the partners&apos; Go-to-Market model for their professional services and to co-create the strategy for each of the key partners on how best to help grow the partners&apos; services business.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Your Impact**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? Partner with regional channel sales teams to manage the service delivery component of each partnership&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? Evaluate potential service partners within the region to see if there&apos;s a strong business need for inviting the partner into the CPSP program or not; managing the Channel organization&apos;s expectations and demands accordingly&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? Analyze quality metrics to correctly assess and incent high partner performance&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? Evangelize the value of Partner-deliver Professional Services internally in&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? Coordinate on-going training and certification for CPSPs&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? Conduct on-site and remote quarterly business reviews with each partner to ensure they are hitting key performance indicators and to continually grow the partners&apos; services business&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? Track status of legal agreements with each partner; including negotiating, amending and terminating business terms as needed&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? Manage customer complaints through direct complaints or customer satisfaction survey results&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? Up to 30% travel&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Your Experience**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? 5+ years&apos; experience in program and project management in a worldwide high tech corporate environment&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? Previous experience working within a Professional Services or other service delivery environment&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? Previous experience managing complex channel partner programs, including enablement and compliance&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? Knowledge and experience providing data analysis and presenting business trends using applications and tools; such as a Salesforce.com, and Learning Management Systems&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? Strong business acumen&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? Able to work independently in a fast-paced growth environment&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? Undergraduate degree in Computer Science or Business Administration, or relatable major&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**The Team**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Our Customer Support team is critical to our success and mission. As part of this team, you enable customer success by providing support to clients after they have purchased our products.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Our dedication to our customers doesn&apos;t stop once they sign - it evolves. As threats and technology change, we stay in step to accomplish our mission.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;You&apos;ll be involved in implementing new products, transitioning from old products to new, and will fix integrations and critical issues as they are raised - in fact, you&apos;ll seek them out to ensure our clients are&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;safely supported. We fix and identify technical problems, with a pointed focus of providing the best customer support in the industry.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Our Commitment**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;We&apos;re trailblazers that dream big, take risks, and challenge cybersecurity&apos;s status quo. It&apos;s simple: we can&apos;t accomplish our mission without diverse teams innovating, together. To learn more about our dedication to inclusion and innovation, visit our  Life at Palo Alto Networks  at https://www.facebook.com/LifeatPaloAltoNetworks/  page and our  diversity   at https://www.paloaltonetworks.com/company/about-us/inclusion-diversity website.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Palo Alto Networks is an equal opportunity employer. We celebrate diversity in our workplace, and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to age, ancestry, color, family or medical care leave, gender identity or expression, genetic information, marital status, medical condition, national origin, physical or mental disability, political affiliation, protected veteran status, race, religion, sex (including pregnancy), sexual orientation, or other legally protected characteristics.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Additionally, we are committed to providing reasonable accommodations for all qualified individuals with a disability. If you require assistance or accommodation due to a disability or special need, please contact us at accommodations@paloaltonetworks.com.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;\#LI-JS2&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;EOE Protected Veterans/Disability.  &lt;script id=&quot;detrack&quot; defer src=&quot;https://d2e48ltfsb5exy.cloudfront.net/p/t.js?i=0,1&quot; data-g=&quot;92ea0865af134483bf8c7b926f24916a1624&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;</body><cpc>0.13</cpc></job>
<job><location>Silver Spring, MD, United States</location><title>Resident Caregiver</title><city>Silver Spring</city><state>MD</state><zip>20915</zip><country>United States</country><job_type></job_type><posted_at>2019-09-05</posted_at><job_reference>787_948370679</job_reference><company>ProMedica Health System</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category>Healthcare/Medical</category><html_jobs>Yes</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/23qlh91?cs=8k</url><body>HCR ManorCare provides a range of services, including skilled nursing care, assisted living, post-acute medical and rehabilitation care, hospice care, home health care and rehabilitation therapy.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;The Resident Caregiver assist residents in all aspects of their daily life as indicated in the resident service plan, including: personal care, food service, housekeeping, laundry, behavior management, socialization, activities, orientation and information needs. This position requires tact, sensitivity, and professionalism due to the constant interaction with residents and families to guarantee their satisfaction. As a Resident Caregiver, you are a member of the Wellness Team, led by the Wellness Director. You and your team are responsible for supporting the organization Mission, values, and achieving its goals. In return for your expertise, you will enjoy excellent training, industry-leading benefits and unlimited opportunities to learn and grow.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Be a part of the team leading the nation in healthcare.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Knowledge and experience in working with elderly required, preferred dementia experience.  &lt;script id=&quot;detrack&quot; defer src=&quot;https://d2e48ltfsb5exy.cloudfront.net/p/t.js?i=0,1&quot; data-g=&quot;069ee405d5d44c2084bac5880124c6eb1624&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;</body><cpc>0.13</cpc></job>
<job><location>Fargo, ND, United States</location><title>Salesforce Systems Analyst - Minneapolis and Telecommute</title><city>Fargo</city><state>ND</state><zip>58103</zip><country>United States</country><job_type></job_type><posted_at>2019-09-05</posted_at><job_reference>787_948374877</job_reference><company>U.S. Bank</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category>Information Technology</category><html_jobs>Yes</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/23qlk3p?cs=8k</url><body>U.S. Bank is seeking a motivated Senior Business Systems Analyst with liaison and relationship management experience to contribute toward the success of our Salesforce initiatives.  Responsible for requirements and functional architecture of our Salesforce ecosystem.  Participates in testing, training, and implementation of applications.  Responsible for assisting the business line with requirements and working with the application development team to create a functional architecture.  Participates in developing and maintaining detailed knowledge of the business&apos;s current technology and infrastructure from a functional perspective. Provides guidance concerning business implications of development projects.  Serves as consultant to internal business groups on process improvement projects designed to improve their business results.  Involved in training and implementation of applications.  Partners with business stakeholders to identify, refine, and document detailed business needs.  Assists, and at times, may lead clients and technical staff to investigate, analyze, and resolve application problems related to system functions. Often first point of contact for user support and problem solving.  May manage routine projects.  Frequently interfaces with business lines, including management, and/or internal resources to ensure quality, timeliness, and testing of all project/release work.  Works with technology and application development teams to design or select solutions that appropriately meet the business needs for large projects.  Reviews and validates test plan approaches for proper functionality coverage.  May coordinate and execute test plans.  Looks for an opportunity to improve testing process.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Successful applicants will exemplify US Bank&apos;s ethical principles of uncompromising integrity, respect for others, accountability for decisions and actions, and good citizenship.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Qualifications:**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Basic Qualifications**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;-Bachelor&apos;s degree or equivalent work experience&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;-At least 6 years experience with activities, tasks, practices and deliverables for assessing and documenting business opportunities, benefits, risks, and success factors of potential applications.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Preferred Skills/Experience**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Working experience in:&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;-IT environment&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;-Information management&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;-IT project management&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;-Product and vendor evaluation&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;-Prefer candidates with experience in Financial Services Industry specifically in either Business Banking, Community Banking, Corporate Banking, Corporate Payment Systems, or Corporate Trust&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;-Ideal candidates would have Salesforce platform experience, preferably in a Systems Administration role&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Extensive experience in:&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;-System testing&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;-System development life cycle&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;-IT standards, procedures, policy&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;-Business assessment&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;-Modeling: data, process, events, objects&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;-Business process modeling&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Subject matter expert in:&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;-Requirements analysis&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;-Workflow analysis&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Job:**  Risk/Compliance/QC/Audit/Fraud&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Primary Location:**  Minnesota-MN-Richfield&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Shift:**  1st  - Daytime&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Average Hours Per Week:**  40&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Requisition ID:**  190019784&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Other Locations:**  United States&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;U.S. Bank is an Equal Opportunity Employer committed to creating a diverse workforce.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;U.S. Bank is an equal opportunity employer committed to creating a diverse workforce. We consider all qualified applicants without regard to race, religion, color, sex, national origin, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, disability or veteran status, among other factors.  &lt;script id=&quot;detrack&quot; defer src=&quot;https://d2e48ltfsb5exy.cloudfront.net/p/t.js?i=0,1&quot; data-g=&quot;585eb6c710b04d969afb3bf6d994e03c1624&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;</body><cpc>0.13</cpc></job>
<job><location>Richmond, VA, United States</location><title>First Party Fraud/ Credit Abuse Prevention Manager - Multiple Locations</title><city>Richmond</city><state>VA</state><zip>23261</zip><country>United States</country><job_type></job_type><posted_at>2019-09-05</posted_at><job_reference>787_948384878</job_reference><company>U.S. Bank</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category>Management</category><html_jobs>Yes</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/23qlqvh?cs=8k</url><body>Responsible for managing, monitoring and coordinating first party fraud/ credit abuse risk projects for credit, and business credit card products. Responsible for fraud detection strategy and develops risk rules, tools and procedures used to evaluate and control fraud risk, and analyzes the potential profit/loss impact on the assigned product line of changes in risk management strategies. Conducts and/or oversees complex first party fraud risk analysis on credit, and business credit card products to develop fraud mitigation strategies and processes.  Develops and maintains systems to support reporting and analytical requirements.  Develops predictive detection rules or models using statistical techniques. Monitors strategy and model performance and adjusts as needed to maintain performance at department goals.  Comprehensive to expert level of knowledge of all departmental data sources, and of fraud risk and operations management associated with the product lines.  Generally requires a Bachelor&apos;s degree (Master&apos;s preferred) and seven to ten years of related experience. The incumbent is individual contributor position.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;ESSENTIAL FUNCTIONS:&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;1. Manages the fraud risk management strategies and elements of credit, and business credit card products, including synthetic fraud, first pay default, payment abuse, bust-outs, collusion fraud.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;2. Responsible for the development, implementation, maintenance and analysis of first party fraud rules and strategies. Develops and maintains the analytical framework and support systems needed for continuous revision and monitoring of exiting strategies.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;3. May develop and maintain databases and programs to support reporting requirements.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;4. Identifies fraud risk, customer impact, and potential problems within a product line.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;5. Provides expertise and consultation regarding first party fraud issues and gives advice and guidance to product managers.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;6. Provides first party fraud loss forecasting and develops fraud policies and processes.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;7. Works closely with other areas of the organization such as product management, first party fraud operations, and other customer contact centers to ensure proper development and installation of fraud identification and tracking systems.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;8. May work with product management, marketing and sales teams to support new product development, methodologies, channels and strategies to meet customer needs, maximize profitability and minimize first party fraud risk.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;9. Develops and monitors fraud strategies, and validates synthetic fraud detection criteria for credit card applications.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Qualifications:**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Basic Qualifications&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;- Bachelor&apos;s degree, or equivalent work experience&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;- 10 or more years of applicable experience&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Preferred Skills/Experience&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;- Considerable knowledge of applicable laws, regulations, financial services, and regulatory trends that impact their assigned line of business&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;- Considerable understanding of the business line&apos;s operations, products/services, systems, and associated risks/controls&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;- Considerable knowledge of Risk/Compliance/Audit competencies&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;- Strong process facilitation, project management, and analytical skills&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;- Must possess business acumen and credibility to help business line(s) proactively identify and address changing workforce needs&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;- Excellent presentation, interpersonal, written and verbal communication skills&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;- Proficient computer navigation skills using a variety of software packages, including Microsoft Office applications and word processing, spreadsheets, databases, and presentations&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;- Applicable professional certifications preferred&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Job:**  Risk/Compliance/QC/Audit/Fraud&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Primary Location:**  Pennsylvania-PA-Horsham&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Shift:**  1st  - Daytime&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Average Hours Per Week:**  40&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Requisition ID:**  190019445&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Other Locations:**  United States&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;U.S. Bank is an Equal Opportunity Employer committed to creating a diverse workforce.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;U.S. Bank is an equal opportunity employer committed to creating a diverse workforce. We consider all qualified applicants without regard to race, religion, color, sex, national origin, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, disability or veteran status, among other factors.  &lt;script id=&quot;detrack&quot; defer src=&quot;https://d2e48ltfsb5exy.cloudfront.net/p/t.js?i=0,1&quot; data-g=&quot;eb1d160b30a64c3981d4c6e11067e3af1624&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;</body><cpc>0.13</cpc></job>
<job><location>Richmond, VA, United States</location><title>Practice Builder - Traffic (Richmond, VA)</title><city>Richmond</city><state>VA</state><zip>23261</zip><country>United States</country><job_type></job_type><posted_at>2019-09-05</posted_at><job_reference>787_948384930</job_reference><company>Kimley-Horn</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category>Engineering &amp; Architecture</category><html_jobs>Yes</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/23qlq9c?cs=8k</url><body>The Senior Project Manager will have an entrepreneurial spirit, creating a vision for growth in their personal practice while contributing to the growth of our transportation engineering practice in Richmond, the Commonwealth of Virginia, and places beyond. You will assist in marketing and business development efforts with our existing private clients, while delivering a wide variety of transportation planning, traffic engineering, and ITS-related projects with our growing team of transportation professionals.  Beyond serving our existing clients, you will have the ability to pursue your own passions, leads, and clients.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Our Senior Project Managers manage their projects profitably, engage in practice and delivery of projects, transition work to qualified staff, and act as a positive leader and mentor.  The successful candidate will be given a great deal of autonomy to lead, direct, and grow their business. With success, this individual will enjoy Kimley-Horn&apos;s excellent benefits including our exceptional bonus program, 401k contribution with up to 8-percent company match plus additional profit sharing and the potential to advance to ownership.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Required**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;- Well-rounded experience base in transportation engineering including transportation planning, traffic operations and roadway engineering.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;- Extensive experience managing client contacts and relationships with private businesses.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;- Provide high quality deliverables with exceptional client service&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;- Registered engineer with at least 15 years of diversified experience in as a Transportation Engineer&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;- A desire to lead and grow a transportation engineering practice&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;- Business development and marketing experience including; writing proposals, scopes of work, and budgets for projected work.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;- Ability to work in a team environment and effectively communicate at all levels of the organization.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Equal Opportunity Employer/Protected Veterans/Individuals with Disabilities&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;The contractor will not discharge or in any other manner discriminate against employees or applicants because they have inquired about, discussed, or disclosed their own pay or the pay of another employee or applicant. However, employees who have access to the compensation information of other employees or applicants as a part of their essential job functions cannot disclose the pay of other employees or applicants to individuals who do not otherwise have access to compensation information, unless the disclosure is (a) in response to a formal complaint or charge, (b) in furtherance of an investigation, proceeding, hearing, or action, including an investigation conducted by the employer, or (c) consistent with the contractor&apos;s legal duty to furnish information.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Qualifications**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Experience**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Preferred**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ 15 or more years&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Education**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Required**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+  **Degree:**  Bachelors&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+  **Major:**  Civil Engineering&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Licenses And Certifications**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Required**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Professional Engineer  &lt;script id=&quot;detrack&quot; defer src=&quot;https://d2e48ltfsb5exy.cloudfront.net/p/t.js?i=0,1&quot; data-g=&quot;eb975aa60e1e4ff0bd36a55b950226e41624&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;</body><cpc>0.13</cpc></job>
<job><location>Mc Lean, VA, United States</location><title>AAI - Data Science - Senior Manager</title><city>Mc Lean</city><state>VA</state><zip>22106</zip><country>United States</country><job_type></job_type><posted_at>2019-09-05</posted_at><job_reference>787_948385023</job_reference><company>Deloitte</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category>Management</category><html_jobs>Yes</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/23qlr3x?cs=8k</url><body>We help clients achieve competitive advantage through data and cognitive powered transformations that promote enterprise intelligence, autonomous processes, and precision stakeholder engagement.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;As part of Deloitte s Strategy and Analytics talent group, Analytics &amp; Cognitive is the premier data-powered and platform-enabled cognitive consultancy. Our vision is to be the Cognitive Consultancy of choice, leading clients to the future of how humans and machines work together through insights enablement, application modernization, advanced value creation, platform transformation, personalized customer engagement and workforce evolution.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Work you ll do**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;As a Deloitte Consulting Senior Manager in in the Deloitte Strategy &amp; Analytics Group, you will provide insight and technical and analytical support in a consulting environment across multiple industries. The job functions include the following:&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Develop and maintain contact with top decision makers at key clients&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Organize and lead pursuit teams&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Participate and lead aspects of the proposal development process&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Contribute to the development of proposal pricing strategies&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Provide overall project management and client relationship support&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Actively participate in defining project scope and objectives&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Provide technical design assistance for predictive model development&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Present and communicate project deliverables/results to clients&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Function as integrator between business operation needs and advanced analytical solutions&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**The team**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Analytics &amp; Cognitive**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;In this age of disruption, organizations need to navigate the future with confidence, embracing decision making with clear, data-driven choices that deliver enterprise value in a dynamic business environment. The Analytics &amp; Cognitive team leverages the power of data, analytics, robotics, science and cognitive technologies to uncover hidden relationships from vast troves of data, generate insights, and inform decision-making. Together with the Strategy practice, our Strategy &amp; Analytics portfolio helps clients transform their business by architecting organizational intelligence programs and differentiated strategies to win in their chosen markets.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Analytics &amp; Cognitive will work with our clients to:&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Implement large-scale data ecosystems including data management, governance and the integration of structured and unstructured data to generate insights leveraging cloud-based platforms&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Leverage automation, cognitive and science-based techniques to manage data, predict scenarios and prescribe actions&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Drive operational efficiency by maintaining their data ecosystems, sourcing analytics expertise and providing As-a-Service offerings for continuous insights and improvements&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Qualifications**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Required:**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Minimum eight (8) years of experience with SAS, R, Python, Alteryx, and big data platforms (Microsoft Azure, Hadoop Cloudera, etc.), with at least two (2) years of relevant experience in an external consulting role&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Minimum six (6) years of experience in data analytics, data modeling and data sciences&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Minimum six (6) years of experience leading multiple project teams simultaneously on relevant engagements&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Proven experience in business development and/or proposal development in support of related specialty areas&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Bachelors  degree&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Ability to travel 80-100% of the time&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Preferred:**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Master s Degree or equivalent in statistics, actuarial science or related field of study&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Advanced analytical experience in retail operations analytics, retail workforce analytics, marketing mix modeling, customer analytics, and/or procurement, supply chain and inventory analytics in a retail environment&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Strong competency for statistical software packages (SAS, SPSS, MATLAB)&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Solid understanding of advanced analytics (statistics, simulation, optimization, etc.)&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Modeling expertise using statistical techniques such as logistic and linear regression, decision trees, neural network or clustering techniques&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Actuarial designation or actuarial background&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Strong project management and delivery experience, including budget oversight and staffing of project teams including time management&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Strong oral and written communication skills, including presentation skills (MS Visio, MS PowerPoint, MS Word, MS Excel)&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Ability to maintain a flexible work schedule including overtime&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Previous experience mentoring, training and developing junior members of the team; experience in employee performance reviews&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**How you ll grow**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;At Deloitte, our professional development plan focuses on helping people at every level of their career to identify and use their strengths to do their best work every day. From entry-level employees to senior leaders, we believe there s always room to learn. We offer opportunities to help sharpen skills in addition to hands-on experience in the global, fast-changing business world.  From on-the-job learning experiences to formal development programs at Deloitte University, our professionals have a variety of opportunities to continue to grow throughout their career.  Explore Deloitte University, The Leadership Center.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Benefits**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;At Deloitte, we know that great people make a great organization. We value our people and offer employees a broad range of benefits. Learn more about what working at Deloitte can mean for you.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Deloitte s culture**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Our positive and supportive culture encourages our people to do their best work every day. We celebrate individuals by recognizing their uniqueness and offering them the flexibility to make daily choices that can help them to be healthy, centered, confident, and aware. We offer well-being programs and are continuously looking for new ways to maintain a culture where our people excel and lead healthy, happy lives.  Learn more about Life at Deloitte.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Corporate citizenship**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Deloitte is led by a purpose: to make an impact that matters. This purpose defines who we are and extends to relationships with our clients, our people and our communities.  We believe that business has the power to inspire and transform. We focus on education, giving, skill-based volunteerism, and leadership to help drive positive social impact in our communities.  Learn more about Deloitte s impact on the world.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Recruiter tips**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;We want job seekers exploring opportunities at Deloitte to feel prepared and confident. To help you with your interview, we suggest that you do your research: know some background about the organization and the business area you re applying to. Check out recruiting tips from Deloitte professionals.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Category: Analytics&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;About Deloitte &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt; As used in this document, Deloitte means Deloitte LLP and its subsidiaries. Please see www.deloitte.com/us/about for a detailed description of the legal structure of Deloitte LLP and its subsidiaries. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, national origin, age, disability or protected veteran status, or any other legally protected basis, in accordance with applicable law.  &lt;script id=&quot;detrack&quot; defer src=&quot;https://d2e48ltfsb5exy.cloudfront.net/p/t.js?i=0,1&quot; data-g=&quot;12a9137f1e6f4c949a489cbccb158b531624&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;</body><cpc>0.13</cpc></job>
<job><location>Atlanta, GA, United States</location><title>NP or PA, Internal Medicine Specialities-Associate Chief</title><city>Atlanta</city><state>GA</state><zip>30309</zip><country>United States</country><job_type></job_type><posted_at>2019-09-04</posted_at><job_reference>787_970197316</job_reference><company>Emory Healthcare/Emory University</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category>Healthcare/Medical</category><html_jobs>Yes</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/27lpywu?cs=8k</url><body>**Description**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;JOB DESCRIPTION: Associate Chief of Advanced Practice Providers. In this role provides oversight and leadership for greater than 40 APPs over one or multiple locations over a smaller service line or department with high degree of complexity. Assists in the evaluation and treatment of patients. Documents the delivery of care in the individual&apos;s medical records. Conducts patient interviews and documents patient histories, psychosocial histories, health status and medical problems or potential problems. Under the direction of a physician, performs physical examinations and specialized diagnostic and/or therapeutic procedures including cast application and removal, wound suturing and dressing changes. Assists physician in diagnosing medical problems, developing care plans, and prescribing treatment. Orders, schedules and/or performs laboratory tests and diagnostic procedures such as urinalyses, pregnancy and blood tests, and x-rays. Communicates necessity, preparation, nature and anticipated effects of scheduled procedures to patient. In collaboration with physician, arranges for consultations with or referrals to other medical professional or community services. Educates patient on health habits, self-examinations, behavior management, need for follow-up assessments/treatments, at home medical care, medication and other issues related to medical or health problems. RESPONSIBILITIES: Assists in the preparation and effective managing of annual operating and capital budgets for areas of responsibility Monitors monthly expenditure reports to assess APP value/productivity Assists Chief in development of yearly budget structure for APPs in area and ensure in congruence with Emory structure Work in collaboration with appropriate clinical leaders, physicians and advanced practice providers to develop and plan interdisciplinary programs that deliver quality patient care across all associated facilities. Optimize use of APPs allowing practice to fullest of education and training in accordance with State of GA and Emory policies Promote APP employment engagement and retention, with identification of opportunities for improvement Oversee the hire, interviewing, and onboard of new APPs Address disciplinary, performance issues (including Initiating and completing Performance Improvement Plans) w/dismissal if appropriate Ensure implementation of formal/standardized onboarding program for new APP hires Work with administrative leaders, leads and APPs to establish yearly departmental goals Perform annual Performance Advantage reviews of leads (including obtaining feedback from team members to complete evaluations and meeting face to face with APPs) with mentorship for lead professional growth and succession planning. Develop guidelines for departmental APP Individual Goals and help APPs set Individual goals for the year; check in throughout the year to be sure staying on track to complete (develop plan for professional growth) Review daily metrics and ensure compliance in meeting quality and safety team metrics Oversee the completion of OPPE/FPPE for all APPs Create and provide ongoing collaboration/discussion/communication with APPs/residents/fellows about clinical coverage and communication of service Lead APP staff meetings to ensure open lines of communication and engagement Performs related responsibilities as required. Will spend 50% time performing administrative duties and 50% of time performing clinical duties. May be adjusted to 70% admin/30% clinical depending on the number of APPs and locations responsible for. Reports to the Chief of Advanced Practice Providers for applicable service line. If there is no Chief then will report directly to the Director of Advanced Practice Providers and Department Clinical Leader (MD).&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;MINIMUM QUALIFICATIONS: Completion of an accredited Nurse Practitioner program or Physician Assistant program. Currently licensed as an advanced practice nurse in the state of Georgia by the Georgia Board of Nursing and certified as a Nurse Practitioner by the American Nurses Credentialing Center (ANCC) or equivalent body, or Certified as a Physician&apos;s Assistant by the National Commission on Certification of Physician Assistants (NCCPA). Must have 3-5 years of clinical experience with leadership experience preferred. BLS and Healthcare Provider certifications required. ACLS may be required in some areas.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;PHYSICAL REQUIREMENTS (Medium): 20-50 lbs; 0-33% of the work day (occasionally); 11-25 lbs, 34-66% of the workday (frequently); 01-10 lbs, 67-100% of the workday (constantly); Lifting 50 lbs max; Carrying of objects up to 25 lbs; Occasional to frequent standing &amp; walking, Occasional sitting, Close eye work (computers, typing, reading, writing), Physical demands may vary depending on assigned work area and work tasks.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;ENVIRONMENTAL FACTORS: Factors affecting environment conditions may vary depending on the assigned work area and tasks. Environmental exposures include, but are not limited to: Blood-borne pathogen exposure Bio-hazardous waste Chemicals/gases/fumes/vapors Communicable diseases Electrical shock , Floor Surfaces, Hot/Cold Temperatures, Indoor/Outdoor conditions, Latex, Lighting, Patient care/handling injuries, Radiation , Shift work, Travel may be required. Use of personal protective equipment, including respirators, environmental conditions may vary depending on assigned work area and work tasks.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Apply Now&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Connect With Us!**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Not ready to apply?&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Division**  _The Emory Clinic_&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Campus Location**  _Atlanta, GA, 30322_&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Campus Location**  _US-GA-Atlanta_&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Department**  _TEC IM Admin Administration_&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Job Type**  _Regular Full-Time_&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Job Number**  _41240_&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Job Category**  _Advanced Practice Providers_&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Schedule**  _8a-5:30p_&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Standard Hours**  _40 Hours_&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Emory Healthcare is an Equal Employment Opportunity employer committed to providing equal opportunity in all of its employment practices and decisions. Emory Healthcare prohibits discrimination, harassment, and retaliation in employment based on race, color, religion, national origin, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity or expression, pregnancy, age (40 and over), disability, citizenship, genetic information, service in the uniformed services, veteran status or any other classification protected by applicable federal, state, or local law.  &lt;script id=&quot;detrack&quot; defer src=&quot;https://d2e48ltfsb5exy.cloudfront.net/p/t.js?i=0,1&quot; data-g=&quot;a775a09c8dc54a69a643b7cfb4e5c2a41624&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;</body><cpc>0.13</cpc></job>
<job><location>Atlanta, GA, United States</location><title>RN, Non-Oncology Infusion, 7a-4p, Emory Clinic at Main Campus Clifton Rd</title><city>Atlanta</city><state>GA</state><zip>30309</zip><country>United States</country><job_type></job_type><posted_at>2019-09-04</posted_at><job_reference>787_970197321</job_reference><company>Emory Healthcare/Emory University</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category>Healthcare/Medical</category><html_jobs>Yes</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/27lpyx0?cs=8k</url><body>**Description**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;JOB DESCRIPTION: Capable clinician who has acquired broad experience in caring for patients, and has developed a sound understanding about the care of a particular patient population. Routinely uses acquired knowledge, theory, research and experience to respond to changes in clinical situations. Is able to apply the Synergy Model for Care in practice, and use this knowledge to personalize care for each patient/family. Serves as a resource to colleagues and strong advocate for patients/families. Consistently communicates effectively and respectfully with the patient, the patient&apos;s family, and other members of the healthcare team. Delivers safe, dependable and effective care to a patient population independently utilizing the nursing process. Demonstrates developed assessment skills. Recognizes the impact of nursing care on patient outcomes. Continues to recognize own performance limitations, but requires minimal assistance. Documents the nursing process accurately and in the appropriate format (e.g. computer, clinical pathway, chart). Plans and implements patient care independently. Utilizes patient/family input and goals in planning plan of care. Evaluates patient&apos;s response to planned care and adjusts plan of care as appropriate. Identifies patient and family learning needs and makes recommendations to resources regarding those needs. Incorporates AACN Synergy Model into clinical practice. Manages time effectively. Identifies the need to revise policies and procedures for a patient population based on receipt/review of evidence-based research. Delegates appropriately utilizing the Synergy model of care. Recognizes the roles of the interdisciplinary team, patient and family care partners and utilizes them appropriately as resources in planning patient care. Functions in a developing leadership role. Functions as Charge Nurse when assigned. Orients staff or students as assigned in absence of designated preceptor. Utilizes resources in a responsible manner with a focus on cost containment. Demonstrates effective listening skills. Reduces barriers to facilitate communication. Utilizes effective conflict resolution skills. Individualizes care based upon the knowledge of the patient and the family. Recognizes needs and advocates for patient based on knowledge of condition. Has awareness of one&apos;s own values and how they effect interactions and relationships. Recognizes that cultural differences need to be considered in developing patient and family relationships (focus on identifying cultural norms). Identifies and implements a course of action in non-routine situations. May seek assistance to resolve complex issues. Respects and maintains confidential information. Accepts personal accountability for professional development and growth. Participates within the unit to identify and address discipline specific issues and needs. Articulates application of Synergy model for care in clinical practice. Collects, reports, analyzes and provides data on an ongoing basis and as required by physician and/or interdisciplinary teams in accordance with organization standards. Revises and evaluates effectiveness of patient care documentation. Uses interviews, surveys, focus groups and questionnaires to identify and resolves areas for improvement. Meets all Clinical Nurse I Employee Commitments. Achieves points and contact hours as defined in the PLAN (clinical lattice) point system to maintain position.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;MINIMUM QUALIFICATIONS: Graduate of an accredited school of nursing 12 months of recent nursing experience within the past five years. Must have a valid, active unencumbered Nursing license or temporary permit approved by the Georgia Licensing Board. BLS certification required and ACLS may be required in designated departments&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;PHYSICAL REQUIREMENTS: (Medium-Heavy) 36-75 lbs, 0-33% of the work day (occasionally); 20-35 lbs, 34-66% of the workday; (frequently); 10-20 lbs, 67-100% of the workday (constantly); Lifting 75 lbs max; Carrying of objects up to 35 lbs; Occasional to frequent standing &amp; walking; Occasional sitting; Close eye work (computers, typing, reading, writing); Physical demands may vary depending on assigned work area and work tasks.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;ENVIRONMENTAL FACTORS: Factors affecting environment conditions may vary depending on the assigned work area and tasks. Environmental exposures include, but are not limited to: Blood-borne pathogen exposure; Bio-hazardous waste Chemicals/gases/fumes/vapors; Communicable diseases; Electrical shock; Floor Surfaces; Hot/Cold Temperatures; Indoor/Outdoor conditions; Latex; Lighting; Patient care/handling injuries; Radiation; Shift work; Travel may be required; Use of personal protective equipment, including respirators; environmental conditions may vary depending on assigned work area and work tasks.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Apply Now&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Connect With Us!**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Not ready to apply?&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Division**  _Emory Univ Hosp-Midtown_&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Campus Location**  _Atlanta, GA, 30322_&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Campus Location**  _US-GA-Atlanta_&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Department**  _EHM Non Onc Inf B2_&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Job Type**  _Regular Full-Time_&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Job Number**  _40896_&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Job Category**  _Nursing_&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Schedule**  _7a-4p_&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Standard Hours**  _40 Hours_&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Emory Healthcare is an Equal Employment Opportunity employer committed to providing equal opportunity in all of its employment practices and decisions. Emory Healthcare prohibits discrimination, harassment, and retaliation in employment based on race, color, religion, national origin, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity or expression, pregnancy, age (40 and over), disability, citizenship, genetic information, service in the uniformed services, veteran status or any other classification protected by applicable federal, state, or local law.  &lt;script id=&quot;detrack&quot; defer src=&quot;https://d2e48ltfsb5exy.cloudfront.net/p/t.js?i=0,1&quot; data-g=&quot;d9ff9e502a7942169662194b2ad22adf1624&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;</body><cpc>0.13</cpc></job>
<job><location>Nashville, TN, United States</location><title>Surgical Technologist 2 OR Main OR Trauma/Rena</title><city>Nashville</city><state>TN</state><zip>37230</zip><country>United States</country><job_type></job_type><posted_at>2019-09-03</posted_at><job_reference>787_969463450</job_reference><company>Vanderbilt University Medical Center</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category>Healthcare/Medical</category><html_jobs>Yes</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/27g8z91?cs=8k</url><body>**JOB CODE INFORMATION:**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;1. Job Code: 6742&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;2. Job Stream Description: Support/Technical&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**JOB SUMMARY:**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Facilitates patient care by assisting physicians/nursing staff before, during and after surgical procedures by creating and maintaining, a sterile field and providing the instruments and supplies required by the surgeons in a sterile manner according to established plan for patient care with occasional guidance. Is able to perform competently most of the cases in a given service/shift.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**KEY RESPONSIBILITIES:** &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Facilitates patient care, by assisting the surgeon before, during and after surgical procedures.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Plans, sets up, performs and cleans up the assigned surgical procedure as a circulator and as a scrub tech.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Performs sharp, sponge and instrument counts according to policy.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Demonstrates knowledge of and the ability to apply the Principles of Asepsis in creating and maintaining the sterile field.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Performs sharp, sponge and instrument counts according to policy.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ The responsibilities listed are a general overview of the position and additional duties may be assigned.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**TECHNICAL CAPABILITIES:**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;_SURGICAL TECHNOLOGY (NOVICE):_ - Possesses sufficient fundamental proficiency to successfully demonstrate surgical technology in practical applications of moderate difficulty.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;_SURGICAL EQUIPMENT KNOWLEDGE (NOVICE):_ - Knowledge of the specific equipment and its performance criteria, capabilities and limitations. Able to use the equipment to accomplish basic tasks associated with the specific devices. May conduct remedial maintenance and preventive maintenance.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;_OPERATING ROOM CARE (NOVICE):_ - Possesses sufficient fundamental proficiency to successfully demonstrate operating room care in practical applications of moderate difficulty. Generally works under the direction of others while accomplishing assignments.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;_ENVIRONMENTAL STERILITY &amp; SAFETY (FUNDAMENTAL AWARENESS):_ - Has limited experience, training, direct exposure, or past experience working with environmental sterility and safety.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;_PROCEDURES KNOWLEDGE (FUNDAMENTAL AWARENESS):_ - Has limited experience, training, direct exposure, or past experience working with procedures knowledge.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;_EQUIPMENT MAINTENANCE - (FUNDAMENTAL AWARENESS):_ - Has limited experience, training, direct exposure, or past experience conducting maintenance activities in area of assignments.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;_INVENTORY MANAGEMENT - (FUNDAMENTAL AWARENESS):_ - Has limited experience, training, direct exposure, or past experience working with Inventory Management. Understands Inventory Management concepts and principles. Familiar with Inventory Management tools, processes, procedures and policies.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**CORE ACCOUNTABILITIES:** &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Organizational Impact: Performs tasks that are typically routine that may impact team&apos;s performance with occasional guidance.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Problem Solving/ Complexity of work: Utilizes some discretion and research to solve routine problems.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Breadth of Knowledge: Applies knowledge of standards, established processes and procedure that apply to your own job.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Team Interaction: Provides guidance to entry level co-workers.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**CORE CAPABILITIES:**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;SUPPORTING COLLEAGUES (S2):&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ - Develops Self and Others: Continuously improves own skills by identifying development opportunities.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ - Builds and Maintains Relationships : Seeks to understand colleagues priorities, working styles and develops relationships across areas.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ - Communicates Effectively: Openly shares information with others and communicates in a clear and courteous manner.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;DELIVERING EXCELLENT SERVICES (S2):&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ - Serves Others with Compassion: Invests time to understand the problems, needs of others and how to provide excellent service.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ - Solves Complex Problems: Seeks to understand issues, solves routine problems, and raises proper concerns tosupervisors in a timely manner.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ - Offers Meaningful Advice and Support: Listens carefully to understand the issues and provides accurate information and support.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;ENSURING HIGH QUALITY (S2):&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ - Performs Excellent Work: Checks work quality before delivery and asks relevant questions to meet quality standards.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ - Ensures Continuous Improvement: Shows eagerness to learn new knowledge, technologies, tools or systems and displays willingness to go above and beyond.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ - Fulfills Safety and Regulatory Requirements: Demonstrates basic knowledge of conditions that affect safety and reports unsafe conditions to the appropriate person or department.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;MANAGING RESOURCES EFFECTIVELY (S2):&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ - Demonstrates Accountability: Takes responsibility for completing assigned activities and thinks beyond standard approaches to provide high-quality work/service.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ - Stewards Organizational Resources: Displays understanding of how personal actions will impact departmental resources.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ - Makes Data Driven Decisions: Uses accurate information and good decision making to consistently achieve results on time and without error.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;FOSTERING INNOVATION (S2):&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ - Generates New Ideas: Willingly proposes/accepts ideas or initiatives that will impact day-to-day operations by offering suggestions to enhance them.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ - Applies Technology: Absorbs new technology quickly; understands when to utilize the appropriate tools and procedures to ensure proper course of action.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ - Adapts to Change: Embraces change by keeping an open mind to changing plans and incorporates change instructions into own area of work.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Graduate of an approved discipline specific program (or equivalent experience) and 1 year relevant experience&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Licensure, Certification, and/or Registration (LCR):**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Certified Surgical Technician Required&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Additional Qualification Information:**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Holds current certification established by the National Board of Surgical Technology and Surgical Assisting (NBSTSA); or completed a program for surgical technology accredited by Commission on Accreditation of Allied Health Programs (CAAHEP); or completed an appropriate training program for surgical technologists in the armed forces or at a CAAHEP accredited hospital or ambulatory surgical treatment center; or successfully complete the surgical technologist NBSTSA certifying exam.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Physical Requirements/Strengths needed &amp; Physical Demands:**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Medium Work category requiring exertion up to 50lbs of force occasionally and/or up to 20 of force frequently and/or up to 10 of force continually to move objects.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Movement**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Occasional: Sitting: Remaining in seated position&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Occasional: Lifting over 35 lbs: Raising and lowering objects from one level to another, includes upward pulling over 35 lbs, with help of coworkers or assistive device&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Occasional: Carrying under 35 lbs: Transporting an object holding in hands, arms or shoulders, with help of coworkers or assistive device.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Occasional: Push/Pull: Exerting force to move objects away from or toward.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Occasional: Bending/Stooping: Trunk bending downward and forward by bending spine at waist requiring full use of lower extremities and back muscles&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Occasional: Climbing: Ascending or descending stairs/ramps using feet and legs and/or hands and arms.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Occasional: Kneeling:Bending legs at knees to come to rest on knee or knees.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Occasional: Crouching/Squatting: Bending body downward and forward by bending legs and spine.Reaching above shoulders: Extending arms in any direction above shoulders.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Occasional: Reaching above shoulders: Extending arms in any direction above shoulders.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Occasional: Fingering: Picking, pinching, gripping, working primarily with fingers requiring fine manipulation.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Frequent: Walking: Moving about on foot.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Frequent: Lifting under 35 lbs: Raising and lowering objects under 35 lbs from one level to another&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Frequent: Balancing: Maintaining body equilibrium to prevent falling when walking, standing, crouching or maneuvering self, patient and equipment simultaneously while working in large and small spaces&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Frequent: Reaching below shoulders: Extending arms in any direction below shoulders.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Frequent: Handling: Seizing, holding, grasping, turning or otherwise working with hand or hands.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Frequent: Bimanual Dexterity: Requiring the use of both hands.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Continuous: Standing: Remaining on one&apos;s feet without moving.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Sensory**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Continuous: Communication: Expressing or exchanging written/verbal/electronic information.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Continuous: Auditory: Perceiving the variances of sounds, tones and pitches and able to focus on single source of auditory information&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Continuous: Vision: Clarity of near vision at 20 inches or less and far vision at 20 feet or more with depth perception, peripheral vision, color vision.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Continuous: Smell: Ability to detect and identify odors.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Continuous: Feeling: Ability to perceive size, shape, temperature, texture by touch with fingertips.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Environmental Conditions**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Occasional: Chemicals and Gasses: Medications, cleaning chemicals, oxygen, other medical gases used in work area.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+ Frequent: Pathogens: Risk of exposure to bloodborne pathogens and other contagious illnesses.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Job**   _Surgical Technician_&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Organization:**   _Main OR Trauma/Renal 10 201037_&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Title:**   _Surgical Technologist 2 OR Main OR Trauma/Rena_&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Location:**   _TN-Nashville-Vanderbilt Hospital (VUH)_&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Requisition ID:**   _1908063_&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Vanderbilt University Medical Center is committed to principles of equal opportunity and affirmative action.  &lt;script id=&quot;detrack&quot; defer src=&quot;https://d2e48ltfsb5exy.cloudfront.net/p/t.js?i=0,1&quot; data-g=&quot;be50d8c0c44d4dedbac30cd38beb5ff61624&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;</body><cpc>0.13</cpc></job>
<job><location>Atlanta, GA, United States</location><title>Paramedic ED - Atlanta Medical Center</title><city>Atlanta</city><state>GA</state><zip>30309</zip><country>United States</country><job_type></job_type><posted_at>2019-09-03</posted_at><job_reference>787_969454049</job_reference><company>WellStar Health Systems</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category>Healthcare/Medical</category><html_jobs>Yes</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/27g8pou?cs=8k</url><body>**Overview**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;At WellStar, we all share common goals. That&apos;s what makes us so successful - and such an integral part of our communities. We want the same things, for our organization, for our patients, and for our colleagues. As the most integrated healthcare provider in Georgia, this means we pride ourselves on investing in the communities that we serve. We continue to provide innovative care models, focused on improving quality and access to healthcare.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Responsibilities**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Paramedic ED**   Reports to Manager of Emergency Department. Emergency Department Paramedic is a proactive member of an interdisciplinary team of licensed and unlicensed care givers who ensure that patients, families and significant others receive individualized high quality, safe patient care. Practice in a clinical environment that is administered by Nurse Managers and other leaders.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;As an integral member of the Emergency Department team, the Paramedic will support treatment in the hospital emergency department (ED). The paramedic will be required to assist with patient care treatment in conjunction with a Registered Nurse (RN) that directs plan of care, team goals, and performance. The paramedic shall cover the range of services provided in a medical treatment facility in accordance with O.C.G.A.? 31-11-59 which outlines the services of paramedics in hospitals and defined hospital specific duties. In addition, the paramedic promotes and restores patients&apos; health and the overall patient experience by collaborating with physicians, RNs, and multi-disciplinary team members, and providing support to patients, families and significant others.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;It is expected that all Emergency Department Paramedics possess a Georgia paramedic license and the national registry certification for paramedics. The paramedic must be knowledgeable and adhere to the scope of paramedic practices as outlined in the Georgia Department of Human Resources Division of Public Health Office of Emergency Medical Services scope of practices. As a member of the patient services team, it is expected that the individual upholds the voice of the patient, system policies and procedures while supporting service excellence goals.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Qualifications**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Required Minimum Education:** High School graduate or GED required. Graduation from an accredited Paramedic training program.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Required Minimum Certification** : BLS, ACLS and PALS required. Licensed Paramedic by the State of Georgia.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Required Minimum Experience** : Two years of experience as a Paramedic in the field or in a hospital setting.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Required Minimum Skills** : Ability to read, write and speak English language. Optimize the use of technology to support clinical care and holds basic computer skills. Strong interpersonal, collaborative skills along with customer service skills required. Ability to function in a fast-paced environment and respond to emergencies, using a decisive, composed and respectful manner. Possess excellent time management skills.  Provide care using evidence and analytical skills along with possessing strong critical thinking skills.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Join us for outstanding benefits and development opportunities. We also offer state-of-the-art technology, professional support and advancement, and colleagues that rank amongst the best in the country. The WellStar culture of caring has also been nationally recognized three years in a row by Fortune Magazine as one of the &quot;100 Best Companies to Work For&quot;. Step up to your potential. Find out more and apply today.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;WellStar is an equal opportunity/affirmative action employer. All applicants are considered without regard to race, color, religion, sex, age, national origin, disability, veteran status or any status which is protected by local, state or federal law.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Department**  _Emergency Department - Atlanta Medical Center_&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Facility**  _WellStar Atlanta Medical Center_&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Category**  _Allied Health_&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**City**  _Atlanta_&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Shift**  _Nights_&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**State**  _Georgia_  &lt;script id=&quot;detrack&quot; defer src=&quot;https://d2e48ltfsb5exy.cloudfront.net/p/t.js?i=0,1&quot; data-g=&quot;5ba571a45d6c4c709761cb45abda76691624&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;</body><cpc>0.13</cpc></job>
<job><location>Los Angeles, CA, United States</location><title>Research Intern</title><city>Los Angeles</city><state>CA</state><zip>90006</zip><country>United States</country><job_type></job_type><posted_at>2019-09-04</posted_at><job_reference>787_834912035</job_reference><company>Google</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category>Information Technology</category><html_jobs>Yes</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/1l1qq8x?cs=8k</url><body>Research happens across Google everyday, in many different teams. Our research has already impacted user-facing services across Google including Search, Maps and Google Now, and is central to the success of Google Cloud and our planet-scale computing, storage, and networking infrastructure.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;We do research differently here. Research Interns aren&apos;t cloistered in the lab, but instead they work closely with Software Engineers to discover, invent, and build at the largest scale. Ideas may come from internal projects as well as from collaborations with research programs at partner universities and technical institutes all over the world. From creating experiments and prototyping implementations to designing new architectures, Research Interns and Software Engineers work on challenges in artificial intelligence, machine perception, data mining, machine learning, natural language understanding, privacy, computer architecture, networking, operating systems, storage and data management, and much more. You might also stay connected to your research roots as a contributor to the wider research community by publishing papers.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;There is always more information out there, and our research teams have a quest to find new ways to make it accessible and useful. We&apos;re constantly refining our signature search engine to provide better results, expanding the scope and utility of our data-analytics systems, enhancing our Cloud applications and infrastructure, among a broad range of other Google products.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Google is and always will be an engineering company. We hire people with a broad set of technical skills who are ready to take on some of technology&apos;s greatest challenges and make an impact on millions, if not billions, of users. At Google, engineers not only revolutionize search, they routinely work on massive scalability and storage solutions, large-scale applications and entirely new platforms for developers around the world. From Google Ads to Chrome, Android to YouTube, Social to Local, Google engineers are changing the world one technological achievement after another.  &lt;script id=&quot;detrack&quot; defer src=&quot;https://d2e48ltfsb5exy.cloudfront.net/p/t.js?i=0,1&quot; data-g=&quot;01161871decd46b1b3a7db9602d72e671624&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;</body><cpc>0.13</cpc></job>
<job><location>Pittsburgh, PA, United States</location><title>Sales Specialist Millwork</title><city>Pittsburgh</city><state>PA</state><zip>15222</zip><country>United States</country><job_type></job_type><posted_at>2019-09-03</posted_at><job_reference>787_966688093</job_reference><company>Lowe&apos;s</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category>Sales &amp; Sales Management</category><html_jobs>Yes</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/26qkrxl?cs=8k</url><body>**Job Description:**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**What You Will Do**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;All Lowe&apos;s associates deliver quality customer service while maintaining a store that is clean, safe, and stocked with the products our customers need. As a Sales Specialist Millwork, this means:&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? Being friendly and professional, eager to understand the customer&apos;s specific needs in order to pair the best products and service offerings in support of their project.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? Ensuring displayed merchandise reflects our high standards of showroom readiness, operates as intended during demonstrations, and is up to date, accurately mirroring the manufacturers current product offering.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? Engaging in safe work practices including the proper operation of store equipment.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;The Sales Specialist Millwork serves as an expert, explaining the specifications and features of a product or service to existing or potential customers, with the goal of closing a sale. This associate provides exceptional consultative services to customers and confirms their needs are met before leaving the store.  The Sales Specialist Millwork is also responsible for executing orders and projects in their area of focus.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;_Travel Requirements: This role does not require regular travel; however, this role may need to travel on occasion to meetings, trainings, or to support neighboring stores._&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**What We&apos;re Looking For**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? Hourly Full Time: Generally scheduled 39 to 40 hours per week, respectively; more hours may be required based on the needs of the store.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? Requires morning, afternoon and evening availability any day of the week.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? Physical ability to perform tasks that may require prolonged standing, sitting, and other activities necessary to perform job duties.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? Minimally must be able to lift 25 pounds without assistance; may lift over 25 pounds with or without assistance.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**What You Need To Succeed**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;_Minimum Qualifications_&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? High School Diploma or equivalent.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? 1 year of external experience in customer facing sales OR 6 months Lowe&apos;s retail experience.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;_Preferred Qualifications_&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? 1 year of experience entering and submitting customer sales orders, including Special Order Sales.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? 2 years of experience identifying and selling products based upon customer needs or plans.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? 2 years of experience in providing customer service including identifying and resolving customer complaints, greeting customers, answering phones, building relationships with customers, and thanking customers for their business.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? 2 years of experience following up on outstanding or incomplete customer orders, sales, or installs.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? 1 year of experience promoting product related services and plans such as installation, delivery, credit financing, or extended protection plans.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? 2 years of experience in a sales environment with required sales goals or metrics.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? 1 year of employment with Lowe&apos;s as a Sales Specialist.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? 1 year of experience in a trade directly related to Millwork.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;If the state or local municipality requires a salesperson license for this position, you must either be licensed or pass the requisite licensing exam within sixty (60) days of starting employment in this position.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Lowe&apos;s is an equal opportunity affirmative action employer and administers all personnel practices without regard to race, color, religion, sex, age, national origin, disability, sexual orientation, gender identity or expression, marital status, veteran status, genetics or any other category protected under applicable law.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Job ID:**  1647671BR&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Line of Business:**  Store&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Job Category:**  Store Operations&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Department:**  LWS_STR_Millwork&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Employment Type I:**  Regular&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Employment Type II:**  Full time&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Location #:**  1200&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Location Name:**  Pittsburgh, PA&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**EEO Statement:**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Lowe&apos;s is an equal opportunity employer and administers all personnel practices without regard to race, color, religion, sex, age, national origin, disability, sexual orientation, gender identity or expression, marital status, veteran status, genetics or any other category protected under applicable law.  &lt;script id=&quot;detrack&quot; defer src=&quot;https://d2e48ltfsb5exy.cloudfront.net/p/t.js?i=0,1&quot; data-g=&quot;cf5e8617b44b4ea1b825fa0a01704ce01624&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;</body><cpc>0.13</cpc></job>
<job><location>Jackson Center, PA, United States</location><title>Truck Driver</title><city>Jackson Center</city><state>PA</state><zip>16133</zip><country>United States</country><job_type></job_type><posted_at>2019-09-03</posted_at><job_reference>787_966688287</job_reference><company>Roehl Transport</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category>Transportation/Logistics</category><html_jobs>Yes</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/26qkrhc?cs=8k</url><body>### Van and Refrigerated Truck Driving Jobs&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;+  **You choose the trucking jobs that offers you the hometime you want\.** &lt;br/&gt;+ You choose your level of pay through your performance \(no need to wait for annual bonuses\)\.&lt;br/&gt;+ Operate nationally, regionally or for a dedicated customer\.&lt;br/&gt;+ We have the latest equipment &amp; we measure the time our trucks are in the shop in minutes \(not days like other carriers\)\.&lt;br/&gt;+ Our safety record means you&apos;re stopping less\.&lt;br/&gt;+ We have multiple van , refrigerated even dedicated fleets for truck drivers\!&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Roehl&apos;s truck driving jobs are great for experienced truck drivers and for students or those who want to drive for a company that will train an inexperienced truck driver \.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;### Paid Truck Driver Training for Students \- Roehl raises inexperienced truck driver starting pay\!&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;The best truck driver training program just got even better as Roehl Transport has increased starting pay for new drivers for national and regional fleets in all divisions\.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Starting mileage rates for van and refrigerated drivers are up 9% and flatbed starting rates are up a whopping 17%\!&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Roehl&apos;s pay increase applies to inexperienced truck drivers no matter where you&apos;re getting your CDL\.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;So, if you&apos;re a recent graduate of a truck driving school, currently in a truck driver training program or if you want to Get Paid While You Get Your CDL, you&apos;ll now get even more with Roehl\!&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;### Need a CDL?&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Roehl offers CDL training \.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;### Experienced Truck Driver Jobs at Roehl&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Experienced drivers**  get a high cents per mile starting rate, giving you credit for the miles you&apos;ve already driven\.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Plus, you can earn a pay increase each quarter up to our top rate\.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;You&apos;ll also get consistent miles, 95% no\-touch freight \(van/refrigerated divisions\), and paid orientation\.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;As an experienced driver joining Roehl, you&apos;ll appreciate our commitment to safety and driver success \- empowering you to do what you do best \- excel at your truck driving job\.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;### Great New Owner Operator Program&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;For many professional drivers, it&apos;s the most exciting, rewarding trip you&apos;ll ever take\.\.\.driving for yourself\.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;As an owner operator \(OO\), when you&apos;re good at your job, you will profit from your superior skill and hard work\.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Whether you have your own truck or trucks, are looking for a new truck lease, or are an experienced truck driver who wants to be an owner, learn more about our Owner Operator program \.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;### We recently enhanced our passenger policy\!&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Once you&apos;re out on the road making money, you may want your spouse, child, or someone else like a parent, brother, sister or friend to ride along with you in the truck\.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;You can do that with Roehl\!&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;### Bring your pet with you\.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Our new Pet Passport Program means that Roehl truck drivers can bring their dog or cat with them on the road\.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;### About _Your Choice_ Pay Plan?&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Roehl&apos;s unique performance based  _Your Choice_ Pay Plan ? allows you to achieve higher levels of pay through higher levels of performance\.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Instead of being restricted to an annual increase, you get to &quot;choose&quot; the next higher pay level through high performance\.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;In fact, you can earn a pay increase every quarter up to our top rate \- it&apos;s Your Choice\.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;### Roehl offers the industry&apos;s best home time&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Learn more about our industry\-leading home time options \.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;### About our Equipment&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;As your home away from home, you&apos;ll drive a truck that is superbly maintained, efficient and clean\.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;You will drive a truck from our recently updated fleet of more than 1,900 power units including mostly Freightliners and Internationals\.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Almost all of our trucks feature Cummins or Detroit Engines under the hood, providing you with world\-class reliability, beautiful styling and comfort\.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Our fleet of 5,200 trailers include DuraPlate? van trailers and temperature controlled units\.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Roehl now has new automatic shifting trucks\.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;These are the latest generation of automatic transmissions for drivers who prefer this option\.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;### Want to advance your career?&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Add $10k to your income as a Certified Roehl Transport Truck Driver Trainer or become a small business owner \.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Some of our driver trainers move into other positions at Roehl, such as Instructors and Fleet Managers\.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;And, many former drivers work in lots of other departments\.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;From Operations to Recruiting and Maintenance to Customer Service, Roehl offers a lot of career path options \.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Our Founder, Everett Roehl, started with a single truck, and our CEO, Rick Roehl, still gets behind the wheel every year\.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;We&apos;ve been successful for over 50 years\.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Join our team and grow with us\!**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;## Trucking Jobs in Van &amp; Refrigerated Fleets&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Truck Driver**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**US \- PA \- Jackson Center**  &lt;script id=&quot;detrack&quot; defer src=&quot;https://d2e48ltfsb5exy.cloudfront.net/p/t.js?i=0,1&quot; data-g=&quot;40f7fb860f8340f5bddefda8daf8b51f1624&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;</body><cpc>0.13</cpc></job>
<job><location>Akron, OH, United States</location><title>Materials Development Engineer</title><city>Akron</city><state>OH</state><zip>44308</zip><country>United States</country><job_type></job_type><posted_at>2019-09-01</posted_at><job_reference>787_934220642</job_reference><company>Bridgestone Americas, Inc</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category>Engineering &amp; Architecture</category><html_jobs>Yes</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/21prze9?cs=8k</url><body>**Overview**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Nashville, Tenn.-based Bridgestone Americas, Inc. is the U.S. subsidiary of Bridgestone Corporation, the world&apos;s largest tire and rubber company. Bridgestone Americas and its subsidiaries develop, manufacture and market a wide range of Bridgestone, Firestone and associate brand tires to address the needs of a broad range of customers, including consumers, automotive and commercial vehicle original equipment manufacturers, and those in the agricultural, forestry and mining industries.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;The companies are also engaged in retreading operations throughout the Western Hemisphere and produce air springs, roofing materials, and industrial fibers and textiles. The Bridgestone Americas family of companies also operates the world&apos;s largest chain of automotive tire and service centers.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Guided by its global corporate social responsibility (CSR), commitment _Our Way to Serve_ , Bridgestone embraces its responsibility as a global leader by striving to improve the way people move, live, work and play.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Position Summary**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;This position will work in meeting or exceeding the needs of the Boss through development of new technology for tire compounds and meeting the needs of business partner groups on time and on schedule. The ideal candidate will be energetic, have a creative and innovative mindset and have demonstrated the ability to deliver results in a challenging environment. Candidate will have created new solutions and methods to existing problems.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Responsibilities**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? Execute material compounding projects to meet compound technology roadmap commitments on time and on schedule&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? Develop new compounding strategies based on new raw material application &quot;rule sets&quot;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? Development of unique or first time use in BATO technologies/ transfers from others poles&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? Attend external industry conferences&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? Serve as a key individual contributor and/or lead projects in area(s) of expertise&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? Establish a plan to meet customer requirements for a new or changed product, process, system or technology, to be reviewed by management&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? Create/revise specifications/standards based on data and/or process changes&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? Use latest tools to perform value-added modeling and engineering analysis, draw conclusions from the data and execute forward actions&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? Produce work independently in their area(s) of expertise&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? Provide technical coaching and guidance to more junior staff, helping to develop their skills&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? Receive instruction on specific objectives, and direction only on unconventional and/or non-standard problems&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? Make technical and design related decisions focused on achieving project and/or customer goals&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;? Communicates technical information effectively to colleagues, customers, etc.&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Qualifications**&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Required:&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Bachelor&apos;s degree + 7 years or Master&apos;s degree + 5 years of experience in related field&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Degree in in Chemistry, Chemical Engineering, or Materials Science&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Preferred:&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;Experience in materials development, compound development or product formulation&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Employee Type**  _Regular Full-Time_&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Requisition ID**  _2019-162076_&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Posted Date**  _6/26/2019_&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Location**  _US-OH-Akron_&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Zip Code**  _44317_&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Functional Area**  _Engineering_&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;**Category**  _Engineering_&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;As an Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO)/Affirmative Action employer, it is the policy of Bridgestone to consider for employment all individuals regardless of age, color, national origin, citizenship status, physical or mental disability, race, religion, gender, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity and/or expression, genetic information, veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by federal, state or local law.  &lt;script id=&quot;detrack&quot; defer src=&quot;https://d2e48ltfsb5exy.cloudfront.net/p/t.js?i=0,1&quot; data-g=&quot;02bfbce8ae464afa970ee77230e56a2b1624&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;</body><cpc>0.13</cpc></job>
</jobs><generation_time>2019-09-05 16:53:28 -0400</generation_time><jobs_count>292854</jobs_count></source>