<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><source><jobs>
<job><location>UniversityPark, TX, United States</location><title>Entry Level Software Engineer</title><city>UniversityPark</city><state>TX</state><zip></zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Full Time</job_type><posted_at>2018-12-27</posted_at><job_reference>6874_afb82f92b9aa8e87b6a62b202df1b653</job_reference><company>Revature</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/1c9pwvi?cs=e3e</url><body>nbsp nbsp Revature is the fastest growing employer of emerging technology talent in the US and we are currently looking to hire over 100 new Software Engineers.  nbsp nbsp Our Software Engineers design, analyze and build next-gen software systems, including business applications, games, computer applications, middleware, and network control systems across a variety of industries, including finance, insurance, retail, healthcare and government.  nbsp nbsp Revature has been featured in the Wall Street Journal, Money, Time, on MSN, and was recently named as one of the 8 Cool Companies to Apply to in 2018 With Awesome Benefits   httpswww.glassdoor.comblogcompanies-awesome-benefits-2018  by Glassdoor.  nbsp nbsp Join us and be part of the next generation of Software Engineers. Interviews are starting now!  nbsp nbspWhat We Are Looking For  MUST have a Bachelor&apos;s Degree (preference given to Computer Science, Engineering and STEM majors )  0-3 years experience  Excellent problem solver  Solid understanding of Object Oriented Programming  Outstanding verbal and written communication skills  Exposure to one of the following Java, Javascript, C++, CSS  Solid foundational knowledge of SQL  Willing to relocate anywhere in the US  Must be authorized to work in the US on a permanent basis - ability to secure US government security clearance if needed  Ability to relocate anywhere in the US   nbsp nbspRevature is not currently sponsoring work visas or transfers at this time.  nbsp nbspWhat We Offer  Competitive Salary  Relocation Assistance  Corporate Housing  Health, Vision and Dental Insurance  Paid Time Off  Enterprise level development training  Life Insurance  401K  Mentoring and on-going support throughout your entire Revature career  Experience with one of the world&apos;s most largest and most reputable companies in the US   nbsp nbspSuitable candidates are encouraged to apply immediately  Not Mentioned</body><cpc>0.23</cpc></job>
<job><location>Houston, TX, United States</location><title>Information Security Professional- Threat &amp; Risk Management</title><city>Houston</city><state>TX</state><zip>77002</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Full Time</job_type><posted_at>2018-12-28</posted_at><job_reference>6874_9fbff498dc608197deb19e4242874c66</job_reference><company>Harris County ITC</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/1dcewlb?cs=e3e</url><body>Harris County was founded in 1836 and is located in the Gulf Coast region of Texas approximately 50 miles from the Gulf of Mexico. Harris County covers over 1700 square miles with over 4 million residents, making it the most populous county in Texas and third most populous in the United States.   The Harris County Central Technology Services (CTS) exists to support the mission of Harris County by developing, implementing and supporting high quality, innovative and cost effective information technology solutions.   Job Description Under minimal direction, designs and executes vulnerability, threat and incident management processes to help ensure cybersecurity risks and threats are proactively identified and addressed to maintain the protection of Harris County information and information systems.enspenspenspensp enspResponsibilities include bull Leads the design and implementation of vulnerability management tools and processes bull Executes vulnerability management processes and outcomes to ensure proactive discovery and remediation of risks bull Effectively communicates security vulnerabilities and risks to issue owners and consults on remediation efforts bull Facilitates routine vulnerability management review meetings with stakeholders to drive remediation efforts bull Serves as a senior subject matter expert on vulnerability and threat management bull Analyzes vulnerability data to determine broad issuestrends and to determine root cause problems bull Researches, designs and implements solutions to address the root cause problems on behalf of the enterprise bull Governs and enforces cybersecurity policies and vulnerability remediation deadlines bull Utilizes and enforces the utilization of cybersecurity and vulnerability management procedures, tools and internal reportingtracking mechanisms bull Develops and maintains executive dashboards andor regular reports to communicate department-specific cybersecurity risks and threats bull Develops procedures, training materials, metricsmeasures packages, reports, project plans, and communication and executive presentations with little guidance, as needed to support the overall delivery of cybersecurity objectives bull Participates on Cybersecurity Incident Response Team (CIRT) investigation and response activities as required bull Demonstrates in-depth knowledge and understanding of the global threat landscape, cybersecurity trends, emerging technologies and an ability to relate them to the county and its objectives bull Must be able to weigh business needs against security concerns and articulate issues to management and stakeholders bull Works on multiple projects as a subject matter expert, including projects or issues of high complexity that require in-depth knowledge across multiple technical areas and business segments bull May serve as a general security subject matter expert and project consultant to IT staff and other departmentsagencies as necessary to support the demand for cybersecurity expertise bull May also participate in the evaluation and implementation of other new security solutions and technologies.    Requirements EDUCATION  Bachelor&apos;s degree in Computer Science, Information Systems or similar area of study from an accredited college or university is required   EXPERIENCE A minimum of 5 years of progressive work experience in Information Security is required, including direct experience designing, implementing and executing vulnerability, incident or threat management processes, tools and technologies to include   bull Hands-on experience operating vulnerability scanning, incident detection  response (IDR) or penetration testing tools bull Experience designing, implementing and executing vulnerability, threat or incident management processes bull Experience performing vulnerability assessments or penetration tests bull Experience validating, analyzing and prioritizing reported vulnerability and security risks bull Ability to build and maintain strong relationships across departmentsteams and effectively communicate vulnerability findings to issue owners and support remediation efforts bull Exceptional leadership, verbal and written communication, and project management skills bull Ability to confront challenges in a constructive fashion and influence others through consensus building techniques bull Strong organizational skills, including the ability to drive adherence to cybersecurity processes and tools and to keep focus on multiple tracks of work and open issues in parallel bull Strong technical writing, research, analysis and analyticalproblem solving skills bull A passion for cybersecurity, self-starter mentality, flexibility and willingness to take on new challenges and ability to thrive in a team environment     Preferences   EDUCATION  Certified Information Systems Security Professional (CISSP), Global Information Assurance Certification (GIAC) or CompTIA Security+ Certification is preferred ensp EXPERIENCE bull Experience in security event analysis, monitoring and response technologies and processes bull Experience in threat intelligence gathering, research and analysis bull Experience participating in Cybersecurity Incident Response Team (CIRT) activities bull Experience consulting with business and technology partners on general security requirements and best practices   A broad understanding of cybersecurity concepts across all domains, applicable security models (e.g. ISO 2700X, NIST and CIS Critical Security Controls) and regulations (e.g. SOX, PCI, HIPAA and CJIS)   General Information   40 hours per week  Monday ndash Friday. Weekends and 24 on-call infrequently, as needed   Applicants for this position will be subject to a criminal background check that includes being fingerprinted. This applies to any position with network access to CJI (Criminal Justice Information) systems or access to an area where CJI is received, maintained or stored either manually or electronically (i.e. custodian, maintenance). Automatic Disqualifiers - Conviction, probation, or deferred adjudication for any Felony - Conviction, probation, or deferred adjudication for any Class A Misdemeanor - Conviction, probation, or deferred adjudication for a Class B Misdemeanor if within the previous 10 years - Open arrest for any criminal offense (Felony or Misdemeanor) - Family Violence conviction</body><cpc>0.41</cpc></job>
<job><location>New York, NY, United States</location><title>Technical Support Analyst</title><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><zip>10001</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Contractor</job_type><posted_at>2018-12-25</posted_at><job_reference>6874_81f3e4a6c43aa4ec5c8690a172048698</job_reference><company>DTG Consulting Solutions Inc.</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/199mw5c?cs=e3e</url><body>Technical Support Analyst - NYC   William Barry wbarrydtgconsulting.com, 212-629-4660   Job Qualifications Required Skills This position provides hands-on technical support the client support functions, which principally includes the Service Desk. In addition, the position provides engineeringtechnical support andor liaises with the IT Engineering Group as required and performs some systems administration duties. This Senior Technical Support Engineer will implement and troubleshoot client-facing hardware and software solutions. More generally, the Technical Support Engineer will assist the Director, Client Services in ensuring the timely delivery of high quality technical support, supporting system administration and end user computing environments, addressing information security-related issues, and managing day-to-day IT operations. Responsibilities bull Resolve a spectrum of IT user technology-related issues via the Service Desk providing end-to-end customer service (i.e., from ticket assignment to issue resolution) bull Deliver and install hardware and configure software as part of the School on-boarding process and as needed. bull Provide ongoing technical support to the Student Laboratory and confirm equipment is functioning as required. bull Implement patching and software upgrading of all Juilliard devices including Windows and Macintosh clients using appropriate tools. Publish periodic reports summarizing patch status of all network-attached devices. bull Assist in managing user accounts provide quality, consistent and timely end-user support to Juilliard staff, faculty, students and Alumni. bull Solid experience with Active Directory, Group Policy, Okta, Azure, Office 365, and Remote Access experience with Citrix environment and Virtual Private Network (VPN) bull Under the direction of the CTO, and Director, Client Services, participate in I.T. solutions research, technology assessments and pilot projects designed to enhance the range and quality of IT services provided to the Juilliard community.  bull Respond rapidly to IT disruptions.  bull Support asset provisioning and tracking efforts across the enterprise and thereby ensure updated inventory is distributed and status recorded bull Publish, review andor provide significant input to a monthly report summarizing key Service Desk metrics. emsp Minimum Requirements bull Appropriate technical certifications bull Experience in servicing a complex Windows domain bull Experience and familiar with Windows PC, Macintosh, mobile devices, and printersscanners bull Knowledge of Office 365 bull Ability to communicate technical information to non-technical personnel bull Excellent knowledge of computer security systems, applications, procedures, and techniques bull Strong interpersonal and communication skills and the ability to work effectively with a wide range of constituencies in a diverse community  William Barry wbarrydtgconsulting.com, 212-629-4660</body><cpc>0.41</cpc></job>
<job><location>Pennington, NJ, United States</location><title>.NET/UI Developer</title><city>Pennington</city><state>NJ</state><zip>08534</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Contractor</job_type><posted_at>2018-12-28</posted_at><job_reference>6874_c2b22b520eefdc413200ef2c214005ca</job_reference><company>Matlen Silver</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/199lzzi?cs=e3e</url><body>.NETUI Developer Great communication skills, project management skills, proven ability to be a technical lead for a project and to lead the team of junior developers. Technical knowledge required Senior knowledge of JavaScript development using OO JS concepts and various JS librariesFrameworks ndash AngularJS, typescript plus nice-to-have npm, systemJS, gulp, grunt, FluxReact  HTML5CSS3, jQuery .NET REST Services development, .NET WCF Services development SQL Server Database development Experience in designing enterprise level applications and delivering design artifacts SADs, LLDs, arch. diagrams Experience in communicating to business partners to come up with technical requirements from business requirement Any experience with knowledge managementcontent management systems is helpful</body><cpc>0.41</cpc></job>
<job><location>Woburn, MA, United States</location><title>Salesforce/Steelbrick CPQ Project Manager</title><city>Woburn</city><state>MA</state><zip>01801</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Contractor</job_type><posted_at>2018-12-28</posted_at><job_reference>6874_f8a59ed95b89180e31c7de13a7319d3a</job_reference><company>Endure Technology Solutions, Inc.</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/19w2y65?cs=e3e</url><body>Position Senior Project ManagermdashSalesforceSteelbrick CPQ Location Woburn, MA Duration 9 Month+ Contract  Keys  This role is for a Project Manager to run a project implementing Spring CM (Contract and Document Management) and CPQ (Configure Price Quote) on top of their Salesforce platform thatrsquos already in production. This person must be sharp and have the Salesforce CPQ experience. Should have a history managing CPQ implementations   Our client is looking for a Project Manager to help run a big implementation of Spring CM and CPQ on top of their existing Salesforce platform. This person will need to work with vendors and multiple stakeholders to keep this project on track and delivered successfully.  Responsibilities  Create  followenhance a repeatable framework for a project structure to account for all IT required tasks Create and manage detailed project plans for projects with clear identification of resources, dependencies, risks and milestones. Develop detailed cost estimates for the project. Develop change management procedures for the project and milestone sign-off criteria. Drive integration project plans with clear metrics, operating mechanisms and regular updates to stakeholders. Identify and manage project risks escalate as needed for resolution. Improve project management processes and increase efficiencies Manage relationships with cross-functional project partnersservice providers Demonstrate ability to create executive summaries and reports.    Best Regards, Rhea Moraes Technical Recruiter Endure Technology Solutions Tel 703-853-1668 Fax 703-544-8827  tel703-544-8827  Email mrheaendure.tech  mailtomrheaendure.tech</body><cpc>0.41</cpc></job>
<job><location>Stillwater, OK, United States</location><title>iOS Developer</title><city>Stillwater</city><state>OK</state><zip>74075</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Full Time</job_type><posted_at>2018-12-29</posted_at><job_reference>6874_c2f54f21161d3662ff905d600593f594</job_reference><company>LexisNexis - Risk Solutions</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/199mdv9?cs=e3e</url><body>iOS Developer  SST Software is looking for Developers that can make things happen with iOS development. This position will help create wonderful applications for Apple mobile devices that utilize the services and knowledge of SST in precision agriculture.  Candidate must have the talent to easily switch contexts and know their way around iOS development tools and techniques. Candidate must have the ability to deal with everything from high level conversations down to task writing.   Skills and Responsibilities Responsible for writing software in a small team Participate in design and planning sessions Strong knowledge of Swift andor Objective-C Understanding of OOD and OOP   Excellent troubleshooting skills     Preferred Knowledge and Skills Experience working with REST-based web services. Relational database experience (preferably SQLite) Automated testing    EducationExperience  3-5 yearsrsquo experience    Benefits SST offers competitive pay and outstanding benefits including two weeks paid vacation each year, 401(k) matching, Medical, Vision, Dental, and Disability Insurance, shyFlex Spending Account and Career Development.</body><cpc>0.41</cpc></job>
<job><location>Los Angeles, CA, United States</location><title>Full-Time Senior FPGA Design Engineer</title><city>Los Angeles</city><state>CA</state><zip>90024</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Full Time</job_type><posted_at>2018-12-25</posted_at><job_reference>6874_b6872efe02f3822f952a62e6e4994930</job_reference><company>Silvus Technologies, Inc.</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/199mrpn?cs=e3e</url><body>Silvus Technologies is seeking FPGA Design Engineers to participate in the design and development of our StreamCaster line of MIMO mesh networking products and participate in advanced wireless systems RD. Must be a U.S. person (permanent resident or citizen) due to clients under government contract The Opportunity Silvus Technologies is a fast-growing, wireless engineering company located in the heart of West Los Angeles. Founded in 2004, Silvus has developed and produced multiple generations of its StreamCaster line of MIMO radios minus the most technologically advanced Mobile Ad-Hoc Networking (MANET) solution available. In addition to our successful MANET product line, Silvus also conducts ground breaking research in the area of wireless data communications and has executed on over 54M in RD contracts for the US government and commercial entities. Our technical team members possess very strong interdisciplinary capabilities and have provided innovative solutions to a broad range of important challenges for customers in military communications, law enforcement, public safety, commercial broadcasting, unmanneddrone systems and more. Technical Responsibilities Our FPGA designers actively participate in all aspects of the development process from concept to field deployment FPGA design architecture definition Fixed point system simulations RTL coding and test bench development FPGA design synthesis and timing closure Hardware verification and troubleshooting  Qualifications Must be a U.S. person (permanent resident or citizen) due to clients under government contract MSEE required, Ph.D in Electrical Engineering a plus 4+ years of FPGA design experience required Proficient in VHDL (preferred) or Verilog (2+ years preferred) Experience with Digital Signal Processing (DSP), MIMO, wireless systems is a plus Experience with multiple clock-domain, high-speed, high-utilization FPGA designs Experience with Xilinx FPGAs, SoCs and the Vivado IDE Experience with MatlabCC++ is a plus (2+ years preferred) Ability to pass background check</body><cpc>0.41</cpc></job>
<job><location>Albany, NY, United States</location><title>Oracle DBA @@ Albany, NY</title><city>Albany</city><state>NY</state><zip>12201</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Full Time</job_type><posted_at>2018-12-28</posted_at><job_reference>6874_9445c7d2a978aac0e9ec99efee1ee402</job_reference><company>Sriven Systems Inc.</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/1emiu14?cs=e3e</url><body>Hi, Greetings from Sriven Systems! Please go through the below Position and If you are interested send me your Updated Profile with Contact details   In case if you are not currently available or not interested in the below position, I apologize for the inconvenience and request you to forward my mail to your friends or colleagues whom you feel would excel this opportunity.   Role Oracle DBA   Location Albany, NY  Duration Long Term    Primary Responsibilities bull            Create schemas, tables and role based security based on requirements and direction from the team bull            Assist users with both basic SQL questions and sophisticated SQL tuning strategies bull            Test backup and recovery scenarios, as well as formulate disaster recovery procedures bull            Use Enterprise Manager and other tools for availability and performance monitoring bull            Analyze database resource consumption, for problem avoidance and trend forecasting bull            Install, upgrade and patch Oracle databases so that our environments remain current bull            Automate database administration tasks using PLSQL and shell scripts bull            Strong working knowledge of security controls required for regulatory compliance. This includes areas of encryption, centralized logging, inactive disablement, un-intrusive logging techniques, STIG change protocol and implementation, secure coding requirements, account management and access control standards. bull            Work closely with Security Auditors to remediate regular penetration test findings. bull            Work with engineers in support of SSO authentication requirements. bull            Set-up new users and reset passwords for existing users.   To be considered for this position, applicants need to meet the qualifications listed in this posting.   Required Qualifications  bull            5+ years of experience with Oracle RDBMS, SQL and PLSQL bull            5+ years of experience with UnixLinux knowledge including Shell scripting bull            3+ yearsrsquo experience managing multi-terabyte Oracle database environments bull            3+ Data Warehouse experience bull            Experience with and willingness to support 24x7 production environments bull            ASM and RMAN Experience bull            Work experience in Oracle 12c bull            Perform Database Upgrade to new Oracle version quarterly. Applying security patches more frequently when needed bull            Support of service level agreement bull            Experience with Oracle Performance Monitoring  Tuning bull            Strong Understanding of Oracle Optimizer, optimizer parameters, parsing mechanism and how optimizer influences in controlling, stabilizing execution plans bull            Accomplished in handling Performance Benchmarking and configuration, of in-memory database tuning and other middleware bull            Effective interpersonal skills bull            Thorough knowledge of Dimensional Data Modeling and traditional ER modeling and leveraging Performance Impacts on data warehouse systems bull            Healthcare experience bull            Exceptional troubleshooting and analytical problem-solving skills bull            Strong communications skills and collaborative work style bull            Strong working knowledge of security controls required to meet health care regulatory requirements.   Preferred Qualifications bull            Strong knowledge in Exadata bull            State Medicaid Data Warehouse or Medicaid Management Information Systems knowledge bull            Experience with MedicaidHealth Exchange data bull            Informatica tuning experience to assist ETL developers in meeting SLA load requirements. bull            Tableauperformance tuning experience.   If you are interested send me your Updated Profile with Contact details dicesrivensys.com  mailtodicesrivensys.com  (OR) Call631-259-4349.</body><cpc>0.41</cpc></job>
<job><location>Plano, TX, United States</location><title>CA IDM Developer</title><city>Plano</city><state>TX</state><zip>75023</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Contractor</job_type><posted_at>2018-12-26</posted_at><job_reference>6874_b1258ce0da79a3fe3446ecafe5939796</job_reference><company>Sysmind, LLC</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/1ecim9q?cs=e3e</url><body>Hi, Position CA IDM Location  Plano TX Contract  12 month +  bull Design and implement one or more of the following from the CA IDM suite, including but not limited to IdentityMinder, SiteMinder, SiteMinder Federation, ControlMinder, GovernanceMinder, and the CA Directory  bull Develop identity management system requirements, processes, and design specs based on organizational needs  bull Implement new functionality in IDM system based on organizational requirements  bull Provide production support to Identity Management system developed  bull Develop new solutions based on requirements and analysis  bull Design and configure CA IDM components including resource adapters and synchronization  Qualifications bull MS or Bachelor&apos;s degree in Computer Science, Management Information Systems, or related field with minimum 5 yearsrsquo experience  bull Working knowledge of the following technologies  o Firewall Rules, Networking, Application Servers, Web Servers, Active Directory, ADAM (LDS), LDAP, Windows, UNIX  bull Ability to manage setup and configuration of Policy servers, Web agents, Secure Proxy Server  bull Ability to resolve or manage SiteMinder production issues  bull Experience on configuring federated applications  bull Ability to monitor performance metrics and tune the system.  bull Strong experience with one or more directories, including Active Directory, Sun Directory Server, or CA Directory  bull Working Knowledge of programming language like Java, J2E etc.  bull Must have hands on deployment experience with CA products  bull Strong oral and written communication skills (MS Visio, MS PowerPoint).  bull Strong problem solving and troubleshooting skills with the ability to exercise mature judgment. bull Ability to travel up to 25 preferred Nice to have  middot Exposure to support process. middot Management consulting experience  - Experience on Mainframes, MQ series, Java, J2EE, Unix Scriptiing, etc middot Experience working with various verticals (i.e. financial services, insurance, retail, healthcare, technology)  - Familiarity with supporting J2EE applications that use WebSphere and Apache Webserver.  Thanks and Regards Rajat Chauhan Email Rajatcsysmind.com Phone 609-897-9670 Extn 3523 Address 38 Washington Road, Princeton Junction, NJ 08850</body><cpc>0.41</cpc></job>
<job><location>Los Angeles, CA, United States</location><title>Director of Mobile Software Development</title><city>Los Angeles</city><state>CA</state><zip>90069</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Full Time</job_type><posted_at>2018-12-28</posted_at><job_reference>6874_d4ed5ca68511730ab10e26bf297fb49d</job_reference><company>Robert Half Technology</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/199m1dr?cs=e3e</url><body>nbsp nbspTitle Director of Mobile Software Development  nbsp nbspIndustry Technology Startup  nbsp nbspLocation Los Angeles  nbspTarget Salary will depend upon experience  nbsp nbspEligible for Bonus amp Equity Yes  nbspBenefits strong health, dental, vision benefits, 401K matching, generous vacation and sick time  nbsp nbsp This is a chance to work on an exciting new technology for a heavily funded startup. This individual will be a hands-on manager responsible for building the mobile software team from the ground up. Expertise with Objective-C, Swift, Java, iOS SDK and Android SDK required. Competitive compensation structure including benefits, bonus and equity.  nbsp Job Requirements  nbsp nbspResponsibilities and Requirements  nbsp  nbsp Expertise with Objective-C, Swift, Java, iOS SDK and Android SDK required.  nbsp Own and define the back end architecture required to deliver the future roadmap  nbsp Build the mobile software team in Los Angeles with exceptional engineering talent  nbsp Architect our complex mobile apps that push the limits of mobile technology  nbsp Develop code and review code as needed. Lead by example.  nbsp Conceptualize, develop, and launch new features  nbsp  nbsp nbsp EducationExperience  nbsp  nbsp 8+ years of experience developing mobile applications on iOS  nbsp BSBA degree in a technical field, such as Computer Science (or equivalent years of relevant experience)  nbsp  nbsp nbsp For immediate and confidential consideration please email your resume to Catherine Hamilton nbspat catherine.hamiltonrht.com   mailtocatherine.hamiltonrht.com    nbsp nbsp Connect with me on LinkedIN httpswww.linkedin.comincatherinehamiltonrht   httpswww.linkedin.comincatherinehamiltonrht</body><cpc>0.41</cpc></job>
<job><location>Andover, MA, United States</location><title>UX Design</title><city>Andover</city><state>MA</state><zip>01810</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Full Time</job_type><posted_at>2018-12-26</posted_at><job_reference>6874_b2548234ba33b90bb470d734e7b611d6</job_reference><company>Bernard, Nickels &amp; Associates</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/1cf3inm?cs=e3e</url><body>Job Title UX designer Type Perm Start Date asap Location Andover, MA Max BillSalary 75K to 95K, plus 5 bonus  Job Description Are you a UX designer UX Lead? Are you creative, passionate, polyvalent and autonomous? Do you have 3-5 years of professional experience?   Profile You have a Bachelors or Masterrsquos degree in UXUI Design from a Design school, with a solid artistic background You listen. You know how to collect, analyze and synthesize customer needs You know how to manage a project from the initial phase to the follow up of developments You are organized and effective to guarantee the quality of deliverables and deadlines You are agile, highly adaptable and able to work in a variety of contexts in a changing international environment You like to share your ideas and you have a collaborative temperament and working style You know how to communicate effectively and gain commitment    Missions Design the user interface of our applications in close collaboration with marketing and development teams, while conforming with the specificities of the companyrsquos brand design. Implement the UX process steps from upstream design thinking stages to the final mock-up, user testing, and development follow-up Lead the projects entrusted to our partner design agencies Ensure a permanent watch of UXUI trends and methods of innovation through design Evangelize marketing and RD teams about brand design and UXUI best practices    Required competencies Be able synthesize, step back, explain and argue simply Master UX methodologies and be able to adapt them to the specific context of each project Be able to prototype from laquo quick  dirty raquo up to laquo pixel perfect raquo storyboards, wireframes, user flows, interactive mockups, etc. Be able to design using a design system (guidelines and DSM) Master design tools (Sketch, Illustrator, Photoshop) and prototyping tools (Invision, Flinto, Principle) Be able to manage several projects in parallel and prioritize Understand web and mobile development technologies    Additional competencies appreciated Micro-interactions prototyping Front-end development</body><cpc>0.41</cpc></job>
<job><location>New York, NY, United States</location><title>Lead QA Automation Engineer</title><city>New York</city><state>NY</state><zip>10016</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Full Time</job_type><posted_at>2018-12-27</posted_at><job_reference>6874_f3ad99a507470ed1dfa8f5671b16aa70</job_reference><company>Ubergig</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/1dzj7mv?cs=e3e</url><body>Need to write in some JS syntax   someone with REAL automation  modern web application - javascript talks to APIs - APIs hit databases - and  Ed wants - &quot;I know how to automate your testing on API side and how to make testing efficient AND which tools to use&quot;   REQUIRE some form of knowledge of command line - can configure the jobs. What plugins do you need? Play around with the tools and set them up. THERE IS NO ONE ELSE TO DO THIS NOW. THERE IS NO DEVOPS. Command line execute shell and python scripts (not a guru but has this experience).  Someone who really understands performance testing websites. Is more about how much traffic you sustain before site fails. What if you were hosting in AWS and you paying for nodes, that cost could grow if you donrsquot know what your consumption is. AGAIN - REAL performance testing - what tools you would use AND how you would do it.   Job Purpose We present a unique opportunity to work with cutting-edge technology and business in the financial sector. This role is for a full-time Lead QA Automation Engineer.  Duties and Responsibilities  Build, modify, and maintain Test Automation Frameworks for Web applications  Interact with development teams to help implement optimized and re-usable functional test automation  Maintain the functional test portion of the Continuous Integration pipeline  Review automated test code to assure adherence to standards and to advise on optimization  Research, identify, and implement new test automation technologies  Define, document, and conduct training on test automation practices, tools, and coding standards  Troubleshoot application issues and report technical findings to development.  Knowledge and Experience  3+ years of experience in JavaScript  3+ years of experience working with UI test automation  3+ years of experience in developing test automation of RESTful APIs or Microservices  3+ years of automation or regression testing experience  2+ years of SQL experience  3+ years of experience with continuous integrationcontinuous deployment and build tools (i.e. JUnit, GIT, Maven, Jenkins or equivalent) and using an industry standard source control management system  Knowledge of test technology trends and Web frameworkstools (React, Angular, NodeJS, etc.)  Knowledge and experience of performance testing Web applications  Knowledge and experience of performance testing RESTful APIs or Microservices  Ability to diagnose application issues (reviewing applications logs, reviewing server stats, etc.)  Solid understanding of behavior driven development  Experience working in a continuous integration environment  Solid Understanding of Agile development lifecycle  Solid understanding of software testing practices  Excellent verbal, written, and interpersonal communication skills  Experience working with cloud services Selenium grids and cloud services device farms (Sauces Labs is preferred)  Core Competencies Competencies are the skills and behaviors that are critical both to your personal performance and to our continued success. The core competencies apply to every member of staff Teamwork  Offers time andor assistance to colleagues is widely regarded and respected as someone to go to for help  Fosters friendly and cooperative relationships with others colleagues enjoy working with the  employee  Shares knowledge and mentors staff works to develop othersrsquo knowledge as well as own  Gives and shares credit as appropriate  Contributes to recruiting and training efforts of others, including candidate referrals, job interviews and mentoring  Attends and participates in company and department level functions inside and outside of the office  Problem-Solving  Decision-Making  Demonstrates an understanding of the urgent nature of our business and the need to proactively find and fix problems quickly and effectively takes ownership and follows through on decisions doesnrsquot minimize or forget about problems  Determines and fixes root causes rather than just treating symptoms  Applies novel techniques to solve problems that are more ambiguous challenges long-held beliefs when necessary  Quickly and effectively identifies alternative solutions and the proscons of each confirms that a proposed solution has no unintended consequences  Takes steps to mitigate risk  Consults with colleagues and recommends solutions based on the best interests of customers and shareholders, even when the opinion is unpopular  Communication  Actively listens and speaks to, not over, others  Uses clear and constructive language orally and in writing  Communicates important developments to the relevant and appropriate audiences in a timely and consistent manner  Asks follow-up questions to ensure all points are understood  Takes time to objectively listen to all viewpoints before forming an opinion  Builds consensus among differing views  Professionalism  Integrity  Makes a positive impression represents the company well on the phone and in person, including maintaining attire and appearance that is consistent with company image and appropriate for employeersquos role  Models a lsquocan-dorsquo attitude and takes initiative as a self-starter inspires and motivates others to do the same  Embraces, rather than resists, additional responsibilities  Refrains from office gossip settles rather than creates conflict with and between others  Exhibits desired work habits including regular office hours and extra hours when necessary while minimizing breaks and non-work related activities  Adheres to all corporate policies makes prudent use of company resources</body><cpc>0.41</cpc></job>
<job><location>San Francisco, CA, United States</location><title>Distributed Computing Architect</title><city>San Francisco</city><state>CA</state><zip>94102</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Full Time</job_type><posted_at>2018-12-26</posted_at><job_reference>6874_82b8590ad492ba06d64b454c83f4d2f1</job_reference><company>Synechron Inc.</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/199m5u2?cs=e3e</url><body>About Synechron Synechron, one of the fastest-growing digital, business consulting  technology services providers, is a 500 million firm based in New York. Since inception in 2001, Synechron has been on a steep growth trajectory. With 8,000+ professionals operating in 18 countries across the world, it has presence across USA, Canada, UK, France, The Netherlands, Switzerland, Luxembourg, Serbia, Hungary, Germany, Italy, UAE, Singapore, Hong Kong, Philippines, Japan, Australia and Development Centers in India   Synechron is seeking a motivated Distributed Computing Architect with expert level programming in Java  Python  Scala to to drive design, technology decision and solution for large scale platform built for ML and artificial intelligence.   Job Description To build Web-based applications using J2EE Frame works like Spring, Hibernate, Webservice(SOAPRest), JMS, EJB, Angular JS, JSF and SQLPLSQL. To build application using Websphere Portal Assisted in Cluster maintenance, Cluster Monitoring and Troubleshooting, Managing and Reviewing data backups and log files. To analyze tools to mine data, Predictive analysis, evaluating the underlying patterns and implement complex algorithms for data analysis. iumlsbquomiddot Implement unified data platform to gather data from different sources using Kafka Java Producers and consumers. Develop Map Reduce programs using Apache Hadoop for analyzing the Big Data    Required Skills  Expert level programming in Java  Python  Scala Expert level programming knowledge at kernel level for spark, Kafka, graph DB Expert level programming in Disturbed programming  parallel programing  grid programming Expert at multi-threading programming Architect level person to drive design, technology decision and solution for large scale platform built for ML and artificial intelligence Knowledge of NLP algorithms, Data science and Machine learning with Deep Neural network as added advantage Design of data structures, APIs desired High performance high throughput programming experience Design of algorithms from ground up desired Masters or PhD in software engineering and AI, applied mathematics 15+ years of experience in core coding profile.no manager or ivory tower architects</body><cpc>0.41</cpc></job>
<job><location>Waukesha, WI, United States</location><title>C++ Application developer with Linux</title><city>Waukesha</city><state>WI</state><zip>53186</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Contractor</job_type><posted_at>2018-12-29</posted_at><job_reference>6874_da56501c951689e8322c604c42e72411</job_reference><company>Talent Junction, LLC.</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/1c64gtw?cs=e3e</url><body>Title C++ Application developer with Linux  Location Waukesha,WI  Education Bachelorrsquos Degree in Computer Science or in ldquoSTEMrdquo Majors (Science, Technology, Engineering and Math)  Required ExperienceSkills  - Minimum of 5 years of professional experience in software development OR Masterrsquos degree with 3 years of experience in software development.  - Strong analytical skills, knowledge of Object Oriented Analysis and Software Design Patterns  - Strong  Good development experience core CC++  - Good knowledge of Unix  Linux ( UbuntuREdhat) based platforms  - Experience working in a challenging and fast paced environment  - Experience with scripting skills (bash, Python, SQL, PERL, PHP, etc  - Experience working in complex software development projects  - Experience in all steps of the software development cycle and knowledge of configuration management tools</body><cpc>0.41</cpc></job>
<job><location>San Diego, CA, United States</location><title>Security Engineer</title><city>San Diego</city><state>CA</state><zip>92101</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Contractor</job_type><posted_at>2018-12-27</posted_at><job_reference>6874_bf24f03e899bab94316932687bebb4a5</job_reference><company>Infogroup Northwest</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/199m20o?cs=e3e</url><body>Title Security Engineer  Location San Diego  Type Contract to Hire  Job DE133708828   nbsp At IGNW (formerly InfoGroup Northwest), we use our deep technical insights, local market knowledge and rock-solid relationships and reputation to create exceptional business outcomes for people and companies every day. We are based in Portland, OR with global partnerships to deliver the industry&apos;s top technical solutions and talent to every one of our clients. Our clients, consultants, contractors, partners and employees choose IGNW because we tackle the tough problems, and we care deeply about people while we do it.   nbsp We are proud to foster a great team working environment, to offer highly competitive compensation and to offer full benefits packages including medical, Flexible Spending Accounts, dental and vision. If you would like to learn more, join our team, or explore how IGNW can benefit your business, please reach out today!!   nbsp Project Scope  A Security Engineer is part of the client s Technology Solutions team. As a part if this team you will work directly with practice leadership and will be engaged in all aspects of client s post-sales business cycles. The primary role of a Security Engineer is to work alongside Project Managers (PMs) and Solutions Architects to successfully deliverquantify the technology solutions, services and business capabilities sold by client s Architecture Team. Security Engineers have strong technology and interpersonal skills that enable them to engage with client s customers, to deliver high-impact Security solutions.   nbsp Responsibilities  Working under the direction of the VP of Professional Services and Engineering Management.  Working alongside Solution Architects and Practice Leaders to deliver top notch solutions for client s customers biggest security challenges.  Contributing your breadth of technology knowledge to help the client realize the rewards of their solution purchase.  Staying connected to sales and project management teams to make sure projects are delivered seamlessly.  Recognizing other opportunities to contribute to client s customer success and development.  Training and mentoring the client s customers team on new security solutions you ve deployed.  Delivering engaging and informative presentationsreports on assessments performed.  Building strong and continuous relationship with client s customers, becoming their go-to advisor.   nbsp Requirements  You have a strong technology background that includes hands-on solution implementation.  You have a consulting background.  You have the expertise and professionalism to interact with client contacts.  You re a self-starter, you take initiative and have the ability to multi-task.  You have the ability to travel to customer s locations (as required).  High-level understanding of LANWANsecurity architectures, solutions, frameworks, and components.  High-level understanding of cloud computing technologies and workload transition challenges.  Hand s-on experience deploying network protection solutions such as firewalls, Anti-DDOS, IPS, SSL, VPN, DLP, NAC, WAF, SIEM.  Hand s-on experience deploying Endpointserverdata protection including antivirus, malware protection, webURL filtering, and MDM.  Hand s-On experience performing security operations including security monitoring, network and endpoint visibility, incident response, threat management, and forensics.  Hands-on experience performing Security Services such as Incident Response, Compliance Readiness Assessments, Penetration Testing, Security Optimization Services andor vulnerability scans.   The ideal candidate will have hands-on experience with the majority of the following technologies  A10 Networks SSLi  Aruba ClearPass  Cisco AMP for End Points  Cisco ASAFirePower Solutions  Cisco Email Security  Cisco ISE  Cisco Web Security  ForcePoint Web Security  McAfee Endpoint Protection Solutions  Palo Alto Networks PAN  Palo Alto Networks Traps  RSA 2-Factor Authentication  SonicWall Firewalls  Sophos Endpoint Solutions  Trend Micro Endpoint Solutions    nbsp Please note Our clients may require that candidates pass a drug andor background check.   nbsp To apply, please send your resume to resumesinfogroupnw.com   mailtoresumesinfogroupnw.com     nbsp nbsp Oregon&apos;s Top 100 Best Companies to Work For - 3 years running   nbsp IGNW has earned the Best of Staffing Award for providing remarkable service to hiring managers and job seekers. Check it out!  httpswww.bestofstaffing.comagenciesignw   httpswww.bestofstaffing.comagenciesignw    nbsp To view other IGNW opportunities please visit www.ignw.io   httpwww.ignw.io    nbsp IN   nbsp  nbsp  nbsp</body><cpc>0.41</cpc></job>
</jobs></source>