<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><source><jobs><job><location>Agoura Hills, CA, United States</location><title>DataCap Consultant</title><city>Agoura Hills</city><state>CA</state><zip>91301</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Full Time</job_type><posted_at>2018-12-10</posted_at><job_reference>6874_a23736af7db35cd49c86b82c644b4ed8</job_reference><company>Next Level Business Services, Inc.</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/199mif3?cs=e3e</url><body>Understand the client requirements and provide Solution. Building Imaging solutions using Datacap 9.0 Developing Custom Actions using .Net  VB Script for Datcap applications Deploying Datcap applications in High Availability environment Datacap Navigator configurations</body><cpc>0.20</cpc></job>
<job><location>Denver,, CO, United States</location><title>Java Developer</title><city>Denver,</city><state>CO</state><zip></zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Contractor</job_type><posted_at>2018-12-09</posted_at><job_reference>6874_d5c8f5ce7b6b7188834d75e45b3a5254</job_reference><company>Ascent</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/199nd7m?cs=e3e</url><body>Title Java Developer (with Python)  Location Denver, CO (LOCAL CANDIDATES ONLY)  Type ContractC2H    Responsibilities   This person will be part of a highly focused team of software innovators who develop network applications and services using telecom technologies such as SIP, IMS, VoIP, etc. Network capabilities such as real-time call control, call feature interaction and multimedia messaging are made accessible through web portals, web services, message buses, etc.     The qualified candidate must be able to work effectively in a team environment using Agile practices and be a self-starter.     This person will design and develop new applications primarily in Java using XML, web  bus services, integrated with services from Oracle DBMS  WeblogicOCCAS, Tibco, and other 3rd parties. This is a highly distributed services oriented architecture (SOA), that also exposes API39s to third parties. The person will interface frequently with product owners, architects and analysts to deliver solutions.     Key Logistics  1. Needs to be able to work from downtown location, however initial period could be at Mineral location.  2. 12+ month contract, may be hire option in future.    Qualifications  1. Python    Minimum Qualifications   Bachelor39s degree in Computer Science or related Engineering field, preferably with a Masters.     3-7 years experience designing and developing object oriented applications, web andor client applications using Java  XML, web services  message buses in SOA environment, API development.     3-5 years experience working in a telecommunications environment, preference given to the areas of call processing and messaging services using AIN, VoIP, IMS, SIP, SIP servlets, etc.     Desired Qualifications   Experience with several of the following WeblogicOCCAS, Tibco Bus, iBatis, Spring framework, Eclipse, Jakarta Apache commons, RESTSOAP Web services, Corba, Ajax, Oracle, Android, webRTC, HTML5, websockets.     Experience working in a product RD environment evolving complex architectures and innovative services, ideally using AgileLean.       If this is not a fit for you or you are not interested, Ascent Services Group offers an excellent Referral Bonus! We look forward to hearing from you!     About Ascent The Ascent Services Group (ASG) is a nationally recognized technology staffing and consulting firm whose fundamental business is providing staffing services to Small, Medium, and Large Enterprise clients in our core market verticals Financial Services, Healthcare, Technology and Life Sciences. As consultants for ASG, you will have access to many of the top clients within the industries we serve. Our goal is to deliver innovative talent through proven best practices and effective resource optimization. Become one of ASGrsquos candidates and experience the difference!</body><cpc>0.20</cpc></job>
<job><location>McKinney, TX, United States</location><title>Senior ICM Configurator</title><city>McKinney</city><state>TX</state><zip>75070</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Full Time</job_type><posted_at>2018-12-11</posted_at><job_reference>6874_867723f7c5bc722b98329dff43680d78</job_reference><company>Torchmark</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/199n3dh?cs=e3e</url><body>Job Description and Responsibilities Responsible for designing, developing, implementing and maintaining models with IBMs Cognos Incentive Compensation Management (ICM) system, formerly known as Varicent. Derive and understand business needs, and document findings Conduct discovery, design, build and unit testing activities for prescribed ICM model changes Design and implement data extracttransformload strategies for ICM models Participate in creating test plans, test cases, and performing unit and integration testing. Assist in planning and organizing tasks, report task progress, coordinate with team members during implementation. Support and maintain existing ICM applications - troubleshoot and fix defects, perform maintenance activities. Assist business partners with problems and resolve issues independently.  Knowledge and Experience  Business knowledge of the sales compensation business processes. Familiarity with variable incentive compensation applications such as IBM Cognos ICM (Varicent) or Oracle Incentive Compensation. Knowledge of software development and implementation lifecycles. Comfortable with emerging technologies, learning new software, understanding a data model and an object model, writing SQL queries, and writing design specifications. Experience with web technologies including HTML and JavaScript Experience in application support of production systems based on ITIL methodology. Knowledge and familiarity with database design and architecture, as well as general database development tools (SQL, PLSQL) Knowledge of ETL concepts and large volume data handling between systems. Knowledge of mathematical calculations to summarize and aggregate large volumes of data.</body><cpc>0.20</cpc></job>
<job><location>Windsor Locks, CT, United States</location><title>Teamcenter Team Lead</title><city>Windsor Locks</city><state>CT</state><zip>06096</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Contractor</job_type><posted_at>2018-12-09</posted_at><job_reference>6874_b6f8c20f0ddb3bb086c162e2cfb78a8c</job_reference><company>eclaro</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/1a44zyg?cs=e3e</url><body>ECLARO is a company that delivers talent. We provide fully customizable, comprehensive talent acquisition and management of seasoned professionals through a number of business models, including Consulting, Professional Hire, Global Integrated DeliveryTM and Managed Services.   Teamcenter Team Lead Eclaro is looking for a Teamcenter Team Lead who can work for a contract opportunity in South Windsor, CT. We encourage all authorized to work in the US to apply, we cannot subcontract.   Responsibilities and SkillsExperience required bull Lead team of Teamcenter developers and administrators in large Aerospace Company. bull Enterprise level project management and planning bull Helpdesk ticket process and experience bull Supervisory experience bull Engineering Support bull Strong Individual contributor and team player bull Effective communication skills     If interested see contact details below  Ashly T. Velasco Technical Recruiter Phone 646-357-1236 SMS 224-310-3251 Email ashly.velascoeclaro.com Send a Word resume along with the six digit position ID number, your hourly rate and availability.   ECLARO recruits and manages a staff of highly skilled individuals in an array of specialized disciplines. This approach enables our clients to leverage new opportunities, respond to increased and changing demands and increase their profitability. Please visit www.eclaroIT.com  httpwww.eclaroit.com  to see why the Right People are The AnswerTM.   Specialties Customized solutions for Human Capital and Talent Acquisition, Permanent placement and retained search, Recruiting, Staff Augmentation, Contract Labor, Managed Services, RPO, MSP, VMS, IT solutions, management and support, offshore business process outsourcing.   Equal Opportunity Employer Eclaro values diversity and does not discriminate based on Race, Color, Religion, Sex, Sexual Orientation, Gender Identity, National Origin, Age, Genetic Information, Disability, Protected Veteran Status, or any other legally protected group status.   Website httpwww.eclaro.com  httpwww.eclaro.com  Industry Staffing and Recruiting Type Privately Held Company Size 501-1000 employees Founded 1999</body><cpc>0.20</cpc></job>
<job><location>City Of Industry, CA, United States</location><title>Design Engineer - Security Systems</title><city>City of Industry</city><state>CA</state><zip>91714</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Full Time</job_type><posted_at>2018-12-09</posted_at><job_reference>6874_e9a6436979de1080d3f73c6e1e1622dc</job_reference><company>Engage2Excel</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/19jkcuz?cs=e3e</url><body>Leverage Your Experience in Electronic Security or Communication Systems to Join a Global Industry Leader in Integrated Security Solutions Make your mark in a newly added design role supporting a premier client. If you&apos;re looking for a challenging design engineer opportunity, where you&apos;ll work on interesting projects as a member of a collaborative, tight-knit team, look no further. As Design Engineer with the Systems Integration division of G4S USA, you&apos;ll create construction design packages for access control, video, communication and other system solutions. This is a role where you will Leverage the breadth of your skill-set and learn new skills and technologies where you may have gaps. Enjoy working on a wide variety of interesting projects for a large, important client. In fact, this role is being added specifically to meet the needs of this client and projects across three states. Have the autonomy to manage your assignment with minimal oversight, along with ample support when you need it. Join us during a transformative time in our history -- we&apos;re making strategic changes and pursuing strong growth. In our innovative, growth environment, you can make an impact, spotlight your talent and advance your career with G4S, here in California or at locations across the globe.  Enjoy the best of both worlds including The stability and resources of an evolving global corporation with more than 100 years of success, and The entrepreneurial atmosphere of a new initiative and a high-profile client.  Receive highly competitive compensation and an outstanding benefits package, including a company car. And while you will travel around Southern California, overnight travel is limited -- just a couple of weeks per year.  To meet the basic qualification for the Design Engineer, Security Systems opportunity, you must have legal authorization to work permanently in the United States for any employer without requiring a visa transfer or visa sponsorship. In addition, to be a good fit for the role, you will have A bachelor&apos;s degree in Engineering, Science, Business or another directly relevant discipline (highly preferred) or the equivalent combination of education and directly relevant experience an advanced degree in Engineering or a related field is a strong advantage. 6-10 years of experience in the electronic security or communication industries Strong experience in one or more of the following Access Control Systems Video Surveillance Systems Ethernet Switches and Routers Servers and IT Infrastructure Wired and Wireless Communication Systems  At vendor andor industry certifications preferred  G4S secures people, property and assets by understanding and mitigating security risk. We offer a suite of products and services, including risk consulting and investigations, systems integration, security software and technology, and security professionals. We provide security for governments, Fortune 500 companies, nuclear plants, petrochemical companies, ports, airports, colleges and universities, hospitals, banks, residential communities and more, and align services to deliver innovative, essential and scalable solutions that span your entire operation.  G4S Systems Integration bring systems together. We design, build and maintain stand-alone and integrated security systems. A trusted partner to customers and suppliers, G4S takes great pride in delivering outstanding expertise and superior service. We have the ability to provide full turnkey services taking a customerrsquos requirements, developing the concept, designing the network, selecting the product that best fits the requirements, and completing the installation.  EOEAAMFVetsDisabled</body><cpc>0.20</cpc></job>
<job><location>Los Angeles, CA, United States</location><title>Deployment Engineer, Google Apps</title><city>Los Angeles</city><state>CA</state><zip>90046</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Full Time</job_type><posted_at>2018-12-08</posted_at><job_reference>6874_db642a557a88750564bda333cd5ffeb9</job_reference><company>SADA Systems Inc</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/19elb66?cs=e3e</url><body>Join SADA Systems as a Deployment Engineer, Google Apps!    Primary Duties include the following Work with SADA team members and clients to understand technical and business requirements, then develop robust technical solutions leveraging Google products to meet these requirements Lead deployment and configuration tasks within customer environments, working individually or as part of a team Participate in the development of detailed project specifications and effort estimates taking into account feasibility and design. Communicate status and technical items with customer and internal stakeholders, identifying areas of technical risk and proposing different options for mitigating these risks Work on multiple projects at a time, both small and large  You Would Be Great For This Position If You Have BS degree in Computer Science or Information Systems 3 plus of years previous experience required Previous HelpdeskIT Support experience required Google APIs, such as Directory SDK, Apps Script Proxy configuration and troubleshooting Understanding of VPN concept OneDrive, Box, Dropbox Data governance Experience with databases, LDAP Experience in Security (Kerberos, SAML, NTML), Authentication vs Authorization, and Web Technology concepts Experience with networking Experience in migration between different messaging platformsversions Strong understanding of DNS, E-Mail Routing, Email Tracking, SMTP  application Mail Relay A positive attitude towards change and ability to adapt. Ability to handle customer situations with empathy and ownership Able to think critically and logically under pressure to resolve technical issues Absolute commitment to customer service and a ldquocan-do&quot; attitude Customer Advocacy Excellent interpersonal skills and the ability to work in a team environment and interact with all levels of management as well vendors and customers.  Strong problem solving and AnalyticalReasoning skills. Excellent written and oral communication skills. Well-proven time management skills while remaining flexible in responding to changing company andor client needs. Experience writing code for web based applications a plus Experience with programming with Java, Python, or similar language a plus Experience with Linux operating systems a plus  Why you&apos;ll love working at SADA You&apos;ll work with a great group of people, one of the best in the business, in a highly collaborative, team and results oriented atmosphere You&apos;ll have the opportunity to work in a dynamic and extremely positive environment where there is always the opportunity to challenge your skills and really move the needle Yoursquoll work with large, sophisticated and progressive clients throughout North America Unlimited PTO More awesome benefits include competitive and attractive compensation, huge performance based bonuses, holidays, medical, dental, vision, life, short and long term disability insurance, 401K and more</body><cpc>0.20</cpc></job>
<job><location>San Francisco, CA, United States</location><title>Pega Consultant</title><city>San Francisco</city><state>CA</state><zip>94104</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Contractor</job_type><posted_at>2018-12-10</posted_at><job_reference>6874_ee0d6721631dadd08f9739e453dc2a0f</job_reference><company>Xoriant Corporation</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/1a94aw0?cs=e3e</url><body>Job Title Pega Consultant Location Bay Area, CA Duration 6-12 months  Position Description  Min 5 years of Pega experience.   Must be CSSA or LSA certified  Will be working as an onsite coordinator.   Should have hands-on technical experience and be able to manage and understand the requirements from customer.   Cisco experience is add-on.   Thanks  Regards, Chakravarthi Kotni (Chuck) Xoriant Corporation  Phone 408-484-3154  chakravarthi.kotnixoriant.com</body><cpc>0.20</cpc></job>
<job><location>Scottsdale, AZ, United States</location><title>Lead Full Stack Developer</title><city>Scottsdale</city><state>AZ</state><zip>85258</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Contractor</job_type><posted_at>2018-12-09</posted_at><job_reference>6874_8abaf6ecc9e36b890fa191f3f05fa5ba</job_reference><company>Sharp Decisions</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/1aectl0?cs=e3e</url><body>Responsibilities Participates in all phases of SDLC from system analysis and design thru development and test to deployment and support. Provides development estimates and participates in project planning. Participates in designing and developing complex systems by writing Design Specifications description of framework, interfaces, services, reports, business components, and interaction between the components. Responsible for ensuring quality delivery of code through static and dynamic testing techniques Is able to troubleshoot any complex issues as well as provide support to production. Keep abreast of the current technologies and technological trends. Ability to learn and prototype new technologies, and recommend their use in the company products. May lead a team of developers, possibly offshore to ensure that the project is successfully completed. Peer mentoring experience of more junior team members. Ensures adherence to standards for self as well as team. Other duties as assigned    Requirements  Bachelor&apos;s degree in Computer Science or related field Minimum 9 years of experience as a Developer Minimum 2 years of experience as a Lead Developer Excellent written and verbal communication skills Demonstrated experience of estimation and planning Demonstrated abilities to successfully document and communicate software designs of complex systems. Proven history of developing and unit testing complex software components. Ability to be flexible, set priorities and meet deadlines in a changing environment for self as well as team. Must have decision-making skills for problem identification and solution recommendation. Ability to work independently and as part of a team while demonstrating initiative and using good business judgment Demonstrated ability to drive process improvement and improve the process efficiency Expert Knowledge in using Java and Java based frameworks Spring,Spring boot etc Hands on experience using Java script stack using AngularJS or ReactJS etc Expert knowledge in JSON, REST and SOAP web services Hands on experience with API integration Experience with GIT ,SVN etc Good understanding of unit testing frame works Junit etc Quick learner of new tools and technologies Ability to thrive in a fast-paced work environment Demonstrated ability to reduce andor prevent production defects based on the continuous root cause analysis and process improvement Ability to maintain effective working relationships across teams and with a diverse workforce Able to represent the Company in a positive and professional manner.  Nice to have  Experience with Node JS ,DOCKER containers ,Kubernetes Experience with MEAN stack and couchbase or any other NOSQL database Experience using Systemdata integration tools (i.e. Mirth Connect, iPAASSnapLogic , Mulesoft).</body><cpc>0.20</cpc></job>
<job><location>Bellevue, WA, United States</location><title>Application Security Engineer</title><city>Bellevue</city><state>WA</state><zip>98004</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Full Time</job_type><posted_at>2018-12-11</posted_at><job_reference>6874_d2a9d5a4524f4152c60f34e3cacc20a9</job_reference><company>Synectics</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/1aecstl?cs=e3e</url><body>Summary  As a member of the Application Security team, perform hands-on security assessments on the web, mobile, and console applications, working closely with technology and business partners across the company.  Ensure that both internally developed applications and third-party vendor applications are implemented in a manner that assures the highest security protections.  Stay ahead of the bad-actors at all times.  Identify and demonstrate the exploitation of the vulnerabilities in code and in run-time applications.  Perform staticdynamic code testing, manual code review, threat modeling, and penetration testing of internal web applications and external partner applications to identify vulnerabilities and security defects.  Support the implementation and enforcement of secure design principles according to policies, standards, and patterns of Information Security.  Work closely with feature teams early on in the design phase to ensure systems are built securely.  Develop and implement manual and automated web application security testing of web applications to enforce security standards    Qualifications  Must have at least 7+ years of experience in Application Security.  Must be very well versed with OWASP Top 10 vulnerabilities and must demonstrate to exploit such vulnerabilities in mobile, web and console applications.  Expertise in performing penetration testing on mobile, web, APIs, Web Services is a MUST.  Must be able to communicate at all levels in the organizations and when required you also need to act as a technical document writer.  Must be familiar with Fortify SCA (Expertise Advanced), Fortify Web Inspect (Expertise Advanced), Nessus, Nmap, Veracode, Burp Suite, ZED attack proxy, SCAP, Threat Modeling (e.g. STRIDE).  Hands-on application penetrationsecurity testers who can break into applications and find security flaws in the applications web, API, and mobile.  Telecom experience highly preferred    Since 1984, Synectics has been committed to aligning talented professionals with jobs they find challenging and fulfilling. Let us leverage our recruiting experience and our long-standing relationships with our clients to help you in your job search. To view a comprehensive list of jobs offered by Synectics, please visit our website at www.synectics.com  httpwww.synectics.com . We offer a wide variety of positions in cities throughout the United States. Synectics is an Equal Opportunity Employer. Donrsquot forget to follow us on LinkedIn, Twitter, and Facebook for news, updates, and new opportunities!</body><cpc>0.20</cpc></job>
<job><location>Allen Park, MI, United States</location><title>Web developer</title><city>Allen park</city><state>MI</state><zip>48101</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Full Time</job_type><posted_at>2018-12-09</posted_at><job_reference>6874_d65d46f6a4d4b5bea377e1a1a72b2d7f</job_reference><company>Wipro Ltd.</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/1aoln6k?cs=e3e</url><body>Job Title Web Developer  Location Allen Park, MI  Job Type Full timePermanent  Required Skills a. Web Development experience using HTML. b. Java Scripting experience c. Experience in ReactJs or Angularjs Framework   you can reach out at ummaboya.manjulawipro.com</body><cpc>0.20</cpc></job>
<job><location>Madison, WI, United States</location><title>Senior Retail CounterPoint Application Developer</title><city>Madison</city><state>WI</state><zip>53701</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Contractor</job_type><posted_at>2018-12-10</posted_at><job_reference>6874_cb1c907b2cbf6ade6cd35f497711faba</job_reference><company>blueStone, LLC</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/1ashc5k?cs=e3e</url><body>My client, a global leader in the retail vertical, is seeking a Sr. Retail CounterPoint Application Developer to join their team. This is an exciting opportunity, located just West of Madison, WI, with excellent benefits and a great family-oriented culture.  As a Sr. Retail CounterPoint Application Developer, you would be responsible for management of Point-of-Sale, Kiosk, and other retail technology systems.  Responsibilities Management of Point-of-Sale, Kiosk, and other retail technology systems Participate in the planning and support of retail systems Take a lead technical role in development and implementation of retail systems  Develop and create customized operational monitoring tools including alerts and dashboards that report on system performance and issues. Assess and recommend improvements to retail systems based on business and technical analysis. Lead retail technology implementations for new stores. Provide users with technical support and track issues through to resolution.  Qualifications Bachelorrsquos Degree in information systems. Dedicated and passionate IT professional with 7+ years of experience. 5+ years of retail experience either as a retail associatemanager, retail technologist or other related retail experience. 3+ years of experience with NCRrsquos POS CounterPoint systemsapplications. Experience designing and developing solutions. Experience with SQL including insertselectjoin queries, writing stored procedures and understanding database architecture.</body><cpc>0.20</cpc></job>
<job><location>Hopkins, MN, United States</location><title>MES Integration Developer</title><city>Hopkins</city><state>MN</state><zip>55343</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Contractor</job_type><posted_at>2018-12-08</posted_at><job_reference>6874_f52e23ab2ac2bd31bac91a725579a774</job_reference><company>Net2Source Inc.</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/1ajgtue?cs=e3e</url><body>Title  MES Integration Developer Location  Hopkins, MN Contract Length  12+ Months Mandatory Skills  4+ years of development experience on .Net Framework, C and Workflow solutions  Experience working with MES interfaces with Level 2 (PLC, SCADA etc..) and Level 4 (ERP..) Experience working with devices firmware and drivers.   Preferred Skills    Experience field mapping definitions for integrations between different systems.  Experience working on solutions using various integration middleware like TIBCO, API gateway, Webservices calls, File Share and MII  Knowledge on ISA 95 Standards Preferable to have Savigent Certification on Workflow and connector developments   Job RolesResponsibilities   Review the ToBe Process map to build field mapping for the integrations between systems.  Coordinate design of integration between L2-L3-L4 using appropriate integration components (Connectors) Build integrations components test the components with stub data and support integration testing Troubleshoot and fix integration issues from integration testing, user acceptance testing and Post go live support  Work with Solution Architect in resolving any integration issueschallenges between systems.   Thanks  Regards Ankit Raikuni Associate Recruiter Net2Source Inc. Corp HQ  317 George St., Suite 220, New Brunswick, NJ 08901 T (201) 340.8700 Ext.  560  D (201) 474-0198  F (201) 221.8131 Email araikuninet2source.com  httpnet2source.com   Web www.net2source.com  httpwww.net2source.com   LinkedIn http  ....  www.linkedin.cominankit-raikuni-05b6a513b  httpwww.linkedin.cominankit-raikuni-05b6a513b</body><cpc>0.20</cpc></job>
<job><location>Seven Hills, OH, United States</location><title>Release Developer</title><city>Seven Hills</city><state>OH</state><zip>44131</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Full Time</job_type><posted_at>2018-12-10</posted_at><job_reference>6874_aeaf505b01f0a21e04b438a8e3813415</job_reference><company>Acumen Solutions, Inc.</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/199mzg7?cs=e3e</url><body>Acumen Solutions drives excellence - not only in our performance, but also in the results we deliver for our clients. We are a global cloud consultancy that combines the insight of our strategists, the vision of our innovators, and the ingenuity of our engineers to achieve this extraordinary impact. The Fortune 500 trust us to build solutions focused on growing revenue and profits by amplifying competitive advantage and strengthening customer relationships. Our groundbreaking solutions in the public sector streamline operations and improve productivity. We apply this same focus on excellence to our unparalleled social responsibility program, generating sustainable impact across our local communities. Engage with us at www.acumensolutions.com  httpwww.acumensolutions.com  or on Twitter AcumenSolutions  httpstwitter.comAcumenSolutions . Acumen Solutions is currently hiring a Release Developer to join our team in our Cleveland, OH location. Role and Responsibilities We seek a talented release developer to join a strong technology team responsible for the implementation and support of high volume, high performance client facing applications. The candidate will provide deploymentrelease support for applications that are part of cloud based, mobile, andor on premise environments.  Great opportunity to be part of a new, growing office for an established company that provides cutting edge IT solutions to Fortune 500 and Public Sector clients. Essential Functions  Verify successful continuous delivery deployments  Maintain a version control repository  Deploy releases to a clientrsquos production environment  Review continuous delivery validation builds for failures  Move development and configuration work between version control branches  Resolve deployment issues with development and configuration teams  Qualifications  Interest in software release management  Self Managing  Understanding of waterfall, agile, and iterative development methodologies  Strong technical ability  Well Organized  Work well in teams  Ability to learn new applications quickly  Flexibility to work outside of business hours as a release schedule requires  Minimum Qualifications - Bachelorrsquos degree in Management Information SystemsComputer Information Systems or related field - Authorized to work for any U.S. employer Benefits   Acumen Solutions offers the opportunity for growth and advancement, as well as a competitive base salary, annual performance based incentives, medical, dental, and vision benefits, Paid Time Off, 401k, and more. About Us As a leading management and technology consulting firm, Acumen Solutions offers a range of challenging and rewarding opportunities whether yoursquore just starting out in your career, looking to advance your career, or seeking a senior leadership position. Acumen Solutions employees are ambitious, committed, passionate problem solvers.  EOE MFVD VEVRAA Federal Contractor</body><cpc>0.20</cpc></job>
<job><location>New Hope, MN, United States</location><title>Website UI Design</title><city>New Hope</city><state>MN</state><zip>55428</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Contractor</job_type><posted_at>2018-12-11</posted_at><job_reference>6874_a3698336cc11a94ca705043739514274</job_reference><company>Dahl Consulting</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/1ax0ist?cs=e3e</url><body>Website Designer Responsibilities Identify website needs for our target customers ndash participate in customer research that will inform how our digital properties support our customerrsquos journey. Conduct internal stakeholder interviews to understand internal user needs Use research to tell the customer story that our website design needs to support Translate research, user stories and strategy into an easy-to-use UI and site structure tailored to customer unique needs. Partner with marketing and research to understand and articulate customer needs Partner with technical teams to translate insights to UI and technology requirements Wireframe UI solutions, userflow diagrams, and sketches. Get stakeholder buy in and user feedback Make updates to site structure and design using tools and page templates, and partner with agency to execute dev updates  Update merchandising and content strategy for our website by redesigning structure and updating content on key pages Create an easy to shop store header design and navigation structure that helps our target customers accomplish their goal Partner with marketing on a content and messaging strategy to deliver the right messaging to the right customers at the right time on our site Give photographer and graphic teams clear direction for photoshoot needs for content   Experience Experience creating and successfully implementing UI design and strategy Knowledge of Javascript, XML, HTML, CSS a plus Hands-on experience in designing for applications using WebSphere Commerce Suite a plus Understanding of WCS data model a plus</body><cpc>0.20</cpc></job>
<job><location>Des Moines, IA, United States</location><title>Infrastructure Technical Specialist</title><city>Des Moines</city><state>IA</state><zip>50319</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Full Time</job_type><posted_at>2018-12-12</posted_at><job_reference>6874_85795ed31387137393131119b8bdea20</job_reference><company>Spectra Infosystems</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/1c0e814?cs=e3e</url><body>Infrastructure Technical Specialist (INTS) with State of Iowa-OCIO   Interview Web Cam or In Person Interview Work Location 1305 E Walnut, Des Moines, IA 50319   The Infrastructure Technical Specialist (INTS) is a senior level resource with specialized knowledge and experience in specific technologies with an emphasis is on storage management.   OVERVIEW  This is an onsite position ndash no remote option for this role.    The INTS has an overall knowledge of IT infrastructure and architecture that serves as a strong base for technical expertise in a specific product or program. The emphasis of this position is on storage management, and the agency is looking for a person who is responsible for the entire system, not just someone whorsquos brought in on a project basis to migrate from one platform to another. The right candidate is someone who has strong experience managing the entire system. The emphasis of this position is on STORAGE MANAGEMENT, specifically someone with hands-on experience managing a large storage system end to end. The candidates for this position should be experienced doing the day-to-day feeding and monitoring of systems, in addition to doing must-have changes, studying performance statistics, communicating when upgrades are required, maintenance is required, capacity is needed, as well as many other issues.      NOTE   The department sees this as a long-term engagement and not just a project.   The type of candidate required for this opportunity is someone who has extensive experience managing the entire system, not just someone who is brought in on a project basis to migrate from one platform to another. The department is not looking someone who has done a lot of migrations from one backup system to another backup system, one of those being IBM, and not so much hands-on storage. The backups are not the priority for this position.  SCOPE bull   Perform configuration management, problem management and monitoring of enterprise data storage systems.  bull   Provision storage for use by mainframes, virtual and physical servers and databases. bull   Collaborate with other IT personnel on technology and support design and issues. bull   Configure and manage DR replication to ensure the ability to recover systems during outage events rapidly. bull   Monitor health and utilization of systems. Perform trending and performance analysis. Provide health and performance reporting and take appropriate actions based on trends in data.  EXPERIENCE  Demonstrated experience of at least four years in architecting and hands-on administration, configuration, and performance troubleshooting of IBM storage at an enterprise level  bull   Working knowledge of IBM SAN Volume Controller (SVC) and IBM V7000 bull   IBM mainframe storage and virtual tape management   bull   SAN administration including zoning, LUN security, and HBA configuration bull   Experience with SAN replication technologies and disaster recovery planning bull   Working knowledge of basic RAID, storage tiering, storage architecture concepts, storage virtualization, replication processes, and storage best practices bull   Experience monitoring and troubleshooting storage performance. IBM TPC experience preferred bull   IBM Spectrum Protect or Tivoli Storage Manager experience a plus bull   NetApp Data OnTap experience a plus bull   Demonstrated ability to identify, research and analyze technical problems and recommend solutions bull   Demonstrated ability to interact, advise, guide, train, and communicate effectively and professionally bull   Demonstrated ability to read and write fluently in English   SkillRequired  DesiredAmountof ExperienceWorking knowledge of IBM SAN Volume Controller (SVC) and IBM V7000Required4YearsIBM mainframe storage and virtual tape managementRequired4YearsSAN administration including zoning, LUN security, and HBA configurationRequired4YearsExperience with SAN replication technologies and disaster recovery planningRequired4YearsExperience wbasic RAID, storage tiering, storage architecture concepts, storage virtualization, replication processes and storage best practicesRequired4YearsExperience monitoring and troubleshooting storage performance. IBM TPC experience preferredRequired4YearsIBM Spectrum Protect or Tivoli Storage Manager experience a plusDesired2YearsNetApp Data OnTap experience a plusDesired2YearsDemonstrated ability to identify, research and analyze technical problems and recommend solutionsRequired4YearsDemonstrated ability to interact, advise, guide, train, and communicate effectively and professionallyRequired4YearsDemonstrated ability to read and write fluently in EnglishRequired   Michael  Spectra Infosystems Tel +1 571-482-1375 michaelspectrasystems.net    11539 Park Woods Circle,Suite 105,Alpharetta GA 30005 WMBE and CMMI L3, ISO 9001,20000,27001 Certified  Inc 5000 Honoree- Fastest Growing companies in USA</body><cpc>0.20</cpc></job>
<job><location>Downers Grove, IL, United States</location><title>Senior Azure Consultant  (Full time / Perm)</title><city>Downers Grove</city><state>IL</state><zip>60515</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Full Time</job_type><posted_at>2018-12-08</posted_at><job_reference>6874_deea8f3f3d26c67d54a7252e0ab2e58b</job_reference><company>ENSONO</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/1bklkyv?cs=e3e</url><body>As an Azure Cloud Consultant, you will design, configure and implement cutting edge enterprise Microsoft cloud technology solutions to provide clients with a cloud platform  foundation for success. With a clear focus on delivering the best value to clients for their Microsoft investment, you will work through the complete consulting life cycle, including (but not limited to) Design Running Design workshops, creating solution design documentation, presentations, working closely with the customer to scope project requirements and integration with  their existing systems. Deployment Configuration, integration, testing, optimization and implementation of solutions.  Responsibilities  Work with solution teams to develop offerings and involve in designing solutions for new business opportunities and proposals  Demonstrate capabilities by providing value added information to clients for connecting technology and business value in the solutions developed  Possess a strong background in enterprise-level architecture design  Work closely with Senior Solution Architect for the Microsoft Azure business practice  Skills  Technical o Azure (IaaS, PaaS, Networking etc.) o Identity o Office 365 o Citrix o System Center  Non-Technical o Self-motivated and enthusiastic o Highly organized o Excellent written and oral communication o Respectful of others and high degree of integrity Please note This is a direct hire, full-time opportunity with Ensono. No third parties or contractors please. Unable to help with sponsorship at this time for this role.</body><cpc>0.20</cpc></job>
<job><location>Purchase, NY, United States</location><title>Guidewire Policy Center Sr Developer</title><city>Purchase</city><state>NY</state><zip>10577</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Contractor</job_type><posted_at>2018-12-10</posted_at><job_reference>6874_9166ab89afc81c7d2c7e67792758192e</job_reference><company>iTech Solutions</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/1ashd1o?cs=e3e</url><body>Guidewire Policy Center Senior Developer  We are seeking a Guidewire Policy Center Senior Developer to join our team that will be responsible for the overall plan, design, development and release of Guidewire Policy Center products.   Main areas of responsibility Responsible for leading end-to-end Guidewire Policy Center product implementations. Lead the overall requirements review, assessment and high level and detailed sizing of required configuration and technical effort. Lead the technical design and specifications in line with traceable user-stories  requirements and according to Guidewire and development best-practices. Lead and guide product modelling reviews and required technical design and configurations for new products Collaborate with Business Analysts and Business Architects to interpret, clarify and plan for the implementation of user stories. Conduct and lead joint design sessions to help coach solutioning the end product and to capture sizing information required for resourcing and scheduling. Lead the overall technical solution design and delivery through coordinating with all stakeholders and leading onshore  offshore development teams for scheduling and managing assigned tasks and milestones. Establish sound working relationships with Business Analysis and Quality Assurance Teams to ensure that priorities are reviewed and agreed-upon and that development activities are reviewed and planned for accordingly. Provide periodic updates through Rally, TFS or other life-cycle management tools  processes for full visibility and transparency into the development activities. Responsible for hands-on Configuring and extending products, screens, flows, business logic and rating rules using Guidewire Studio Leveraging available accelerators to accelerate development activities and make reuse of proven architectural patterns Establishing sound and proven architectural, development and integration best-practices, patterns and tooling to ensure that the delivered code is standards-based, code-reviewed with supporting artifacts, reusable and can be supported and maintained (for future product introductions and upgrades) Managing application configuration and releases, and performing minor  major software upgrades Ensuring that respective production and non-production environments and branching (feature  main  release) are set-up, functional and is updated as development occurs across different product lines. Establishing and executing traceable unit (gunit, junit, etc.) and integration tests (preferably through standardized automation as part of continuous integration).     Qualifications, Skills and Experience Guidewire Policy Center Configuration certification required (version 8 preferred). Minimum of 3+ years of experience with Guidewire PolicyCenter development as a Technical Lead with two end-to-end product implementations (GL, Property or PL experience strongly preferred). Strong and demonstrable leadership and application ownership (post-implementation) with Guidewire Policy Center product implementations is required. 5+ years of experience leading and managing onshore  offshore development teams for one or multiple Guidewire product implementations. 5+ years of experience in Guidewire Software Suite of applications. 5+ years of Java development experience. Certification in Guidewire Policy Center integration with a demonstrated hands-on experience is preferred. Demonstrated expertise and experience with Guidewire APIs, Product Designer, GX Model, Integrations and Product Model development (for integration, testing and data migrations). Demonstrable knowledge of and experience with Guidewire Rating engine, Rating workbooks and Rating logic configurations. Experience is required with ALM best-practices in managing code versioning (and associated environments), integration, releasing and maintaining Guidewire Policy Center products (during development and in production as application owner). Experience with installing, partitioning and managing Guidewire suite applications for high performance, scalability and reuse. Knowledge of secure software development practices and expert understanding of architectural standards, patterns and best-practices with respect to Guidewire configuration and integration is required. Knowledge of Commercial PC insurance highly preferred. Excellent problem-solving and analytical skills. Comfort with ambiguity and ability to navigate through and lead teams to solutioning. Experienced with Agile SCRUM methodology and tooling (TFS, Rally, JIRA, etc.) in a technical owner  development track lead capacity. Bachelor&apos;s degree in Computer Science, Management Information Systems, Mathematics or related field is strongly preferred.  For more information please contact Brian Otten at 203-433-7817.   Since 1995, iTech Solutions Inc., has been providing IT Consulting and Direct Hire Services to the Insurance, Financial, Communications, Manufacturing and Government sectors with local offices in Connecticut, Minnesota, Colorado, Massachusetts, Tennessee, North Carolina, and New Jersey  Pennsylvania area.   Our recruiting strategy is simple, if you want to find qualified IT professionals then use IT professionals to find them.  So at iTech Solutions, our personnel are all career IT professionals with a wide range of IT experience. We can honestly say our staff understands the technologies, the complexities of finding and selecting the appropriate personnel and the pressures of running successful IT projects.    Employer will not sponsor applicants for any employment visas, at hiring or in the future, including but not limited to H-1B visas. Corp-to-Corp or subcontract personnel will not be considered for this position.</body><cpc>0.20</cpc></job>
<job><location>Los Angeles, CA, United States</location><title>Senior Node Engineer</title><city>Los Angeles</city><state>CA</state><zip>90025</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Full Time</job_type><posted_at>2018-12-11</posted_at><job_reference>6874_d6834976a8e2dacc5eaf6396b85995f5</job_reference><company>Talener</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/199mcrs?cs=e3e</url><body>The CompanyLocated in Santa Monica, our client is a startup focused on saving customers money!  Their unique platform finds price adjustments on previous purchases and gets you the difference. The JobOur client is looking for a Senior Back End Node Developer with 6 or more years of professional development experience using Node and JavaScript. This role will be assisting in the architecture and implementation of automation bots, building APIs, and working with data pipelines to create the best user experience. Prior experience with AWS, SQL or NoSQL, and RESTful services is a plus. Required Skills 6+ years of professional experience with back end development Development experience with Node and JavaScript Comfortable with Bots, Automation, andor data Computer Science degree required Additional Skills Prior experience working with AWS, SQL or NoSQL, and RESTful services Experience with web scraping, puppeteer, PhantomJS or similar platforms Strong Git skills while working with an Agile team Experience with Google Chrome and JavaScript in the Browser Must have can-do attitude, with an ambition to commit to work Highly organized, results-oriented and attentive to details Comfortable in a startup environment The Offer Competitive salary, based on experience Equity Medical, vision, dental, and life insurance benefits Flexible work hours Generous PTO Catered lunches twice a week Local candidates only please. Talener strives to meet their candidates and clients in person in order to ensure the right fit for everyone. Only candidates who are authorized to work in the United States for any employer will be considered. Our client cannot provide sponsorship at this time.</body><cpc>0.20</cpc></job>
<job><location>Long Beach, CA, United States</location><title>5242  Certified Symantec Management Suite Engineer (soCal based)</title><city>Long Beach</city><state>CA</state><zip>90801</zip><country>United States</country><job_type>Full Time</job_type><posted_at>2018-12-08</posted_at><job_reference>6874_c3c6b15f32dd7c6c0cfd52b511da8403</job_reference><company>Kapital Data Corp</company><mobile_friendly_apply>No</mobile_friendly_apply><category></category><html_jobs>No</html_jobs><url>https://click.appcast.io/track/1ax0ie2?cs=e3e</url><body>Software Packaging Desktop Engineer MUST be  Certified Symantec Management Suite Engineer  Contract to hire, salary may not exceed 80K.  NO Visa sponsorship available for this role. The client is able to hire US Citizen or US Perm ResidentsGreen Card Holders.      Description of duties TROUBLESHOOTING ALL CHANCELLOR&apos;S OFFICE WORKSTATIONS, LAPTOPS, HARDWARE, PERIPHERALS AND APPLICATIONS -Record and update all service requests in Chancellor&apos;s Office IT ticketing system. -Provide application support for the core CO applications including the MS Office suite, Internet Explorer, Adobe Professional, VPN, Smartphones, etc. -Provide coverage for after hours on-call support as required. -Serve as the primary 24x7 executive support contact. -Install, configure, update, and troubleshoot and provide on-site training for current MicrosoftApple operating systems, peripherals, and applications used by the Chancellor&apos;s Office.  -Install, configure, and deploy user hardware, software, and devices. Furthermore, manage central print server. -Provide and maintain documentation on configuration, deployment, and maintenance of supported technology. -Provide technical support for Chancellor&apos;s Office executives and hosted events. -Develop, troubleshoot, and deploy software packages. -Collect and analyze application requirements, dependencies and interactions for production deployments.  -Assist, develop, and implement a quality assurance testing environment for all deployment packages. -Assist, and develop software installations and deployment packages. -Assist, develop, optimize, and maintain CO standard computer image builds. -Assist, develop, optimize, and test OS based scripts for software installation and removal. -Install and configure computer hardware and software and a variety of other client server applications. -Install, configure and develop asset tracking of Chancellor assists including but not limited to, docking stations, power supplies, monitors, projectors, scanners, printers, computers (laptopdesktoptablet), co issued smartphones. Furthermore, track license management, perform analysis and recommendation for simplification of license management. Develop association between purchase order, invoice number, license acknowledgement and serialization and compliance. Moreover, perform routine audits on license pool and application metering. -Install and configure patch management system. Which include development of policies, patch deployment and remediation and reporting. In addition to patch management duties, incumbent will assist Information Security department with perform routine audit of our infrastructure within industry best practices. -Image and install VDI training room machines in a timely manner. Interface with a variety of software vendors to ensure accurate configuration of software for end user custom training classes. -Perform standard AppleHPDellMicrosoft diagnostic tests and submit parts and repair technician requests using the Apple Depot service, HPDell Next Day business, Microsoft depot warranty service. -Provide direction and assistance to the User Services team related to patch management and asset management, assist desktop engineer with the deployment of software packages.  ASSIST AND DEVELOP, TROUBLESHOOT, AND DEPLOY VIRTUAL APPLICATION PACKAGES INCLUDING -Collect and analyze application requirements, dependencies, and interactions for production deployments.  -Assist, develop and implement a quality assurance test environments for virtualized deployment packages. -Develop provisioning documentation for support staff. -Develop and maintain CO virtualized applications, virtual application provisioning, and maintenance of virtualized package user settings. The Software Packaging Desktop Systems Engineer is also responsible for any other duties as assigned. In addition, the incumbent is responsible for keeping current in the industry including technology changes, trends and best practices. The incumbent is also responsible for addressing any concerns regarding technical operations with the appropriate supervisor.  Qualifications This position requires -A Bachelor&apos;s degree in Computer Science or a related field, or an equivalent combination of education and experience of two years of progressive desktop support activities. -DellHP Premier Access Certification for production models. If not currently held, must be obtained within six months of position appointment. -Minimum of 2 years of Symantec Management Suite experience preferable ITSM v7 or v8. Certification preferred.  COMMUNICATION  PEOPLE SKILLS -Solid written communication skills to provide accurate technical documentation. -Supports an environment that motivates others and builds morale. -Works effectively and cooperatively with other team members to achieve goals and developmaintain working relationships. -Ability to effectively communicate with various users. -Uses effective communication and listening skills in order to work with others and problem solve. -Ability to quickly gather information from and disseminate information to the appropriate parties. -Ability to present technical information at training classes. -Comfortable with providing executive level support.  ANALYTICAL SKILLS -Ability to assist in trouble-shooting, including quickly identifying problems and acting appropriately. -Develops practical and thorough solutions to address all aspects of identified problems. -Identifies problems and uses appropriate sources to research technical solutions. -Ability to independently apply technical judgment to standard applications and systems. -Ability to perform analysis and determination of root cause.  PROJECT MANAGEMENT SKILLS -Ability to track and document information between multiple parties. -Experience in coordinating resource requirements. -Pays attention to detail and has solid organizational skills. -Ability to schedule and prioritize in order to meet deadlines. -Ability to work independently with little supervision.  TECHNICAL SKILLS -Proficiency in Microsoft Office Productivity Suite (Word, Excel, Power Point, and Outlook), Project, Visio and the windows registry required. -Expertise in computer networking as well as experience with consumer routers, switches and VPN clients and iOS and Android devices. -Minimum of a year of progressive responsibility in independently developing, testing, and troubleshooting software deployment packages using a variety of captureprovisioning tools. Admin Studio preferred. -Expertise in Symantec Management Suite software delivery techniques. -Expertise in Symantec Management Suite software asset management (including license management) techniques. -Expertise in Symantec Management Suite software patch management techniques. -Expertise in current Microsoft operating systems troubleshooting in a medium (400 computers) to large (over 400 computers) networked environment. -Proficiency in SQL query language. -Experience providing floor support and help desk analysis for networked end user computers. -Solid programing experience with scripting, with an emphasis in PowerShell scripting, windows batchcommand scripts, visual basic scripting, and WMI scripting.   Required skills and experience Desktop Software Imaging development, and deployment. Develop Desktop Images, maintain updates, and deploy updates required. Interview Type Phone Interview Comments (optional) M-F 8-5, Will review resumes on 12318, and interview on 12518.  Contract to hire, salary may not exceed 80K</body><cpc>0.20</cpc></job>
</jobs><generation_time>2018-12-12 03:33:47 -0500</generation_time><jobs_count>37539</jobs_count></source>