<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<jobs total_matches="7467" version="2.0">
 <job>
  <job_id>22792550</job_id>
  <job_title>Cashier</job_title>
  <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
  <description>As a Cashier, you will operate a cash drawer and be responsible for taking the customers' orders and payments, giving them back any change they are due, processing their payments, and delivering both the customers' orders and their sales receipts. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Typically, you will be working a regular 8-hour workday. For most of the day, you will be stationed inside the store at a particular cash register, the contents of which will be the Cashier's cash drawer. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
You will be assigned to a cash register and you will be responsible for healthily maintaining the level of cash in the drawer, as well as the necessary coins needed to dispense change to customers who pay with larger bills (also be fulfilling credit and debit card transactions).</description>
  <location_text>Aurora, Colorado</location_text>
  <distance></distance>
  <latitude>39.729430</latitude>
  <longitude>-104.831920</longitude>
  <industry>Retail|Retail Cashier</industry>
  <company>Mile High Gas &amp;amp; Smoke Shop</company>
  <post_date>Fri, 31 May 2019  09:40:47 GMT</post_date>
  <expiry_date>Sun, 30 Jun 2019  23:59:59 GMT</expiry_date>
  <job_url>https://www.resume-library.com/feed/click/356/22792550?dpj=yes</job_url>
  <apply_url>https://www.resume-library.com/feed/apply_click/356/22792550</apply_url>
  <salary_text></salary_text>
  <annual_salary_max></annual_salary_max>
  <annual_salary_min></annual_salary_min>
 </job>
 <job>
  <job_id>22792549</job_id>
  <job_title>Team Member Steak 'n Shake</job_title>
  <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
  <description>Provide hospitable service to all guests following Steak n Shakes steps of service &lt;br /&gt;
 Ability to work in a fun and fast-paced environment &lt;br /&gt;
Practices selling plus provides prompt, courteous service to all Steak N Shake &lt;br /&gt;
 Rings up all sales on the cash register; properly and accurately handles money and all other types of payment received for products sold. &lt;br /&gt;
Ability to retain menu item information &lt;br /&gt;
Prepare and deliver drinks and other menu items in an expedient manner &lt;br /&gt;
Preparing STEAKBURGER sandwiches, melts, and all other grill products &lt;br /&gt;
Process cash, credit and coupon transactions quickly &lt;br /&gt;
Performs those housecleaning &amp; stocking duties necessary to maintain restaurant cleanliness; performs basic upkeep and/or cleaning of all equipment in the store as required and specified by the store manager. &lt;br /&gt;
 Maintain safety and security procedures as required &lt;br /&gt;
 Maintain uniform standards at all times &lt;br /&gt;
 Maintain Company policies and standards at all times &lt;br /&gt;
 Knows and follows company policy and procedures for carrying out shoplifting and robbery preventive measures. &lt;br /&gt;
 Does not disclose any confidential or proprietary information regarding the Petroleum Wholesale Corporation, coworkers or former employees of Petroleum Wholesale to any outside person or agency; refers all requests for information to the Corporate office. &lt;br /&gt;
 Physically able to lift at least forty (30) pounds. &lt;br /&gt;
 Accomplishes any other duties necessary for the operation and maintenance of the store in an efficient, profitable and safe manner, as directed by Store Manager.</description>
  <location_text>Midland, Texas</location_text>
  <distance></distance>
  <latitude>31.997350</latitude>
  <longitude>-102.077910</longitude>
  <industry></industry>
  <company>Petroleum Wholesale</company>
  <post_date>Fri, 31 May 2019  09:40:44 GMT</post_date>
  <expiry_date>Sun, 30 Jun 2019  23:59:59 GMT</expiry_date>
  <job_url>https://www.resume-library.com/feed/click/356/22792549?dpj=yes</job_url>
  <apply_url>https://www.resume-library.com/feed/apply_click/356/22792549</apply_url>
  <salary_text></salary_text>
  <annual_salary_max></annual_salary_max>
  <annual_salary_min></annual_salary_min>
 </job>
 <job>
  <job_id>22792548</job_id>
  <job_title>Cook And Front Of House</job_title>
  <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
  <description>SAJJ Mediterranean is looking for enthusiastic personnel to join the team. &lt;br /&gt;
Company perks consist of a positive and fun work environment with opportunity for growth/promotion and competitive pay-rates. &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
Currently looking to fill Cook and Front of House positions &lt;br /&gt;
Full-time and part-time positions available. &lt;br /&gt;
No experience needed &lt;br /&gt;
Able to speak, at least, minimal English (to communicate with customers) &lt;br /&gt;
Menlo Park Location at 883 Hamilton Ave &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
Can apply to this ad or in-store. &lt;br /&gt;
Se solicitan cocinero/as, ayudantes de cocina/frente de casa. &lt;br /&gt;
Sueldo a convenir, no se requiere experiencia pero perferido, horario depende. La tienda esta abierta desde Lunes a Viernes. &lt;br /&gt;
Un poco de Ingles se necesita para comunicarse con los clientes. &lt;br /&gt;
Muchas oportunidades de promocion com SAJJ Mediterranean. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Locacion en Menlo Park esta en 883 Hamilton Ave &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Puede responder a este anuncio o en persona en la tienda.</description>
  <location_text>Palo Alto, California</location_text>
  <distance></distance>
  <latitude>37.441880</latitude>
  <longitude>-122.143020</longitude>
  <industry>Hospitality|Food &amp;amp; Beverage|Waiting &amp;amp; Bar Staff</industry>
  <company>SAJJ Mediterranean</company>
  <post_date>Fri, 31 May 2019  09:40:44 GMT</post_date>
  <expiry_date>Sun, 30 Jun 2019  23:59:59 GMT</expiry_date>
  <job_url>https://www.resume-library.com/feed/click/356/22792548?dpj=yes</job_url>
  <apply_url>https://www.resume-library.com/feed/apply_click/356/22792548</apply_url>
  <salary_text></salary_text>
  <annual_salary_max></annual_salary_max>
  <annual_salary_min></annual_salary_min>
 </job>
 <job>
  <job_id>22792547</job_id>
  <job_title>Cook And Front Of House</job_title>
  <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
  <description>SAJJ Mediterranean is looking for enthusiastic personnel to join the team. &lt;br /&gt;
Company perks consist of a positive and fun work environment with opportunity for growth/promotion and competitive pay-rates. &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
Currently looking to fill Cook and Front of House positions &lt;br /&gt;
Full-time and part-time positions available. &lt;br /&gt;
No experience needed &lt;br /&gt;
Drivers License preferred &lt;br /&gt;
Able to speak, at least, minimal English (to communicate with customers) &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
Se solicitan cocinero/as, ayudantes de cocina/frente de casa. &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
Sueldo a convenir, no se requiere experiencia pero perferido, horario depende. &lt;br /&gt;
Experencia no es necesario &lt;br /&gt;
Licensia de manejar es preferido. &lt;br /&gt;
Un poco de Ingles se necesita para comunicarse con los clientes. &lt;br /&gt;
Muchas oportunidades de promocion con SAJJ Mediterranean porque la compania esta en un estado de crecimento.</description>
  <location_text>Sunnyvale, California</location_text>
  <distance></distance>
  <latitude>37.368830</latitude>
  <longitude>-122.036350</longitude>
  <industry>Hospitality|Food &amp;amp; Beverage|Culinary|Cook</industry>
  <company>SAJJ Mediterranean</company>
  <post_date>Fri, 31 May 2019  09:40:43 GMT</post_date>
  <expiry_date>Sun, 30 Jun 2019  23:59:59 GMT</expiry_date>
  <job_url>https://www.resume-library.com/feed/click/356/22792547?dpj=yes</job_url>
  <apply_url>https://www.resume-library.com/feed/apply_click/356/22792547</apply_url>
  <salary_text></salary_text>
  <annual_salary_max></annual_salary_max>
  <annual_salary_min></annual_salary_min>
 </job>
 <job>
  <job_id>22792546</job_id>
  <job_title>Travel CT Tech</job_title>
  <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
  <description>Supplemental Health Care is partnering with a prestigious hospital to hire an experienced Travel CT Tech in Grass Valley, CA! &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
- Contract starting on June 25th&lt;br /&gt;
- Duties: will perform CT, MRI and General X-Ray scans&lt;br /&gt;
- Working Tues-Fri from 11:30a - 8:00p &amp; 8:00a-4:30p on Saturdays. May have on-call on holidays.&lt;br /&gt;
- This is a 13 week contract assignment with a possibility of an extension&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
To Apply: Please contact the Recruiting Manager, Amber Caldwell, for immediate consideration at: ************.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Supplemental Health Care Benefits include: Day One Medical Insurance, Vision/Dental/Prescription Insurance, 401K plan, State License Reimbursement, Housing and Transportation Assistance.</description>
  <location_text>Grass Valley, California</location_text>
  <distance></distance>
  <latitude>39.219060</latitude>
  <longitude>-121.061060</longitude>
  <industry></industry>
  <company>Supplemental Health Care</company>
  <post_date>Fri, 31 May 2019  09:37:47 GMT</post_date>
  <expiry_date>Sun, 30 Jun 2019  23:59:59 GMT</expiry_date>
  <job_url>https://www.resume-library.com/feed/click/356/22792546?dpj=yes</job_url>
  <apply_url>https://www.resume-library.com/feed/apply_click/356/22792546</apply_url>
  <salary_text></salary_text>
  <annual_salary_max></annual_salary_max>
  <annual_salary_min></annual_salary_min>
 </job>
 <job>
  <job_id>22792380</job_id>
  <job_title>Administrative Assistant in Springdale, PA</job_title>
  <job_type>Contract</job_type>
  <description>POSITION TITLE: ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANT&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
LOCATION: SPRINGDALE, PA&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
ZIP CODE: 15144&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
DURATION: 6+ MONTHS CONTRACT (POSSIBLE EXTENSION)&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
SHIFT: MONDAY - FRIDAY 7:30 A.M. - 4:00 P.M.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
PAY RATE: $13/HR (WITHOUT BENEFITS)&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
JOB DESCRIPTION:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
* Uses designated software packages including word processing, spreadsheet, database management, and presentation software in the performance of position tasks. A minimum of 60 wpm is required. Assists employers by performing secretarial and administrative tasks. Handles high volume of detailed work. Compiles, analyses, and reconciles reports. Prepares and verifies weekly, monthly, quarterly, and annual reports such as indexes, budgets, inventories, etc. Organizes employers appointment schedule. Maintains business records and files. Opens and sorts incoming mail and prepares replies or directs mail to their employers for reply. Arranges conferences and travel accommodations. Handles purchase orders, payments of bills, and expense vouchers. Works with confidential materials, personnel records, pay roll and salary data. Works with minimal supervision. May be skilled in a specific work environment, such as legal, finance or marketing. Prepares letters, memos, invoices, manuscripts, and other business documents as directed, using designated word processing software</description>
  <location_text>Springdale, Pennsylvania</location_text>
  <distance></distance>
  <latitude>40.540900</latitude>
  <longitude>-79.783940</longitude>
  <industry>Administration|Administrator</industry>
  <company>Software Specialists</company>
  <post_date>Fri, 31 May 2019  09:12:25 GMT</post_date>
  <expiry_date>Sun, 30 Jun 2019  23:59:59 GMT</expiry_date>
  <job_url>https://www.resume-library.com/feed/click/356/22792380?dpj=yes</job_url>
  <apply_url>https://www.resume-library.com/feed/apply_click/356/22792380</apply_url>
  <salary_text>USD 13.00 to 13.00 per hour</salary_text>
  <annual_salary_max>25349</annual_salary_max>
  <annual_salary_min>25349</annual_salary_min>
 </job>
<job>
  <job_id>22783076</job_id>
  <job_title>Information Security Engineer</job_title>
  <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
  <description>LOCATION: Greater Chicagoland area near the Loop&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
OVERVIEW OF THE POSITION: &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Our client, one of Chicago's Best and Brightest Companies to work for, is currently seeking a Information Security Engineer. We really love working with this company because they pride themselves on being a great place to work, and strive for a true work-life-balance.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
RESPONSIBILITIES:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
* Identify and define system security requirements and design the security monitoring infrastructure for on-site and cloud solutions.&lt;br /&gt;
* Establish technical solutions and new security tools to reduce security vulnerabilities&lt;br /&gt;
* Construct and troubleshoot security infrastructure devices&lt;br /&gt;
* Create and support processes to monitor network traffic for abnormal activity&lt;br /&gt;
* Implement Infosec best practices&lt;br /&gt;
* Monitor network, devices and computer systems&lt;br /&gt;
* Develop security test plans&lt;br /&gt;
* Perform vulnerability assessments and application security evaluations&lt;br /&gt;
* Effective new software/hardware configurations for standards&lt;br /&gt;
* Aid 3rd party security assessments&lt;br /&gt;
* Investigate security incidents and fix and established procedures&lt;br /&gt;
* Inspect suspicious files&lt;br /&gt;
* Perform malware analysis&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
SKILLS:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
* Bachelor's degree with 2+ years' of experience in an IT security capacity&lt;br /&gt;
* Information security certifications GCIA, CISSP, GCIA,GMON, GCIH or others&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
WHEN RESPONDING TO THIS OPPORTUNITY:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Resumes without the required technical skills and experience will not be considered. Although a strong desire for a certain type of position is a credit to your goal, experience is necessary. Our client is not considering sponsorship at this time and is not open to relocation expenses.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
ID#: 13173 - INFORMATION SECURITY ENGINEER</description>
  <location_text>Chicago, Illinois</location_text>
  <distance></distance>
  <latitude>41.850030</latitude>
  <longitude>-87.650050</longitude>
  <industry>Security &amp;amp; Safety|Security</industry>
  <company>TeamBradley</company>
  <post_date>Thu, 30 May 2019  09:06:38 GMT</post_date>
  <expiry_date>Sat, 29 Jun 2019  23:59:59 GMT</expiry_date>
  <job_url>https://www.resume-library.com/feed/click/356/22783076?dpj=yes</job_url>
  <apply_url>https://www.resume-library.com/feed/apply_click/356/22783076</apply_url>
  <salary_text></salary_text>
  <annual_salary_max></annual_salary_max>
  <annual_salary_min></annual_salary_min>
 </job>
 <job>
  <job_id>22783075</job_id>
  <job_title>Instrumentation Technician</job_title>
  <job_type>Permanent</job_type>
  <description>The Middlesex County Utilities Authority is looking to hire a Junior level F/T Instrumentation Technician at its Central Treatment Plant in Sayreville, NJ. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Summary: This position Inspects, installs, calibrates, repairs, troubleshoots and maintains all types of digital and analog instruments, process control systems, alarm systems, chart recorders, and other data acquisition and control equipment in use throughout wastewater treatment plant, pump stations and other locations. This position visually inspects, observes, and tests instrumentation apparatus, machinery, wiring, equipment and systems including pneumatic, digital, electro-hydraulic, computer/PLC driven equipment, VFDs, HMIs and related instrumentation devices.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
E + E: Associate in Arts Degree (A.A.) with a concentration in instrumentation, electronics, computer science or related field; and two (2) years experience involving the installation, maintenance and repair of electrical or electronic components, equipment or systems. Substitution clause: High School Diploma or General Equivalency Diploma (GED) with completion of a four (4) year vocational or technical school electrical/electronic education/training or apprentice certificate.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The salary range for the position is $36,300 - $83,610 with a starting rate of up to $55,000/DOQ. The MCUA is a public sector agency offering competitive pay and benefits, including good pay progression. For a copy of the full job description or to apply, interested candidates should send a request or submit a resume and cover letter.</description>
  <location_text>Sayreville, New Jersey</location_text>
  <distance></distance>
  <latitude>40.465380</latitude>
  <longitude>-74.330430</longitude>
  <industry>Engineering|Technician</industry>
  <company>Middlesex County Utilities Authority</company>
  <post_date>Wed, 29 May 2019  00:00:00 GMT</post_date>
  <expiry_date>Fri, 28 Jun 2019  23:59:59 GMT</expiry_date>
  <job_url>https://www.resume-library.com/feed/click/356/22783075?dpj=yes</job_url>
  <apply_url>https://www.resume-library.com/feed/apply_click/356/22783075</apply_url>
  <salary_text></salary_text>
  <annual_salary_max>83610</annual_salary_max>
  <annual_salary_min>36300</annual_salary_min>
 </job>
 <next_url>
  <value><![CDATA[https://www.resume-library.com/feed/v2/jobsearch?auth=nwjptrjireya&partner_feed_id=356&cc=AoFf6dxT]]></value>
 </next_url>
</jobs>
